<channel xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:bc="http://www.brightcove.com/link" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:fn="http://www.w3.org/2005/xpath-functions" xmlns:functx="http://www.functx.com" id="Rminutemag1.2280" token="1422747632" name="feed" domain="http://feed" requestUrl="/xslt/transform?template=time-to-mpp&amp;bucket=ew&amp;order=published&amp;before=now&amp;limit=150&amp;f=200847&amp;cid=Rminutemag1.2280&amp;bit=Entertainment+Weekly"><item id="urn:onebot:article:39c719d709dc24e2ecf63d7b2e717ed8" t="1422684903" feed="200847" position="1"><title>'Hawaii Five-0' fan recap: The return of Joe White</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/31/hawaii-five-0-recap-the-return-of-joe-white/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-1.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-5.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-4.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-3.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Season 5 | Episode 13 | “La Po’ino” | Aired Jan 30, 2015</strong></p> <p>Joe White is back on <em>Hawaii Five-0</em>! Joe (Terry O’Quinn) is transporting a man in medical quarantine, and Steve meets them at the airport. The patient is Mitch Lange, the first American to contract a new strain of bird flu with an 85 percent mortality rate. Steve is helping Joe and his team transport Lange to receive treatment.</p> <p>In the car, Joe and Steve catch up. Joe asks about Mary and the team, and they awkwardly skirt around the Wo Fat-shaped elephant in the room. Finally Joe offers to answer all of Steve’s questions. He admits he knew about Doris’ relationship with Wo Fat, but he promised her he would never tell Steve. But now Steve deserves answers. (Side note: Joe seems to know none of the drama from the 100th episode. I feel like that warrants at least an email or something.) <span id="more-33859"></span></p> <p>Steve asks Joe where Doris is hiding, but despite the answers Joe promised all of six seconds ago, he doesn’t want to tell. Is Steve going to arrest his own mother? But before Steve can answer, <a href="http://youtu.be/My2FRPA3Gf8?t=41s">Miley Cyrus swings in on a wrecking ball</a>, T-boning the car. (Just kidding, it’s terrorists.)</p> <p>Men storm out, killing Joe’s team and taking the van with Lange inside. Steve and Joe are trapped in their wrecked car, but Steve manages to free them. He calls Chin to get GPS on the stolen van and takes off on a police motorcycle after the bad guys. Steve finds the van parked in a lot, but it’s empty. The men and Lange are already gone. The only reason they would have taken Lange is to weaponize the virus.</p> <p>Steve and Joe get stitched up at the hospital, and after Danny rips his <del>husband</del> partner a new one for getting injured again, he gives them an update. Such a well-organized hit must be an act of terrorism. All of the ways off the island are being monitored.</p> <p><img style="float:left;margin:0 10px 10px 0;" title="Hawaii Five-0 " src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-4.jpg" alt="Hawaii Five-0 " />Back at HQ, Dr. Dyer from the CDC tells Five-0 that their servers were breached and confidential emails were stolen. That’s how the terrorists discovered how and when Lange would be transported. Dr. Dyer explains that the virus is very contagious and spread through direct human contact. Once contracted, the virus kills patients within five days. If Lange doesn’t receive his treatment by the next day, he’ll die.</p> <p>The best way for terrorists to weaponize Lange’s blood would require a specialized lab, and since there isn’t one nearby, they would have to build their own. But Chin says this is good: Now they can track the purchases of specialized equipment to locate the lab.</p> <p>And track them they do! A professor from the University of Oahu, Dr. Howard Rennick, just purchased thousands of dollars of medical equipment—and he hasn’t shown up for work in a few days. Lou, Steve, and Joe go to the doctor’s house, and we immediately jump into a shootout. Joe sneaks in through the back and clears the house. Rennick isn’t there, but his wife is. The guys find her tied up in the closet. She tells them six armed gunmen stormed their house three days ago and took her husband.</p> <p>Background checks show that all the dead shooters are mercenaries, <em>and</em> they all used to be CIA assets for a man named Michael Carson. Joe knows him—he’s dirty and spent time in prison. Before that, he was in charge of a bioware committee. Convenient.</p> <p>Kono and Danny interview Rennick’s colleague to get a better idea of how the virus could be weaponized. She explains that the easiest way would be to turn the virus into a powder; they would just need a delivery system. But she warns them that this strain of bird flu would decimate the world’s population. Finding out the distribution system is the only way to stop the virus from spreading.</p> <p>Meanwhile, our bad guy Carson is taking the virus out for a test drive. He’s “interviewing” a man, but instead locks him in a room with bees pouring out of the vents. He’s stung all over and immediately starts gasping for air. Looks like we just found our delivery system.</p> <p><img style="float:right;margin:0 0 10px 10px;" title="Hawaii Five-0" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/513-3.jpg" alt="Hawaii Five-0" />Luckily, the team isn’t far behind. They figure out about the bees, too, because of science and stuff. And since bee sales are monitored on the island, Five-0 is able to quickly find out where the bees are—and therefore where our bad guys are, too. They arrive at the makeshift lab armed with guns and gas masks. There’s another shootout (a particularly long one). All of the mercenaries are killed except for Carson and another man, who get away with the truck full of infected bees.</p> <p>Joe goes after them, and he and Carson fight in the back of the moving truck before Joe finally takes out the driver. Unfortunately, a box of bees got loose in the van in the process. Joe has to neutralize the threat, so he drives the truck directly into the ocean.</p> <p>Don’t worry! He’s fine! (He’s a SEAL, duh.) Joe pops out of the water a split second before Steve jumps in to rescue him. Lange is rescued and given a cure, and Joe is ordered into quarantine for three weeks for his troubles.</p> <p>When Steve stops by to visit Joe, he learns that Doris missed her last check-in with her handlers. Steve says <em>someone</em> (*cough* Joe! *cough*) probably tipped her off so she could go into hiding. Joe is upset that Steve still doesn’t seem to trust him, and he promises that once his quarantine is over, they are going to find Doris—together.</p> <p>Does Steve trust him? Steve begrudgingly says yes, but when he goes outside to meet Danny, his partner has tapped into the camera in Joe’s room. Turns out Steve lied.</p> <p><strong><em><strong><a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/hawaii_five_0/"><strong>Hawaii Five-0</strong></a></strong></em> airs Fridays at 9/8C on CBS.</strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div>]]></description><author>Samantha Swank</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:6f3092ed9f030d233b745f09d359f21f" t="1422682828" feed="200847" position="2"><title>'Blue Bloods' fan recap: Love and redemption</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/31/blue-bloods-fan-recap-love-stories/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/bb_514lovestories_sg17b.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Season 5 | Episode 13 | “Love Stories” | Aired Jan 30, 2015 <br /> </strong></p> <p>First dates, love, murder, and redemption are all a part of tonight’s <em>Blue Bloods</em> episode. When a homeowner shoots an intruder, it begins to seem like there may be more to the story than a simple break-in. Danny’s son goes on his first date, and Erin works to ensure a woman was not falsely imprisoned 12 years ago. <span id="more-33847"></span></p> <p>After armed man enters Nick Biaco’s home late at night, and Bianco shoots and kills him. When it’s discovered that the intruder, Bruce Epstein, was a hit man, the hunt is on to find out who hired him and why.</p> <p>Bianco is convinced it’s a rival concrete guy, but it doesn’t make sense. Further digging reveals that Bianco had an affair—but only after his wife cheated on him. Organized Crime has been looking into the Biancos and their concrete business, but they don’t have anything solid.</p> <p>But they are able to direct Danny and Baez to Epstein’s girlfriend, who tells them that he was hired by Bianco to kill his wife. Per usual, Danny breaks Bianco, who doesn’t think to ask for a lawyer until after he’s confessed to his crime (because of course we couldn’t end the show without knowing why).</p> <p>Bianco hired him in anger and then changed his mind, so he decided to shoot him and treat it like a home invasion. He forgot one thing: Don’t cross Danny Reagan. You won’t get away with anything.</p> <p>Erin is working on a case where a convicted felon’s son is trying to have his mother’s case retried. Twelve years ago she was put away for her role in a convenience-store murder and robbery. Erin has her investigator, McBride, help her with the case. (Who feels like that would make a good love story for Erin? She’s always so unlucky in love; it would be nice to see her a little happy.)</p> <p>The main witness was a crack addict who testified for a number of different cases, so her testimony is looking shaky. Erin has a cigarette butt from the crime scene sent to the lab, and the DNA matches that of the convicted woman, Suzanne Taylor.</p> <p>Erin persuades her to tell the truth to her son, who has always believed his mother is innocent. This is a sad one to see; the boy went to law school to get his mother out of prison only to find out she is guilty. Erin praises his legal skills and offers her card in case he ever wants to switch sides.</p> <p>Sgt. Gormley made a big uh-oh when he put Danny up for a Medal of Valor. Nothing makes Frank Reagan more angry than when people might think he’s showing favoritism to his family—well, that and public relations. I’m torn between the two sides, because I don’t think Danny should be punished when he’s doing a great job.</p> <p>Pops tells Frank that he regrets never giving him a medal, but Frank says he doesn’t have regrets. In the end, he decides to award the Medal of Valor to both Danny and Baez. It’s nice to see that Baez won’t lose her chance at a medal just because she’s partnered with a Reagan.</p> <p>Evidently, the Reagan grandchildren are growing up: Jack has his first crush on a girl, Charlotte. He’s nervous to ask her out, but even more nervous when she says yes. He forgoes the typical boring movie date and instead takes Charlotte ice skating. Danny and Linda reminisce on their second date at the ice-skating rink—and make us all go aw as Danny gives Linda chocolates made especially for her.</p> <p>The ties of family continue to hold strong with the Reagans as everyone attends Danny’s medal ceremony then gather for a pizza dinner. Pops then presents an honorary medal to Frank for his service and is able to right his one regret.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/blue_bloods" target="_blank">Blue Bloods</a></strong><strong><em> airs Fridays at 10/9C on CBS.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div>]]></description><author>Emily Glover</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:405402ce9d5f8ae65f988bdafaae1726" t="1422679296" feed="200847" position="3"><title>'Hart of Dixie' fan recap: The case of the talent show scandal</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/hart-of-dixie-talent-show/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/wade-2.png?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ha404a_0648b.jpg?w=533&amp;h=800" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ha404a_0911b.jpg?w=300&amp;h=200" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Season 4 | Episode 4 | “Red Dye #40″ | Aired Jan 30, 2015</strong></p> <p>I know what you’re thinking, and the answer is YES! This recap features a full shot of Wade Kinsella wearing nothing but a checkered table cloth around his waist. <em>Hart of Dixie</em> fans rejoice! Zade fans rejoice! Wilson Bethel fans—say hello to your new screensaver!</p> <p>Let’s dive straight in to the good part: Why was Wade shirtless for the majority of the episode? Clearly, The CW has been reading my strongly worded letters. You can thank me later. Of course, the storyline perpetuated this wise costume choice too. When you’ve been dating your baby’s mama secretly for six weeks, and she comes in to the Rammer Jammer in nothing but a trench coat and a coy smile, shirts have a tendency to come off. And as luck would have it, they stay off when the entire town traipses into your place of business to get to the bottom of one huge mystery: Who poisoned Shelby? <span id="more-33841"></span></p> <p>An actual crime has been committed in Bluebell during the town talent show. Shelby is rushed to the hospital after eating chocolate containing red dye #40. Going into anaphylactic shock looks mighty suspicious when a $25,000 prize is on the line. Sergeant Bill is on the case, and he has a list of suspects.</p> <p><strong>The Witness: Rose</strong><br /> Rose is hired to manage light and sound. She needs a quiet place to study for the SAT, so she chooses the rafters of Shelby’s dressing room as any high school student would do. She sees everything.</p> <p><strong>Suspect #1: Wanda</strong><br /> <strong>Motive:</strong> Wants to build a barn so her pet goat won’t eat her unborn child <br /> <strong>Alibi:</strong> The goat ate Shelby’s costume. Wanda ducks into Shelby’s dressing room to fix it before anyone thinks she is sabotaging the contestant to beat. <br /> <strong>Verdict:</strong> NOT GUILTY</p> <p><strong>INTERMISSION</strong><br /> Zoe doesn’t want anyone to know they are dating. This will be a tough explanation since she and Wade are draped in tablecloths. Wade’s has six distinct abs. I counted them while he was complaining about the townsfolk eating his food and drinking his booze.</p> <p><strong>Suspect #2: Stanley</strong><br /> <strong>Motive:</strong> Good old fashioned “This is my town and I’m the star” delusional attitude <br /> <strong>Alibi:</strong> Stanley was missing for two hours, and even though that’s enough time to find some red dye #40 (and bedazzle one’s jazz shoes) he has a witness. He was making out with Sadie in Shelby’s dressing room! <br /> <strong>Verdict:</strong> NOT GUILTY and ready to officially divorce Cricket</p> <p><strong>INTERMISSION</strong><br /> Flashback to Zoe inviting Wade to have a date in the town gazebo. Wade goes in for the “your my girlfriend and I don’t care who knows” kiss when Rose walks up. Zoe steals her Cheese Flavies chips, while mumbling something about checking Wade for pink eye.</p> <p><strong>Suspect #3: Rudy Truitt</strong><br /> <strong>Motive:</strong> Needs money to pay the damages for mud doggin’ in the judge’s truck <br /> <strong>Alibi:</strong> Even though “Making Moonshine with Me and My Brothers” is both a song and a business plan, the Truitt brothers aren’t smart enough to even know what red dye #40 is, let alone know how to inject it into a piece of chocolate. Besides, Rudy went into Shelby’s dressing room because he has to store the dry ice (big finish) in her fridge. <br /> <strong>Verdict:</strong> NOT GUILTY</p> <p><strong>INTERMISSION</strong><br /> Zoe contemplates peeing in a mop bucket instead of facing the town in the dining room. That’s gross. Do you need something to replace that mental image?</p> <p><a href="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ha404a_0648b.jpg"></a></p> <p>Well, I certainly feel better.</p> <p><strong>Suspect #4: Annabeth</strong><br /> <strong>Motive:</strong> To help win singing a duet with Lemon so she can buy back Fancie’s <br /> <strong>Alibi:</strong> She doesn’t have one! She gave Shelby the box of chocolates. She put a note on the box (eaten by the goat) that they were from Lemon. She wants the two to be friends. <br /> <strong>Defense:</strong> She did check the box and they did NOT have red dye #40 in the ingredients.</p> <p><strong>INTERMISSION</strong><br /> Brick has the chocolates tested. They were clean. AB is not the culprit. Then who did it?</p> <p><strong><a href="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ha404a_0911b.jpg"><img class="alignright size-medium wp-image-33842" src="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ha404a_0911b.jpg?w=300&amp;h=200" alt="Hart of Dixie" width="300" height="200" /></a>Surprise Suspect #5: Lemon</strong><br /> <strong>Motive:</strong> If Shelby wins, she’s going to buy Fancie’s and hire Lemon to run the joint <br /> <strong>Alibi:</strong> Lemon wants to keep her alibi a secret. Lavon rigged the entire talent show as a way for her to get the money to buy Fancie’s back. She also doesn’t want AB to know that Lavon confessed that he loves her and wants her to be happy. <br /> <strong>Verdict:</strong> NOT SO FAST</p> <p>Back in the storage closet, Zoe is in mid-meltdown, admitting to Wade that she is not prepared to answer questions about the baby, or a wedding, or where they will live, or how a doctor doesn’t use birth control. Wade does his best to calm her down, assuring her that they are in this together, as she scarfs down Cheese Flavies. Suddenly, Zoe hops up and runs to the dining room.</p> <p><strong>Zoe:</strong> I know who did it! It was Rose. Cheese Flavies have red dye #40. The powder was all over Rose’s hands, which were all over Shelby’s mic. Yes, I’m naked under here. In other news, Wade and I are back together. Also, I’m pregnant and really have to pee.”</p> <p>CASE CLOSED!</p> <p>Shelby wins the talent show and donates the money to Lemon to open Fancie’s all on her own. The Brothers Truitt Band are hired to play at the Rammer Jammer, and George agrees to be their manager. Tom lets Wanda keep the goat, as long as they name the baby Frodo. And Wade helps Zoe deflect all sorts of crazy questions from the citizens of Bluebell.</p> <p>Now, if only we can solve the case of why everyone on the <em>Hart of Dixie</em> set doubled dipped into the self tanner this week… <br /> <strong><br /> Quotable Quips</strong></p> <p>It’s not Truitt Brothers and George Tucker. It will confuse everyone and won’t fit on t-shirts.— <strong>Rudy</strong>, annoyed that George harmonized with the band</p> <p><strong>Lemon:</strong> Diana Ross is spinning in her grave. <br /> <strong>AB:</strong> Or hailing a taxi, because she’s still alive.</p> <p><strong>Zoe:</strong> People all over the world pee in buckets. <br /> <strong>Wade:</strong> I will still love you if I see this, but it may take me a while to recover.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://www.cwtv.com/shows/hart-of-dixie/cw-2014-fall-sizzle/?play=7fdd8c4b-2adf-46dd-b1ff-bc04a63216f1">Hart of Dixie</a> <em>airs</em> <em>Fridays</em> <em>at 8/7C on The CW.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div>]]></description><author>Lincee Ray</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2e5d49b7d0074b2f2f6e17745e6618a5" t="1422663301" feed="200847" position="4"><title>Fandom Friday: The 5 worst superheroes on TV</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/worst-superheroes-tv/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/heroes.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/ff562f_691df5a070d206060da0a8c7bc546c42.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/20110613_599_24_heroes.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/birds-of-prey-4fd28934b1fdd.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/1908039-mqvefmrzikfv7hc_8n63uc1ipmvb1vlp9msrfhs3xaetcat-fsvlg6onlfyzmtzjsxwrtfvr7eqhr2ovvq3ulg.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/hulk-hartter.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;">Whether you like it or not, we’re living in the Age of the Superhero. It all started with the first <em>Iron Man</em> flick in 2008. Hollywood discovered a vast wealth of story material in the realm of comic-book superheroes. Pair up superhero lore with smart scripts, the right casting, and inventive CGI, and you’ve pretty much built your studio its own money machine. A pining for escapism in a rapidly deteriorating world and humanity’s general appreciation for the good vs. evil trope has ensured that the Age of the Superhero won’t be over anytime soon.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">That success has trickled down into television. CGI technology and a willingness to take portraying costumed heroes seriously has enabled previously low-profile characters like The Flash and Green Arrow to take center stage in the watchers’ imaginations. <span id="more-33836"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;">However, putting superheroes on TV is not exactly new. Our tights-wearing saviors have graced the small screen quite a few times in the past. Unfortunately, this was not always handled as successfully as it has been recently. The following are five television superhero series that had you rooting for the bad guy.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <p style="text-align:left;">1) <em>Wonder Woman</em> (1974)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">A 1970s stalwart, Cathy Lee Crosby portrayed Amazonian princess Diana in an early-’70s TV movie that was supposed to have been the pilot for a series. You can actually watch some of it on YouTube, if the paint you were watching has finally dried. The show is somewhat faithful to WW’s general backstory: She’s still from a fabled island of tough gals, and Steve Trevor is still in the mix as her love interest. However, the costume is a little wonky. They eschew the tiara, corset, and star-spangled swimsuit bottom for something that looks like what the U.S. team could have worn to the opening ceremonies of the 1968 Winter Olympics. Crosby gives it her all, but it’s all a bit … boring. Plus, the main villain was named Abner. No. Luckily, Lynda Carter came along.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="Heroes" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/20110613_599_24_heroes.jpg" alt="Heroes cast" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;">2) <em>Heroes</em> (2006)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Before you tear my head off, give me a second. The first season of <em>Heroes</em>, as I’m sure we can all agree, was pretty damn good. Season 1 functioned as the origin story of a bunch of disparate superpowered types, and it worked. We even got a great villain (Zachary Quinto’s Sylar), and the season 1 finale’s ending battle gave us the superpowered showdown for which we had all been jonesing.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The following seasons? Good night, nurse. There was very little actual heroism, way too many characters running around, and insipid (yes, even for a superhero story) plotlines. <em>Heroes</em> had a solid foundation, but the building itself was made of Popsicle sticks. Didn’t it end with a circus or some nonsense? It ended up not being a very good portrayal of superheroes. By the way, <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/07/14/heroes-reboot" target="_blank"><em>Heroes</em> is coming back for another go-around as a miniseries</a>. Yay?</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="Birds of Prey" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/birds-of-prey-4fd28934b1fdd.jpg" alt="Birds of Prey Huntress" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;">3) <em>Birds of Prey</em> (2002)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Their heart was in the right place. In the D.C. Comics universe, the Birds are a small group of female supes led by the wheelchair-bound techspert Oracle (Dina Meyer). Oracle was Barbara Gordon, the former Batgirl who was been crippled after being shot by the Joker. Black Canary (Rachel Skarsten) and the Huntress (Ashley Scott) were her soldier minions in fighting evil. Sounds okay, so far; all three of those butt-kicking ladies were present. But then things went off the boil. Black Canary was suddenly a timid psychic teen. The Huntress looked nothing like the comic version and had cat abilities. Is that really Ferris Bueller’s girlfriend as Harley Quinn? Oh dear.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="Spidey" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/1908039-mqvefmrzikfv7hc_8n63uc1ipmvb1vlp9msrfhs3xaetcat-fsvlg6onlfyzmtzjsxwrtfvr7eqhr2ovvq3ulg.jpg" alt="Spidey Nicholas Hammond" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;">4) <em>The Amazing Spider-Man</em> (1977)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">You could chalk up Spidey’s first appearance on TV (barring short sketches on The Electric Company) being tranquilizing due to the complete absence of any special effects and miscasting. Remember when Spider-Man went to Hong Kong? Yeah, he did. You would think Spider-Man traveling to Hong King to fight bad guys would be visually arresting and action-packed. Nope. It was A LOT of our hero climbing walls really slowly, and wondering what the fake-looking webs were made of that were somehow entangling villains.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Plus, there was nary any of the acrobatics for which the webslinger is known. Actor Nicholas Hammond absolutely looked the part of Peter Parker, but he was so earnest. And bland. Peter Parker is quippy and down on his luck. Sometimes being handsome can inhibit the hero.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="Hulk " src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/hulk-hartter.jpg" alt="Hulk Thor Daredevil" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;">5) Thor and Daredevil of <em>The Incredible Hulk</em> TV movies (1988–1989)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The costumes alone! Prior to Marvel’s emergence as a motion-picture money farm, the company dabbled in TV. One of its more successful properties was <em>The Incredible Hulk</em> television series. The main reason for this success was the nuanced, sensitive portrayal by Bill Bixby of the mild-mannered geneticist who turns into a rage monster against his will. You cared about the dude, and hoped he could find a cure.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Fast-forward to the late ’80s, when Marvel was basically bankrupt and needed some cash. Hence the decision to revive the previously grounded in reality <em>Hulk</em> series and add more superheroes. Like I said, the original series was basically about a dude dealing with a medical condition. It went awry when the two TV movies introduced a Norse god with a magical hammer, and a blind lawyer with radar vision and ninja training. Things quickly become cheesy. You might note that those versions of Thor and Daredevil didn’t receive the TV series for which Marvel had hoped. That was for a good reason.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Agree? Disagree? Let us know YOUR picks for worst television superheroes!</p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>J. Harvey</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2b41d93645ad9cb4f04d1407f3c07297" t="1422660688" feed="200847" position="5"><title>Watch the guys from 'The League' play Charades</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/watch-guys-league-play-charades</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/the-league-charades_612x380.jpg?itok=TDP7FIwf" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>FX’s <em> The League </em>is all about fantasy football, friendship, and a crisp Three Penis Wine. </p> <p>So when Jonathan Lajoie, Stephen Rannazzisi, and Paul Scheer played a game of Charades in our studio, there were plenty of dick jokes to go around. They really put their bodies to work in this football edition of the game, with only one clear winner.  </p> <p> </p><div id="sc-v-4021416254001-ran73" class="bc-video-player"> </div>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:67e3b600f3fcb1542bf40d8d150f3245" t="1422658941" feed="200847" position="6"><title>Watch Kristen Wiig play talk-show host in 'Welcome to Me' trailer</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/watch-kristen-wiig-lottery-winning-talk-show-host-welcome-me-trailer</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/welcome-to-me_612x380_0.jpg?itok=NUb2d5zT" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>The trailer for <em><a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2788716/?ref_=fn_al_tt_1">Welcome to Me</a> </em>is here, showing star Kristen Wiig as a young lottery winner with Borderline Personality Disorder who takes her winnings and buys her own talk show.</p> <p>Inspired by Oprah, Wiig’s character Alice Klieg, creates and stars in her own talk show that is a little more off-beat than your average episode of <em>The Oprah Winfrey Show.</em> The show somehow takes off, and audiences get a front row seat to Klieg’s transformation.  </p> <p>Wiig stars alongside James Marsden, Linda Cardellini, Tim Robbins, Wes Bentley, and Joan Cusack.  <em>Welcome to Me </em>is scheduled to be released this year. </p> <p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="281" mozallowfullscreen="" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/116049504" webkitallowfullscreen="" width="500"></iframe></p>]]></description><author>Megan Daley</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:8f0ac094ce0b8b29e12eb794b959037c" t="1422658937" feed="200847" position="7"><title>HBO greenlights 'Lewis and Clark' miniseries starring Casey Affleck</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/hbo-greenlights-lewis-and-clark-miniseries</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/10/07/Casey-Affleck_612x380.jpg?itok=vuQ_WXBd" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">The adventures of Lewis and Clark will continue on…at HBO.</span></p> <p>The network greenlit <em>Lewis and Clark</em>, a six-hour miniseries starring Casey Affleck as Meriwether Lewis and Matthias Schoenaerts as William Clark. Michael Lombardo, president, HBO Programming, announced the news today.</p> <p>John Curran is directing the miniseries, which he is also writing alongside Michelle Ashford and Edward Norton. The story, which is based on Stephen E. Ambrose’s <em>Undaunted Courage, </em>will follow the Corps of Discovery and its captains, Lewis and Clark, as they trek through new terrain to deliver President Jefferson’s message of sovereignty and search for an all-water route to the Pacific. </p> <p>“In <em>Lewis and Clark</em>, we can see American idealism and the breathtaking natural beauty of the continent, as well as the complexities and tragedies of what came to be known as America’s ‘manifest destiny’,” Lombardo said. “We are tremendously excited to bring together this incredible group of talents to tell a seminal American story.”</p> <p>Tom Hanks, Gary Goetzman, Norton, Brad Pitt, Dede Gardner, Tim Kelly, and Adam Leipzig are executive producing.</p> <p>Production is set to begin this summer. </p>]]></description><author>C. Molly Smith</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:6cca6dbc4ce04ff62c73e8cf65434f4f" t="1422658635" feed="200847" position="8"><title>'X-Files' Fridays: This fits a profile?</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/x-files-pilot/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/rsz_x_files_pilot_rain.png?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/x-files-pilot-scully-mulder-rain.gif" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/x-files-pilot-hug.gif" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/x-files-pilot-meeting.gif" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong><strong>Season 1</strong> <strong>| Episode 1</strong> <strong>| “Pilot</strong><strong>” | Aired Sep 10</strong><strong>, 1993</strong></strong></p> <div style="text-align:left;"> It’s been over two decades since <em>The X-Files</em> made its debut, but the series is as relevant as ever, and with talk of a revival in the air, there’s no better time to revisit it—or to discover it for the first time.​ Community assistant editors <a href="http://www.ew.com/author/andrea-towers" target="_blank">Andrea Towers</a>, who watched in its original run, and Kelly Connolly, who was introduced to the show last summer, will be here each week to talk it out. Whether you’ve had an “I Want to Believe” poster on your wall for 20 years or are just now meeting Mulder and Scully, there’s a lot to discuss.</div> <div style="text-align:left;"></div> <p style="text-align:left;"><span id="more-33821"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY: </strong>Let’s do this. The truth is out there. How long has it been since you’ve seen the pilot?</p> <div style="text-align:left;"> <p><strong>ANDREA: </strong>Oh god…at least 7, maybe 8 years? I think the last time I really watched was back in 2008, when I bought the compilation DVD set that was made for the release of  <i>I Want To Believe.</i> My best friend had never seen the show (still hasn’t, we’re working on that) but understood how important it was for me to see the movie, so she wanted to understand enough of it going in. I think I’ve seen bits and pieces since then, but definitely not the whole thing in full. I can still remember every beautiful word, though. Especially that scene in the rain.</p> </div> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> Mulder and Scully in the cemetery, in the rain, at 5:07 in the morning, has to got to be one of my favorite scenes of this whole series. It’s easy to think that Scully is giving her whole career over to Mulder’s quest, but the way she laughs when she goes along with his theory says that she’s getting something out of this too. She’s having fun. As much as she’s all for science, Scully also likes pushing the rules to their limits, and with Mulder she can do that every day. Plus Gillian Anderson is so tiny and precious. Her sleeves are too long for her arms.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>ANDREA:</strong> I LOVE their relationship and how from the very first episode, we understand it and we get it. I know a lot of that is probably due to David and Gillian, but it’s really hard for me to think about another show, ’90s or not, that set up a relationship so well. Scully is skeptical but she’s not so skeptical that she doesn’t have a heart; Mulder is a brash believer but he’s not such a believer that he can’t take her seriously. But you’re right, it sets up so much of who they are as people and what their partnership will be with each other down the line. Like that hotel room scene? Who else gives two random partners an intimate hotel room scene in their first episode?!</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> THE CANDLES. THE ROBE. The look on his face when she hugs him. It’s the most intimate scene. The friends who introduced me to this show made it very clear that they’d never yelled “MAKE OUT” at their TV screens more than than they did at The X-Files, and as soon as I saw Mulder kneel down to study Scully’s lower back, I got it. Their chemistry drives this show from day one. And it’s her lower back; she really could have thrown on some sweatpants and just pulled up the back of her shirt if she wanted to, but she didn’t care. Scully doesn’t apologize.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="FOX/ iheartthexfiles.com" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/x-files-pilot-hug.gif" alt="FOX/ iheartthexfiles.com" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>ANDREA:</strong> Sometimes I wish I wasn’t so young when I first started watching because I really can only comprehend the amazingness of this scene and basically all the early stuff if I look back in retrospect, having been involved in fandoms and other TV shows long enough to recognize what feelings are. THAT SCENE THOUGH. The fact that she bares herself like that is basically the most vulnerable she can allow herself to be. She’s literally giving him a view into the most private part of her life, and in return, he tells her about Samantha. And I know Mulder isn’t exactly shy about letting people know why he follows his crusade, but he tells her and he tells her honestly. It’s a great exchange of emotions.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> It really is. He’s not just telling her what happened to his sister; he’s telling her what it did to his family and how it eventually led him where he is now. He instinctively wants to open up to her, even when he worries that she’s here to spy on him. As soon as she tells him that she’s not, that he can trust her, he does. And that’s when he gets real about what he thinks happened that night. That’s so huge for him to believe her, because Mulder doesn’t trust a lot of people. He’s trained as a profiler. He analyzes everyone, but he takes Scully at face value the minute she asks him to.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>ANDREA:</strong> You know what I love about this? That <em>The X-Files</em> is a TV show about ALIENS and it’s sci-fi and we’re sitting here talking about their relationship. Which is basically what this whole show was. I think that’s why I became so defensive in the future when Chris Carter would make statements like “the most important thing to me is storytelling,” because the most important thing for me was always Mulder and Scully. They drove the show. It was a show about two human beings and their connection, not just about aliens. (Although I do love aliens. I had a green plastic alien on my keychain in high school. And a Scully bob with dyed red hair.)</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> Did you have a Scully bob, or did the keychain alien? I can’t decide what I want your answer to be.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>ANDREA:</strong> I had a Scully bob AND an alien keychain. But the alien keychain did not have a Scully bob. I feel like Mulder could’ve investigated that.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> That would be an adventure for everyone. And I bought an “I still believe” shirt today, like a responsible adult, so I know what you mean. The aliens and the conspiracies are a huge part of this show’s legacyit wouldn’t be The X-Files without the mythologybut the mythology matters to me mostly for the ways it affects Mulder and Scully. I don’t think I’ve ever been able to focus on the plot when I watch the pilot. I’ve tried, but I keep coming back to how well it sets up their characters.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The FBI has absolutely no idea what they’re starting when they assign Scully to work with Mulder. They just want to shut down the X-Files and get back to their conspiracies (love how the real villains on this show are old guys in suits), but they don’t count on Scully having the integrity that she has, and they don’t count on her rapport with Mulder being so strong right off the bat. They’re setting up the only team that can ever take them down, and it’s because they don’t understand how people work. Scully and Mulder are such a good team precisely because they’re so human. You really can’t love the story behind this show without loving them.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong style="background-color:initial;">ANDREA:</strong> You hit the nail on the head—”you really can’t love the story behind this show without loving them.” That”s why I love that first meeting so much. She just goes down to Mulder’s basement and she’s got no idea who this guy really is, aside from what she’s heard, and isn’t even fazed when he snarks at her. True. Love.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="FOX/ headoverfeels.com" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/x-files-pilot-meeting.gif" alt="FOX/ headoverfeels.com" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>KELLY:</strong> Right! He thinks he’s ready for her. He read her senior thesis. (“I liked it!”) Mulder knows the FBI will want her to debunk his work, and he figures from everything on paper that this little scientist is never going to take him seriously. I think he’s made up his mind to intimidate her, but Scully doesn’t budge. When they’re driving into town and she impresses him by noticing a discrepancy in the autopsy reports, Mulder tells her that she’s pretty good, and she throws back, “Better than you expected, or better than you hoped?” She just sees right through him. She knows he’s resisting her, she’s very aware that it’s because he sees her as a threat to his work, and she’s not afraid to address it—directly, and with a little sass, but with absolute understanding. She means it when she says she’s looking forward to working with him, and she wants him to know it. Scully is in this all the way from the start.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">And by the time you get to that scene in the cemetery, Mulder’s in it too, because he’s seen that she really does want to solve this case with him. I love that moment when he starts to walk away, because he figures that she thinks he’s crazy, and then he turns around and waits for her. They haven’t even wrapped up their first case (as if these two ever wrap up a single case), but already it’s not about whether she agrees with him. It’s just about the two of them refusing to dismiss each other. That’s why they work.</p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Kelly Connolly</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:8fd26c5049bd902ca45cf7dfe772ccf4" t="1422656231" feed="200847" position="9"><title>Your guide to the best Super Bowl XLIX counterprogramming</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/super-bowl-counterprogramming-best-guide</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/19/Kitten-bowl-2_612x380.jpg?itok=nXDpsh8G" t="image/jpeg" author="Marc Lemoine/Hallmark Channel">Marc Lemoine/Hallmark Channel</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Not watching the big game? We live in a TV-world filled with options so if you’re not into football, could care less about the Seahawks or the Patriots, or would rather not see Katy Perry “Roar” during the <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/10/lenny-kravitz-katy-perry-super-bowl">half-time show</a>, there will be something to catch come Sunday.</p> <p>We’ve broken down the best options for counter-programming including cute kittens, crime dramas, and reality show marathons to keep you occupied. Pass the chips and dip and settle in for a Super Bowl Sunday without the Super Bowl.</p> <p><strong>YouTube</strong>: YouTube is hosting an alternative half-time show which will stream from its <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/adblitz">AdBlitz</a> channel and feature more than 20 YouTube stars. According to Business Insider, there will be a <a href="http://www.businessinsider.com/youtube-super-bowl-halftime-show-2015-1">variety of entertainment</a> including sketches, musical numbers, fake Super Bowl ads, and even stunts.  </p> <p><strong>HGTV</strong>: A <em>Property Brothers </em>marathon airs from 12 p.m. to 8 p.m. followed by a look into beach life with <em>Beachfront Bargain Hunt</em>,  <em>Caribbean Life</em>, and <em> Island Life</em> episodes until 11 p.m.</p> <p><strong>Bravo:</strong> <em>The Real Housewives of Atlanta</em> continue to mix things up in a marathon beginning at 12 p.m.</p> <p><strong>E!</strong>: E! is marathoning the <em>Total Divas</em> from 3 p.m. to 7 p.m.</p> <p><strong>Animal Planet</strong>: The <a href="http://www.animalplanet.com/tv-shows/puppy-bowl/">Puppy Bowl XI</a>—it’s like the Super Bowl but with puppies. <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/02/04/puppy-bowl-10-ratings">Last year</a>, 13.5 million unique viewers tuned in to catch a glimpse of the special, airing at 3 p.m.</p> <p><strong>Hallmark</strong>: More of a cat person? Hallmark’s second annual <em>Kitten Bowl</em> airs at 12 p.m. and follows along the same premise, with adorable kittens wrestling and chasing after toys on a faux-football field. Too cute.</p> <p><strong>National Geographic Channel</strong>: But don’t count out the National Geographic Channel as they’re bringing back <a href="http://channel.nationalgeographic.com/wild/fish-bowl/videos/fish-bowl-ii-trailer/"><em>Fish Bowl II </em></a>from 6 p.m. to 10 p.m.</p> <p><strong>AMC</strong>: AMC is airing a full marathon of <em>The Walking Dead</em> seasons one and two ahead of the season-five premiere on Sunday, Feb. 8 at 9 p.m. The marathon begins at 10 a.m.</p> <p><strong>A&amp;E</strong>: A full day <em>Criminal Minds</em> and the BAU begins at 12 p.m. on A&amp;E. </p> <p><strong>BBC America</strong>: BBC America is airing episodes of <em>Star Trek: The Next Generation </em>until 3 a.m. The marathon starts at 9 a.m.</p> <p><strong>WGN</strong>: The first annual “We Know It’s The Day Of The Big Game But Please Watch Us Anyway <em>How I Met Your Mother </em>Barney Bowl Marathon Sponsored By Little Caesars Pizza’” airs on WGN America starting at 12 p.m.</p> <p><strong>USA</strong>: Watch Olivia Benson and co. catch criminals all day on <em>Law and Order: SVU</em> starting at 11 a.m.</p> <p><strong>MTV</strong>: It’s a Rob Dyrdek day over at MTV with the channel airing a <em>Rob Dyrdek’s Fantasy Factory</em> marathon beginning at 9 a.m. followed by episodes of  <em>Ridiculousness</em> until 4 a.m. </p> <p><strong>TBS</strong>: Romantic comedies air all morning beginning at 9:30 a.m. with <em>Valentine’s Day</em> followed by <em>Just Married </em>(12 p.m.), <em>She’s the Man </em>(2 p.m.), and <em>17 Again</em> (4 p.m.) then a marathon of the first three Shrek films is scheduled to begin at 6 p.m.</p> <p><strong>ABC Family</strong>: Another movie marathon over on ABC Family with  <em>Beauty Shop</em> (11:00 a.m.), <em>What to Expect When You’re Expecting</em> (1:30 p.m.), <em>The Blind Side</em> (4:00 p.m.), and <em>Back to the Future </em>(7:00 p.m.) and <em>Back to the Future II</em> (9:30 p.m.). </p> <p><strong>TCM</strong>: Turner Classic Movies kicks off their “ <a href="http://31days.tcm.com/">31 Days of Oscars</a>” showing films from 1927-1930 during their primetime hours with a special documentary entitled “And the Oscar Goes To…” airing at 8 p.m.</p>]]></description><author>Megan Daley</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e4127b9c5ed5ebbca9cacc7d8d6cd08e" t="1422656229" feed="200847" position="10"><title>New look, rules for So You Think You Can Dance</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/new-look-rules-so-you-think-you-can-dance</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422651790/Paula_Headshot_hires2.jpg?itok=2hdgzl97" t="image/jpeg" author="Nino Munoz/FOX">Nino Munoz/FOX</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Prepare to dance for joy when <em>So You Think You Can Dance</em> returns this summer, because the Fox reality series will feature new rules to go along with its new but familiar faces. In case you missed the news: Mary Murphy and her Hot Tamale Train are out, and longtime <em>American Idol</em> judge Paula Abdul and singer/dancer Jason Derulo are in. </p> <p>“Well, Paula Abdul, as soon as I created <em>So You Think You Can Dance</em> I thought, ‘This show is far better for you to judge than anything else!’ I mean, not only was she a great dancer, she was a wonderful choreographer and got so many stars to dance,” said executive producer Nigel Lythgoe at the series’ open call auditions in New York City Jan. 25.</p> <p>Jason Derulo, who has previously guest judged and performed, will bring his hip hop (and wiggle) expertise to the panel. “I made it a point to myself that I would try to find the positive in everybody and also give them the constructive criticism that they need to grow,” he told EW. </p> <p>But this show has never been afraid of change. In previous years, we’ve seen partner swaps, All-Star mentors, and the elimination of a separate results show. Now the dancers will be split up into new categories: street and stage. Each week, one dancer from each group will be eliminated until a winner is crowned.</p> <p>And for Vegas Week, this means no more ballroom dancers struggling through hip hop routines, or vice-versa. Producers have listened to the agonized groaning of viewers who watched their favorite dancer go home early because their free-flowing street style clashed with the demanding control of that one contemporary routine. </p> <p>Stage dancers will compete against each other in styles such as contemporary, jazz and Broadway, while street dancers will be put to the test in animation, popping and more. Once the season’s top 20 is set—10 stage dancers and 10 street dancers—it will be a free-for-all, as both will be tested in all forms of dance. As Lythgoe explained, “Once they hit that top 20, they are going to have to be prepared to do lots of other styles and lots of other things. So we’re gonna see a lot of people fail.” Hey, that’s showbiz for you.</p> <p>Auditions began Jan. 24 in New York and continue Feb. 14 in Dallas, TX; Feb. 22 in Detroit, MI; March 8 in Memphis, TN; and March 15 in Los Angeles, CA.</p> <p>But make sure you have that special something if you want to make it to the next round. As new judge Abdul said, “I want unique ability. I wanna be blown away, because even as a choreographer I’ve witnessed incredible technicians. And with this show, you’ve seen the level of talent is so high. So now I wanna see what’s next, that’s gonna [make me] go ‘Oh my God!’”</p>]]></description><author>Keisha Hatchett</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:6dd7db7ca7ad39fb7ad656150275556e" t="1422656229" feed="200847" position="11"><title>Sia announces Grammy performance on 'Ellen'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/sia-announces-grammy-performance-ellen</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/07/08/Sia-1000-Forms-of-Fear-Review_612x380.jpg?itok=_ZZQzJRt" t="image/jpeg" author="Pretty Puke">1000 FORMS OF FEAR Sia (Pretty Puke)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="324" src="//widgets.ellentube.com/videos/0-rgumk69t/" width="575"></iframe></p> <p>Sia announced Friday on  <em>Ellen </em>she will be taking the stage at this year’s Grammy Awards. The “Elastic Heart” singer is <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/12/05/taylor-swift-iggy-azalea-pharrell-nab-grammy-nominations">nominated for four awards</a> including Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p> <p>While visiting  <em>Ellen</em>, she performed her latest hit “Elastic Heart” with the help of a band of blond-wigged lip-syncers and <em>Dance Moms</em> star Maddie Ziegler, the star of the video for her Grammy-nominated song “Chandelier.”</p> <p>Sia joins a slew of <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/21/grammys-2015-common-john-legend">already-announced performers</a> including Madonna, AC/DC, Ed Sheeran, Lady Gaga and Tony Bennett and more. </p> <p>Watch the performance above as Sia makes her big announcement. The Grammy’s air on Feb. 8 at 8 p.m. ET on CBS. </p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet" lang="en"> <p>Guess who? :microphone::musical_note::notes: 2.8.15 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/GRAMMYs?src=hash">#GRAMMYs</a> <a href="http://t.co/1JqwlmeE1Q">pic.twitter.com/1JqwlmeE1Q</a></p> <p>— The GRAMMYs (@TheGRAMMYs) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheGRAMMYs/status/561237914613338113">January 30, 2015</a></p></blockquote> <p> </p>]]></description><author>Megan Daley</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2d957d6b512f8ae8dad1b2c43e50ed83" t="1422656225" feed="200847" position="12"><title>'Disney Infinity 2.0' Toy Box comes to iPhones, iPads</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/disney-infinity-20s-toy-box-mode-comes-iphones-ipads</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422641945/iphone5_4.jpg?itok=DoQMkHqP" t="image/jpeg" author="Disney Interactive">Disney Interactive</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Disney Interactive has released the  <em>Disney Infinity: Toy Box 2.0</em> for free on iPhones and iPads, meaning it’s now possible for you to have Aladdin and Baymax race each other in <em>Guardians of the Galaxy</em>-themed cars when you’re on the go. </p> <p><em>Disney Infinity 2.0: Marvel Super Heroes</em>’s Toy Box feature allows players to create their own game levels that span different game genres and Disney properties.  <em>Infinity 2.0</em> introduced Marvel heroes like Spider-Man, Iron Man, and the Hulk to the mix of Disney stalwarts like Buzz Lightyear, Donald Duck, and Maleficent.</p> <p>The Toy Box is almost like virtual fan fiction, allowing players to create platformers, tower defense games, races, and other types of games in worlds that integrate a blend of Disney history determined by the player.</p> <p> </p><div id="sc-v-4023019004001-ran2416" class="bc-video-player"> </div> <p>Players can transfer Toy Box levels they have created from other console versions of  <em>Infinity 2.0</em> to iOS devices for editing while away from home. The mobile version will also allow players to build and play their own levels with friends over a wi-fi connection.</p> <p>The iOS version of the Toy Box is <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/app/id895324943?mt=8">available to download now</a>, and will bring with it the enhancements made over the original Toy Box app released in conjunction with the first  <em>Disney Infinity</em>. For more on <em>Disney Infinity 2.0</em>, which launched last year on PlayStation 3, PlayStation 4, Xbox 360, Xbox One, Wii U and Windows PC, read  <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/09/18/disney-infinity-2-0-review-avengers-marvel"><em>EW</em>’s review of the game</a>.</p>]]></description><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e61fe3cf584fd1435e138474c97e6141" t="1422653508" feed="200847" position="13"><title>Peter Berg in talks to replace J.C. Chandor as 'Deepwater Horizon' director</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/jc-chandor-wont-direct-bp-oil-spill-film</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/jc-foreman_612x380.jpg?itok=Pp2nk6SU" t="image/jpeg" author="Richard Foreman">Richard Foreman</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>J.C. Chandor, of  <em>All Is Lost</em> and most recently  <em>A Most Violent Year</em>, will not direct  <em>Deepwater Horizon</em>, a film about the BP oil spill,  EW has confirmed. Deadline first <a href="http://deadline.com/2015/01/jc-chandor-deepwater-horizon-movie-leaving-1201363161/">reported</a> the news, citing “ <span class="s1">creative differences” for Chandor’s decision.  </span></p> <p>Mark Wahlberg is <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/08/19/casting-net-mark-wahlberg-deepwater-horizon">attached</a> to star in the project.  A <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">replacement for Chandor is already being lined up: Peter Berg, Wahlberg’s </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">Lone Survivor </em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">director, is in talks. </span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Chandor </span><a href="http://collider.com/deepwater-horizon-movie-details-jc-chandor/" style="line-height: 1.6em;">talked</a><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> about his plans for the film recently with Collider.</span></p> <p>The film has a September 30, 2016 release date. </p>]]></description><author>Esther Zuckerman</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d14af64c98a0f5710c0ba2fd6ab4bfbf" t="1422653506" feed="200847" position="14"><title>Bradley Cooper talks about 'American Sniper' experience at 'Got Your 6' event</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/bradley-cooper-speaks-about-american-sniper-experience-got-your-6-event</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422649480/GotYour6_NatGeo_4.jpg?itok=y8cnZ-hF" t="image/jpeg" author="National Geographic Channels">National Geographic Channels</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Bradley Cooper spoke about his experience filming <em>American Sniper</em> on Friday when he joined First Lady Michelle Obama and several entertainment industry leaders to announce Got Your 6’s “6 Certified” campaign, which highlights works of film and telvision that portray veterans in an accurate and responsible way.</p> <p>“Cinema was the way in for me. The content we create can actually have a big impact. American Sniper has had such an impact, and has reawakened my motivation to do everything I can for veterans,” Cooper said of the film, based on the autobiography by real-life Navy SEAL Chris Kyle. Kyle is credited with 160 confirmed kills and served for four terms. </p> <p>“6 Certified,” in association with National Geographic and Charlie Ebersol’s The Company hopes to help change the perceptions of veterans in pop culture, steering away from the “negative, stereotypical, and extreme” portrayals of veterans in entertainment by painting a more geniune narrative.</p> <p>In order for a film or television series to become “6 Certified,” they must fulfill one of the <a href="http://www.gotyour6.org/6-certified/">“6 Certified” pledges</a>, and also depict veterans in a balanced light. </p> <p>Cooper spoke with <a href="http://www.people.com/article/bradley-cooper-american-sniper-chris-kyle-life-changing"><em>People </em>about his role</a> and the aftermath with meeting veterans from all over the U.S., saying the experience had been “life-changing.”</p> <p>“At Walter Reed when we screened the movie, afterward a Marine stood up in front of the group and said “thank you for getting it right - you’re one of us,’” said Cooper at the event. <span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> </span></p>]]></description><author>Megan Daley</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d4d147947109e15bfe20643400eb912b" t="1422651789" feed="200847" position="15"><title>Snapchat's getting its own web series, and it's called 'Literally Can't Even'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/snapchat-announces-first-original-series-literally-cant-even</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/spielbergs_612x380.jpg?itok=BwHjrr1w" t="image/jpeg" author="2">2</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Sending self-destructing pictures and videos is nice and all, but Snapchat wants to do more. The popular social network is broadening its horizons and getting into the entertainment game—by making an original web series named after a <a href="http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/i-cant-even"> rather tired Internet meme.</a> </p> <p>The ephemeral messaging service announced on Friday that its first original web series will be called  <em>Literally Can’t Even </em>and star Sasha Spielberg (yes, she’s  <em>that</em> Spielberg’s daughter) and Emily Goldwyn (yes, she’s  <em>that</em> Goldwyn’s daughter). It’s a bit like some of early casting of  <em>Girls </em>in that regard—Spielberg and Goldwyn aren’t really known for anything outside of being the children of very successful people in the entertainment business. Regardless of its cast’s credentials, the new series does reflect the majority of Snapchat’s users— <a href="http://www.businessinsider.com/a-primer-on-snapchat-and-its-demographics-2014-7"> young and mostly female</a>. </p> <p>According to  <a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sasha-spielberg-emily-goldwyn-star-768501"><em>The Hollywood Reporter</em></a>, the series will launch new episodes every Saturday, and each episode will only be available for 24 hours after it’s posted. Each episode will be kept under five minutes and length, and will be “snapshots of our life,” Emily Goldwyn told  <em>THR</em>.</p>]]></description><author>Joshua Rivera</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e0e97842d8db084d8bd9467ec58c1e3e" t="1422651789" feed="200847" position="16"><title>Netflix to exclusively stream Aziz Ansari's next stand-up special</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/netflix-exclusively-stream-aziz-ansaris-next-stand-special</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2013/08/22/AZIZ-ANSARI_612x380.jpg?itok=SFiPT189" t="image/jpeg" author="Jennifer Graylock/Getty Images">Jennifer Graylock/Getty Images</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Aziz Ansari has no problem filling up a venue as big as Madison Square Garden, and now fans will see why in his next stand-up special.</p> <p>Netflix has announced that Ansari’s newest stand-up special,  <em>Aziz Ansari: Live at Madison Square Garden</em>, will be available to stream exclusively on Netflix beginning Friday, March 6, at 3:01 a.m. EST/12:01 a.m. PST.</p> <p>The special, filmed at New York’s Madison Square Garden before a sold-out audience, will include material covering some of Ansari’s staples, like food and relationships. </p> <p>This special will be the second one Netflix has acquired as an original production, following 2013’s <em>Buried Alive</em> special. That special, along with two others from Ansari— <em>Intimate Moments for a Sensual Evening</em> and  <em>Dangerously Delicious</em>—are all currently streaming on Netflix.</p> <p>Until then, Ansari can still be seen as restaurant owner/talent agent/Nacho Average podcast host Tom Haverford on the final season of  <em>Parks and Recreation</em>.</p> <p> </p>]]></description><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a5bd3f5e258a3a3181f3c88b80c88a77" t="1422650392" feed="200847" position="17"><title>Nominated for Nothing: Force Majeure</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/nominated-nothing-force-majeure</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/10/21/Force-Majeure_612x380.jpg?itok=jRX_taI5" t="image/jpeg" author="Everett Collection">FORCE MAJEURE Johannes Kuhnke, Lisa Loven Kongsli, Clara Wettergren, and Vincent Wettergren (Everett Collection)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><em>Just about every year, brilliant movies are utterly ignored by the Oscars. </em>The Searchers, Groundhog Day, Breathless, King Kong, Casino Royale, Touch of Evil, Caddyshack, Mean Streets, The Big Lebowski, Blackfish— <em>the Academy has a long history of overlooking comedies, action movies, horror flicks, hard-boiled genre pics, artsy foreign films, and documentaries that aren’t about World War II. Before the ceremony, we’ll be taking a closer look at films that were too small, too weird, or perhaps simply too awesome for the Academy Awards. These are the Non-Nominees.</em></p> <p><strong>The film: </strong><em>Force Majeure</em>, a tense thriller that’s also a dark comedy, until it becomes a tragic melodrama. Unless it’s all a straightfaced satire, or maybe an allegory for the internal corrosion of the nuclear family. First and foremost,  <em>Force Majeure</em> is a family movie: A handsome businessman and his attractive wife take their cute Swedish children on a ski trip to the French Alps. The beautiful family is having a beautiful time…until their lunch is interrupted by an approaching avalance. The wife hugs the children close to her; the husband runs away. No one is injured, but in the aftermath, the entire foundation of the marriage and the family starts to come undone because of the husband’s split-second decision. It’s equal parts horrifying and hilarious.</p> <p><strong style="line-height: 1.6em;">Why it wasn’t nominated:</strong> Some years, Best Foreign Language Film is the most exciting category at the Oscars. It’s the place to reward adventurous auteurs like Paolo Sorrentino, who won last year for  <em>The Great Beauty,</em> or Asghar Farhadi, who took the prize for 2011’s  <em>A Separation</em>, a Kafkaesque family drama with subject matter and an unusual tone of droll cosmic terror that vaguely recalls  <em>Force Majeure. </em>But Best Foreign Language Film can also trend conservative and sentimental. (Two words: Roberto Benigni.) Above all, when you look at the last decade or so of Foreign Film nominees, you can feel a general urge for importance—although self-importance works, too.</p> <p>So although  <em>Force Majeure</em> was one of the most critically acclaimed films of last year, it’s not difficult to see how it got edged out of the Foreign Film category. The five nominated films are up front about their Big Idea themes: Islamic extremism, Putin-esque political corruption, the Chechen/Georgian conflict. Category frontrunner  <em>Ida</em> sounds, on paper, like a parody of a foreign art film: A black-and-white movie about an orphaned nun who discovers her Jewish heritage before setting off with her alcoholic aunt to find out where her parents are buried.</p> <p><em>Ida</em> is fantastic, but it’s  <em>heavy</em>. And there’s a fundamental lightness to  <em>Force Majeure </em>that feels very anti-Academy. This is not a topical story of political realism or a historical investigation of a defining 20th century event; it’s the story of a family on a ski vacation, a film shot mostly in the corridors of a resort and on the snowy slopes of the Alps.  <em>Force Majeure</em>’s jaunty tone is part of the movie’s stealth-missile impact—it’s a family farce only like  <em>The Great Gatsby</em> is a romantic comedy—but it might have looked weightless next to its more explicit opponents.</p> <p><strong>Why history will remember it better than the Academy did: </strong>Because it’s timeless.  <em>Force Majeure</em>’s perspective on its characters is razor-sharp. It’s sort of like a Richard Linklater movie: The “story” is really just a steady unwrapping of the characters as their happy-family veneer gets stripped away. ( <em>Force Majeure</em> is like the dark mirror of  <em>Boyhood</em>.) But if the characters are specific, the setting is purposefully vague and universal. The characters are Swedish, they’re in France, people they meet speak English:  <em>Force Majeure</em> imagines a luxury resort as a kind of postmodern nowhere, where the usual trappings of society fade away into a Hobbesian state of nature. It’s the kind of place where a wife can finally see her husband clearly.</p> <p>As a result, there’s a fundamental approachability to  <em>Force Majeure</em> that sets it apart from most foreign films—heck, from most films, period. There’s a sequence toward the middle of the movie that practically holds a mirror up to the audience. Why  <em>did</em> the father run away from his children? Was it just an impulse, or something deeper? What would <em>you</em> have done? Again, there’s that Richard Linklater quality: Like the  <em>Before</em> movies,  <em>Force Majeure </em>feels like a film that offers different insights depending on where you are in life when you approach it, and which member of the family you empathize with.</p> <p>Writer-director Ruben Ostlund has been a rising star in his native Sweden, and the acclaim around  <em>Force Majeure</em> seemed to confirm his arrival on the international scene. He’ll have to wait a bit longer for his first trip to the Academy Awards. But at least he can lay claim to one of the high points of the 2015 awards season: A video reaction to his snub that plays a little bit like a meta-sequel to  <em>Force Majeure</em>, complete with a crying fit.</p> <p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hYTWqLmnjt0" width="560"></iframe></p>]]></description><author>Darren Franich</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:0edae981e3abefb7b98b5c9f199e38f8" t="1422650392" feed="200847" position="18"><title>Miranda Lambert, Dierks Bentley, and Florida Georgia Line among nominees for Academy of Country Musi ...</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/miranda-lambert-dierks-bentley-and-florida-georgia-line-among-nominees-academy</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2011/11/04/miranda-lambert-02.jpg?itok=W_dDdqQY" t="image/jpeg" author="Kevin Winter/Getty Images">Kevin Winter/Getty Images</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>The nominees for the 50th Academy of Country Music Awards were announced on Friday morning, and Miranda Lambert leads the pack with eight nominations, including Album of the Year, two nods for her single “Automatic,” and her ninth consecutive nomination for Female Vocalist of the Year. Dierks Bentley is up for seven awards, Florida Georgia Line is up for five, and Luke Bryan, Kenny Chesney, and Eric Church all received four. </p> <p>Fan voting for the Academy’s New Artist of the Year award is now live at  <span class="s1"><a href="http://dickclark.us1.list-manage.com/track/click?u=ce90be5adb2fbc34c3bd0ffc8&amp;id=88eacc4c94&amp;e=99964110db">VoteACM.com</a>, and the poll for Entertainer of the Year opens </span>Wednesday, April 8 at 3:00 p.m. EST.</p> <p>The awards show will be broadcast live on CBS  <span class="s1">Sunday, April 19, 2015 at 8:00 p.m. EST.</span></p> <p> </p> <p> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ENTERTAINER</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> OF THE YEAR</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Jason Aldean</li> <li class="li1">Garth Brooks</li> <li class="li1">Luke Bryan</li> <li class="li1">Miranda Lambert</li> <li class="li1">Florida Georgia Line</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>MALE</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> VOCALIST OF THE YEAR [TIE]</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Jason Aldean</li> <li class="li1">Dierks Bentley</li> <li class="li1">Luke Bryan</li> <li class="li1">Eric Church</li> <li class="li1">Brad Paisley</li> <li class="li1">Blake Shelton</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>FEMALE</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> VOCALIST OF THE YEAR</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Brandy Clark</li> <li class="li1">Miranda Lambert</li> <li class="li1">Martina McBride</li> <li class="li1">Kacey Musgraves</li> <li class="li1">Carrie Underwood</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>VOCAL</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> DUO OF THE YEAR</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Brothers Osborne</li> <li class="li1">Dan + Shay</li> <li class="li1">Florida Georgia Line</li> <li class="li1">Maddie &amp; Tae</li> <li class="li1">The Swon Brothers</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>VOCAL</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> GROUP OF THE YEAR</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Lady Antebellum</li> <li class="li1">Little Big Town</li> <li class="li1">Rascal Flatts</li> <li class="li1">The Band Perry</li> <li class="li1">Zac Brown Band</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ALBUM</b></span></p> <p class="p3"><span class="s2"><b> OF THE YEAR </b></span><span class="s1"><b>[Awarded to Artist(s)/Producer(s)/Record Company–Label(s)]</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b><i>Old Boots, New Dirt</i></b></li> <li class="li1">– Jason Aldean</li> </ul><p class="p4">Producer: Michael Knox</p> <p class="p4">Record Label: Broken Bow Records</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b><i>Pain Killer</i></b>–</li> <li class="li1">Little Big Town</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Jay Joyce</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Capitol Records Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b><i>Platinum</i></b></li> <li class="li1">– Miranda Lambert</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Chuck Ainlay, Frank Liddell, Glenn Worf</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: RCA Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b><i>Riser</i></b></li> <li class="li1">– Dierks Bentley</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Ross Copperman, Jaren Johnston</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Capitol Records Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b><i>The Outsiders</i></b>–</li> <li class="li1">Eric Church</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Jay Joyce</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: EMI Records Nashville</p> <p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>SINGLE</b></span></p> <p class="p3"><span class="s2"><b> RECORD OF THE YEAR </b></span><span class="s1"><b>[Awarded to Artist(s)/Producer(s)/Record Company–Label(s)]</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>American Kids</b></li> <li class="li1">– Kenny Chesney </li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Buddy Cannon, Kenny Chesney</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label:</p> <p class="p5"> Blue Chair Records/Columbia Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Automatic</b></li> <li class="li1">– Miranda Lambert</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Chuck Ainlay, Frank Liddell, Glenn Worf</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: RCA Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Dirt</b></li> <li class="li1">– Florida Georgia Line</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Joey Moi</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Republic Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Drunk On A Plane</b></li> <li class="li1">– Dierks Bentley</li> </ul><p class="p4">Producer: Ross Copperman</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Capitol Records Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>I Don’t Dance</b></li> <li class="li1">– Lee Brice</li> </ul><p class="p4">Producer: Lee Brice</p> <p class="p6">Record Label: Curb Records</p> <p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>SONG</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> OF THE YEAR [TIE]</b></span><span class="s3"><b>[Awarded</b></span></p> <p class="p3"><span class="s1"><b> to Songwriter(s)/Publisher(s)/Artist(s)] </b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>American Kids</b></li> <li class="li1">– Kenny Chesney</li> </ul><p class="p5">Songwriters:</p> <p class="p5"> Rodney Clawson, Luke Laird, Shane McAnally</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> Big Red Toe Music (BMI), Creative Nation Music (BMI), Farm Town Songs (BMI), Smack Ink (ASCAP), Songs Of Universal, Inc. (BMI), Twangin And Slangin Songs (BMI), Universal Music Corporation (ASCAP)</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Automatic</b></li> <li class="li1">– Miranda Lambert</li> </ul><p class="p5">Songwriters:</p> <p class="p5"> Nicolle Galyon, Natalie Hemby, Miranda Lambert</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> EMI Blackwood Music, Inc. (BMI), Pink Dog Publishing (BMI), Sony/ATV Tree Publishing (BMI), Warner-Tamerlane Publishing Corp. (BMI), Wruckestrike (BMI)</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Drink A Beer</b></li> <li class="li1">– Luke Bryan</li> </ul><p class="p4">Songwriters: Jim Beavers, Chris Stapleton</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> House of Sea Gayle Music (ASCAP), Sony/ATV Tree Publishing (BMI), WB Music Corp. (ASCAP)</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Follow Your Arrow</b></li> <li class="li1">– Kacey Musgraves</li> </ul><p class="p4">Songwriters: Brandy Clark, Shane McAnally, Kacey</p> <p class="p4"> Musgraves</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> 351 Music (BMI), Highway 508 Songs (ASCAP), House of Sea Gayle Music (ASCAP), Smack Ink (ASCAP), Universal Music Corporation (ASCAP), Warner-Tamerlane Publishing Corp. (BMI)</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Give Me Back My Hometown</b></li> <li class="li1">– Eric Church</li> </ul><p class="p4">Songwriters: Eric Church, Luke Laird</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> Creative Nation Music (BMI), Longer And Louder Music (BMI), Songs Of Universal, Inc. (BMI), Sony/ATV Tree Publishing (BMI), Twangin And Slangin Songs (BMI)</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>I Hold On</b></li> <li class="li1">– Dierks Bentley</li> </ul><p class="p4">Songwriters: Dierks Bentley, Brett James</p> <p class="p5">Publishers:</p> <p class="p5"> Atlas Holdings (ASCAP), Big White Tracks (ASCAP), External Combustion Music (ASCAP), Songs of Brett (ASCAP), WB Music Corp. (ASCAP)</p> <p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>SONGWRITER</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> OF THE YEAR </b></span><span class="s4"><b>*(Off</b></span></p> <p class="p7"><span class="s1"><b> Camera Award)</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Rodney Clawson</li> <li class="li8"> </li> <li class="li1">Ashley Gorley</li> <li class="li1">Luke Laird</li> <li class="li1">Josh Osborne</li> <li class="li8"> </li> <li class="li1">Chris Tompkins</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>VIDEO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> OF THE YEAR</b></span><span class="s3"><b>[Awarded</b></span></p> <p class="p3"><span class="s1"><b> to Producer(s)/Director(s)/Artist(s)] </b></span><span class="s4"><b>*(Off Camera Award)</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>American Kids</b></li> <li class="li1">– Kenny Chesney</li> </ul><p class="p5">Director:</p> <p class="p5"> Shaun Silva</p> <p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Don Lepore</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Cop Car</b></li> <li class="li1">– Keith Urban</li> </ul><p class="p4">Director: John Urbano</p> <p class="p6">Producer: Michelle Abnet</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Drunk On A Plane</b></li> <li class="li1">– Dierks Bentley</li> </ul><p class="p5">Director:</p> <p class="p5"> Wes Edwards</p> <p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Clarke Gallivan</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>I’m Not Gonna Miss You</b></li> <li class="li1">– Glen Campbell</li> </ul><p class="p5">Director:</p> <p class="p5"> James Keach</p> <p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Julian Raymond</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Somethin’ Bad</b></li> <li class="li1">– Miranda Lambert Duet With Carrie Underwood</li> </ul><p class="p5">Director:</p> <p class="p5"> Trey Fanjoy</p> <p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Trent Hardville <br /><span class="s5"> </span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>VOCAL</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> EVENT OF THE YEAR</b></span><span class="s3"><b>[Awarded</b></span></p> <p class="p3"><span class="s1"><b> to Artist(s)/Producer(s)/Record Company–Label(s)]</b></span><span class="s4"><b>*(Off Camera Award)</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Lonely Tonight</b></li> <li class="li1">– Blake Shelton Featuring Ashley Monroe</li> </ul><p class="p4">Producer: Scott Hendricks</p> <p class="p6">Record Label: Warner Bros. Records</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Meanwhile Back At Mama’s</b></li> <li class="li1">– Tim McGraw Featuring Faith Hill</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Byron Gallimore, Tim McGraw</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Big Machine Records</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>Somethin’ Bad</b></li> <li class="li1">– Miranda Lambert Duet With Carrie Underwood</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Chuck Ainlay, Frank Liddell, Glenn Worf</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: RCA Nashville</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>The South</b></li> <li class="li1">– The Cadillac Three Featuring Florida Georgia Line, Dierks Bentley &amp; Mike Eli</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producers:</p> <p class="p5"> Dann Huff, Justin Niebank</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Big Machine Records</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1"><b>This Is How We Roll</b></li> <li class="li1">– Florida Georgia Line Featuring Luke Bryan</li> </ul><p class="p5">Producer:</p> <p class="p5"> Joey Moi</p> <p class="p5">Record</p> <p class="p5"> Label: Republic Nashville</p> <p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>RADIO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> AWARDS</b></span><b> - The following radio awards will be presented during the annual Radio Winners Reception</b></p> <p class="p1"><b> held the day prior to the ACM Awards telecast, on Saturday, April 18</b><span class="s6"><b><sup>th</sup></b></span></p> <p class="p1"><b> in Arlington, TX.</b></p> <p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>NATIONAL</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> ON-AIR PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Big D, Bubba, Patrick Thomas  </li> <li class="li1">         The</li> <li class="li1">Big D and Bubba Show</li> <li class="li1">Cody Alan  </li> <li class="li1">           </li> <li class="li1">     CMT After MidNite</li> <li class="li1">Crook and Chase  </li> <li class="li1">           </li> <li class="li1"> The Crook and Chase Countdown</li> <li class="li1">Lia Knight</li> <li class="li1">          </li> <li class="li1">         The</li> <li class="li1">Lia Show</li> <li class="li1">Shawn Parr, Elaina Smith  </li> <li class="li1">         Nash</li> <li class="li1">Nights Live</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ON-AIR</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR – MAJOR MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Ben Campbell and Matt McAllister                           KNIX-FM                             </li> <li class="li1">Phoenix, AZ</li> <li class="li1">Dave and Veronica                                                       WQYK-FM                          </li> <li class="li1">Tampa, FL</li> <li class="li1">Lisa Dent &amp; Ramblin’ Ray                                            WUSN-FM                         </li> <li class="li1">Chicago, IL</li> <li class="li1">Razz on the Radio                                                         WXTU-FM                          </li> <li class="li1">Philadelphia, PA</li> <li class="li1">Rob Tanner, Guenn, Chris &amp; Captain Jim                 WSOC-FM                          </li> <li class="li1">Charlotte, NC</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ON-AIR</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR – LARGE MARKET </b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">AJ &amp; Ashley                                                                       </li> <li class="li1">WWKA-FM                         Orlando, FL</li> <li class="li1">Big Dave, Chelsie, Stattman                                            WUBE-FM                          Cincinnati,</li> <li class="li1">OH</li> <li class="li1">Dave O’Brien                                                                     </li> <li class="li1">WLHK-FM                          Indianapolis, IN</li> <li class="li1">Mike Wheless, Marty Young, Janie Carothers             WQDR-FM                         Raleigh,</li> <li class="li1">NC</li> <li class="li1">The Odd Squad                                                                  CKRY-FM                            Calgary,</li> <li class="li1">Alberta</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ON-AIR</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR – MEDIUM MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">97 Country Breakfast Club with Roger, Tom,             WPCV-FM                          </li> <li class="li1"> Lakeland, FL</li> </ul><p class="p5">Melissa and DJ Thee Trucker</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Buzz Jackson                                                                     </li> <li class="li1">KIIM-FM                              Tucson, AZ</li> <li class="li1">Cash and Carey                                                                </li> <li class="li1">KWEN-FM                            Tulsa, OK</li> <li class="li1">Steve &amp; Gina and the Kat 103.7 Morning Show         KXKT-FM                            </li> <li class="li1"> Omaha, NE</li> <li class="li1">Wynn &amp; Wilson in The Morning                                   WQMX-FM                        </li> <li class="li1">  Akron, OH</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>ON-AIR</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> PERSONALITY OF THE YEAR – SMALL MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Brian Gary, Todd Harding, and Susan          KUAD-FM                           </li> <li class="li1">Ft. Collins-Greeley, CO</li> </ul><p class="p1">             Moore -The Good Morning Guys</p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">Gator, Styckman, Cowboy Kyle                                   WUSY-FM                          </li> <li class="li1">Chattanooga, TN</li> <li class="li1">M. Fletcher Brown                                                         WXFL-FM                           </li> <li class="li1">Florence, AL</li> <li class="li1">Philip Gibbons                                                                WGSQ-FM                         </li> <li class="li1"> Cookeville, TN</li> <li class="li1">Scotty Cox &amp; Cara Denis                                               KCLR-FM                             </li> <li class="li1">Columbia, MO</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>RADIO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> STATION OF THE YEAR – MAJOR MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">KNIX-FM                              Phoenix, AZ</li> <li class="li1">WIL-FM                                St. Louis, MO</li> <li class="li1">WKLB-FM                            Boston, MA</li> <li class="li1">WSOC-FM                           Charlotte, NC</li> <li class="li1">WUSN-FM                          Chicago, IL</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>RADIO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> STATION OF THE YEAR – LARGE MARKET </b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">CKRY-FM                             Calgary, Alberta</li> <li class="li1">KAJA-FM                             San Antonio, TX</li> <li class="li1">WMIL-FM                            Milwaukee, WI</li> <li class="li1">WUBE-FM                           Cincinnati, OH</li> <li class="li1">WWKA-FM                         Orlando, FL</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>RADIO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> STATION OF THE YEAR – MEDIUM MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">KUZZ-AM/FM                    Bakersfield, CA</li> <li class="li1">KXKT-FM                             Omaha, NE</li> <li class="li1">WCYQ-FM                           Knoxville, TN</li> <li class="li1">WQMX-FM                         Akron, OH</li> <li class="li1">WYRK-FM                            Buffalo, NY</li> </ul><p class="p2"> </p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>RADIO</b></span></p> <p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b> STATION OF THE YEAR – SMALL MARKET</b></span></p> <ul class="ul1"> <li class="li1">KCLR-FM                              Columbia, MO</li> <li class="li1">KTHK-FM                             Idaho Falls, ID</li> <li class="li1">WGSQ-FM                          Cookeville, TN</li> <li class="li1">WXFL-FM                            Florence, AL</li> <li class="li1">WYCT-FM                            Pensacola, FL</li> </ul>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e3bf9a82ccee1eb0f9129ecdc08e51a4" t="1422650391" feed="200847" position="19"><title>Chris Hardwick looks back at five years of Nerdist</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/chris-hardwick-discusses-nerdist-podcasts-5th-anniversary</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422626534/nerdistpodcast.jpeg?itok=9yPv83Al" t="image/jpeg" author="Tyler Ross">Atrossity Photography (Tyler Ross)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Five years in, Chris Hardwick’s Nerdist is only continuing to grow.</p> <p>What started as three friends gathering around some microphones on Super Bowl Sunday in 2010 has turned into over 600 episodes of the flagship Nerdist podcasts, a website, and a host of other podcasts on the Nerdist Network. </p> <p>The show celebrates its fifth anniversary with <a href="http://www.nerdist.com/pepisode/nerdist-podcast-5th-anniversary-show/">episode 631</a>, a special live show recorded at the <a href="http://nerdmeltla.com/">NerdMelt Showroom</a>. Hardwick spoke to  <em>EW</em> about the live show, what Nerdist has meant for him over the last five years, and where he hopes to take it in the years to come.</p> <p><strong><em>EW</em>: So the fifth anniversary episode is out, but how did the show go from your perspective?</strong><br /><strong>Chris Hardwick: </strong>It was amazing. We didn’t really plan what it was going to be, but it became this celebratory retrospective. I hope it doesn’t come off too much like we’re patting each other on the back, but we started a thing five years ago, and it’s grown and it’s changed our lives and we’ve learned more than I ever could have dreamed that we could have learned from it. We had our producer Katie [Levine] and Kyle [Clark], who’s our production assistant, and my mom came out. We took quemments [a question and a comment] from the audience. It was kind of a last minute idea, like “Oh for the fifth anniversary let’s just do something at Meltdown.” So doing the podcast in the theater, and the theater exists because there’s a podcast. Seeing this community that’s sprouted up around it was pretty incredible. </p> <p>When you’re doing a podcast, it doesn’t feel like you’re doing anything official. It just feels like, oh I’m having a conversation with someone I really want to talk to. So you don’t really think of it in terms of, people are going to hear this and maybe news will break from it, or we’ll have the <em>X-Files</em> 2015 hashtag. But it affects something outside of it, and that’s where I go, oh, I guess it really is a form of media like radio or television. But we just don’t think of it like that on a day-to-day basis.</p> <p><strong>And since it’s started there’s been such a huge growth, not just in popularity but in the dedication of the listeners. How has it been to see that community expand?</strong><br /> Yeah, it has, and the other crazy thing about it is, in the beginning, we had to beg people to come on, and [say] “OK, it’s a podcast, it’s like an internet radio chat.” We were trying to explain what a podcast was to people. “It’s a conversation. You just come in and have a conversation.” And [the reaction] was “What is this? Who listens to this?” [ <em>laughs</em>]</p> <p><strong>“I’ve never heard of one of those before!”</strong><br /> Yeah, exactly. But for every guest we got, it opened the door to another series of guests. So we’re fortunate that enough people took chances with it along the way that now we’re close to 700 episodes in, but the thing that I never really foresaw was, I always assumed that people would just listen to the podcast for the guests. And we started the hostful podcasts, which one of our listeners pointed out was a nicer term than saying guestless [ <em>laughs</em>]. It was really just a way to condition the audience many years, like, “Someday I’m going to run out of friends who can be guests and it’s just going to be Matt, Jonah, and myself, and I’m training you to be OK with that.” And I assumed that people would mostly pass over those and listen to the guest episodes. But what strangely happened was that the hostfuls developed their own personality because it was just the three of us catching up with each other, and those get just as many, if not more downloads than a lot of the guested episodes.</p> <p><strong>Oh wow, really?</strong><br /> Yeah, and so that was something I didn’t really foresee happening. And it’s always the one thing people are like, “Do more hostfuls, do more hostfuls.” And we try, but our schedules have been just a little bit crazy, for good reasons.</p> <p><strong>When listening to the hostfuls, you, Matt [Mira], and Jonah [Ray] often aren’t afraid to open up about your personal lives. How has it been to see the audience have this window into you not just as a host but as someone they can relate to?</strong><br /> As a person, you just go, “well no one wants to hear about me. I’m boring. No one gives a crap about that.” What happens with stand up is you tend to start writing about things that are out in the external world, and the more and more you start to talk about yourself, you think “I’m not doing anything, I’m just talking about myself.” But people connect with that more, and you realize that’s what makes you different because you’re you. That just surprised me, and it makes so much sense now, but it didn’t before, that we’re all just looking for human experiences to connect to with each other. I think a lot of our podcasts, and podcasts in general, feel, as a listener, like you’re sitting in the room. You have to make some effort to get it into your head, which I think is good because it means you’re a little more invested in it. Media that just happens as you’re near it, you’re less invested in and it’s a little more disposable to you, but people tend to really consume [podcasts] as a very intimate form of media because it guides you through your day. It gets people through breakups, it gets them through happy times, or exams or work, or public transportation, or exercise. So we accompany people through very personal times in their lives. </p> <p><strong>It makes the audience feel like a part of something.</strong><br /> I’m proud of the audience. When people come out to live shows, I’m like, these are people I’d hang out with. They’re not just audience members, they’re part of, it sounds hokey, but they’re friends, a community. And then you realize, well if they are not turned off by how we communicate on the podcast, they are probably someone who could sit in with us. I’m very proud of the community around it, and especially when we do live shows, the venues always say “I can’t believe how nice your audience is.” And I’m like, “Yeah, they’re nerds. They’re nice. They don’t want trouble. They just want to come enjoy a thing, they’re peaceful.” [laughter]</p> <p>And then on top of that, we all text each other after podcasts with people that we can’t beleive we just met and talked to. There was a run at the end of last year that was like, Benedict CUmberbatch, Martin Short, Henry Winkler, Paul MCCartney. We just did Bill Gates. It’s silly that we keep tricking these people into sitting down and talking with us. I mean, we sat in Martin Short’s kitchen and he gave us coffee and we just talked.</p> <p><strong>I think that helps the audience relate, because you’re fans of the people you talk to just as they are. Are there moments, like that run at the end of 2014, since the beginning, where you were shocked by who was willing to come on the show?</strong><br /> Well, that always happens where we say, “I can’t believe this person agreed to do the podcast and turned out to be really cool.” Then all of a sudden, Tom Cruise is on, and we can’t believe we got Tom Cruise, and I can’t believe we got Morgan Freeman. But, now, media companies and people are starting to see the value in podcasting, and so they come to us now and pitch us people. Like, Jeff Bridges is coming on next week for a third time. We got a call, “Jeff wants to come back on the podcast.” Like, “OK. Yes!” So I think because the podcast audiences are very engaged, the bigger media outlets are starting to realize that 400,000 podcast listeners are probably more engaged than a million, two million people just watching television at night. Personally, I saw more of an uptick in attendance to my live shows, which has always been a huge goal of mine, from the podcast than all the previous TV things I had done up to that point combined.</p> <p><strong>As a comedy fan, it’s great to see the Nerdist podcast develop from one show into this network that gives a platform to a whole group of really talented comedians.</strong><br /> It’s been great because when I started mine, and I immediately saw people were paying attention, and I had ownership over it, not just in the business sense but I mean spiritual and creative ownership over it, that you don’t get that a lot in the entertainment business. And then when I saw how much fun that was and how it was actually benefitting not just my stand-up writing but live performances, then I immediately ran around and was like, “Kumail [Nanjiani], you’ve got to do a podcast. Pete Holmes, you’ve got to do a podcast. There’s this really great thing and you should be doing it because it’ll change your life.” So it’s been really great to see, the first time Kumail went on the road and saw a bunch of people with Indoor Kids shirts, he was like, “I can’t believe it, you were right. People are paying attention.”</p> <p>Podcasts were a survival mechanism for comedians who didn’t have the same television stand-up show outlet to express themselves anymore, and a stand-up is entirely defined by his or her voice, so if you’re not able to get that out into the world, how should people know whether they should come see you or not? So podcasts, we were the tiny mammals that crawled out of the earth after the asteroid wiped out the dinosaurs of big media and started to thrive because we needed a form of expression. [ <em>laughs</em>]</p> <p><strong>And so as it continues to grow, to episode 1,000 and beyond over the next five years, what do you hope to do with the show?</strong><br /> Well the medium is fun because you can really do anything you want with it. We started doing live shows in the first couple of months that we started it, and then, “Hey why don’t we go in studio?, Ben Folds is going to come on, so why don’t we go in studio and have him play?” We just had Cold War Kids on the show, Broken Bells played a song, Wilco, Spoon, all these really great bands.</p> <p>Something happened when we did the Bill Gates episode where, after we talked to Bill, they said, “Oh well there are other people in the foundation if you want to come down and chat with them.” And at first I was like, well, we got the guy, I think we’re OK. But then I thought, “Well we’ve got the recording equipment, why not? I’m actually interested in talking to the guy who is trying to eradicate polio from the planet or the woman who manages the charity fund that doles out a billion and a half dollars in investments in humanity.” The returns they’re trying to get back for those investments isn’t monetary, it’s “How can we go into a culture and give them an infrastructure so they can then sustain themselves?” So I talked to both of them for 40 minutes each and they were, of course, fascinating. So it made me think, why couldn’t we do a TED Talk thing every once in a while and have an educator on or a scientist or some type of thought leader? I would love to see it expand more on the cultural front rather than just the pop cultural front because what I’ve learned is that everyone has a story, everyone has experiences, everyone has a path that they took, and they’re all interesting. So yes, I would love to get Bill Murray on, I would love to get Steve Martin on. There are still people I would love to get on, but why not also talk to the Elon Musks of the world? And of course, do more hostfuls [ <em>laughs</em>].</p> <p><strong>And in expanding what Nerdist can be about, it’s also expanded just beyond the podcast. Not just to the website and other shows, but even things like <em>@Midnight</em>, which, even if not directly, feels very much of apiece with the podcast.</strong><br /> Yes, it all kind of connects. This little podcast that we did just for us that started five years ago on Super Bowl Sunday in 2010 has now given us the greatest experiences that we could have ever [imagined]. I did a podcast with my dad a couple of years ago, and that was the most significant conversation we’d ever had in our relationship, and that changed the way we saw each other. And everyone who listened, a lot of people [said] it spoke to them about family, and how to talk to your elders as human beings and not just the person that tells you whether you can do stuff. And then when my dad died a little over a year ago, I’m so fortunate that I have that with him now. So going from just watching the first couple thousand people download the podcast to, I think it’s somewhere between six and seven million downloads a month now, so it’s really been life changing. And I can’t believe it’s been five years, half a decade. So we’ll just continue to do it, and like I said to the guys before, we’ll just keep doing it as long as it’s fun.</p>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:64e277ad0a64c39211d0072fc1525f17" t="1422649003" feed="200847" position="20"><title>'Fortitude' premiere react: We're Not in Arendelle Anymore</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/fortitude-premiere-react</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/fortitude.jpg?itok=faR6hiNU" t="image/jpeg" author="Amanda Searle/Sky Vision">Amanda Searle/Sky Vision</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><em>This post contains details from the premiere of </em>Fortitude <em>, which aired Jan. 29.</em></p> <p>“Everyone’s got a job, no one’s poor, so there’s no stealing, no crime. Everybody’s happy.”  <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">—Natalie Yelburton (Sienna Guillory), scientist and Fortitude resident</span></p> <p>There are many underlying themes to the chilling new drama <em>Fortitude,</em> which debuted on the little-known cable network <a href="http://www.pivot.tv/">Pivot</a> Thursday night. Beware the lure of paradise seems to be the one that sticks out following the series’ two-hour premiere. It makes sense, considering that in addition to <em>Fortitude</em>’s large, <em>Downton </em><em>Abbey</em>-esque cast, probably the most major character on the show is the Arctic landscape. The majestic glaciers (or, as so many of the British characters pronounce it, gla-SEE-ers) at every angle can indeed fool you into thinking that this secluded island in the middle of nowhere will provide the answers to all of life’s troubles—which is of course what attracted so many of Fortitude’s citizens to take up residence there. But Fortitude is a place full of secrets, and we’ve stumbled upon this not-so-Shangri-La at the absolute worst time: the moment of its very first murder.</p> <p>As much as you want to spend all of the premiere gazing at <em>Fortitude’</em>s frozen wonderland and the several instances of aurora borealis—the show is shot primarily in Iceland—the plot and character identification quickly take precedence. And you want to make note of who everyone is if you have any hope of solving the crime from the comfort of your couch. This is most likely why the murder in question doesn’t happen until the end of the first episode—we need that time to sort out who everyone is in this town. The good news for avid TV and movie watchers: There are a lot of familiar faces popping up in <em>Fortitude</em>, which should help in keeping the characters straight in our minds <em>.</em> There’s Sheriff Dan Anderssen (Richard Dormer—Beric Dondarrion to <em>Game of Thrones</em> fans), who we see is harboring secrets from his very first appearance in the opening scene, which takes place three months before the story officially begins. In the prologue, Dan covers up a mysterious death witnessed by photographer and longtime Fortitude resident Henry Tyson (Professor Dumbledore himself, Michael Gambon). Henry, like many other characters on the show, is a British citizen, and he eventually becomes a key player in the murder investigation when a rambling drunken phone call, in which he makes serious allegations against Fortitude’s governor, results in the arrival of a London detective to Fortitude’s kingdom of isolation.</p> <p>The governor, Hildur Odegard (Sofie Gråbøl), has a pet project, you see. The Glacier Hotel is a state-of-the art resort that aims to bring romance, adventure, and most importantly, cold hard cash into Fortitude, which has been suffering financially in recent years. Professor Charlie Stoddart (Christopher Eccleston), head of the Arctic Research Centre, oversees the environmental impact assessment for the hotel project. All is going swimmingly—even Hildur’s plan to construct the hotel right in the glacier, à la <a href="http://www.icehotel.com/">the Ice Hotel</a>—until two local kids find a thawed mammoth tooth near the building site and the scientist is forced to reconsider his findings.</p> <p>So when—spoiler alert!—Charlie turns up dead at the end of the first hour, his chest completely eviscerated by an unknown assailant, the suspects are rampant. Was it the already established-to-be-shady sheriff, doing the governor’s bidding? It <em>was</em> a little odd that Dan showed up seconds after Charlie’s body was first discovered by Vincent Rattrey (Luke Treadaway), the newest member of the professor’s research team. (Vincent, FYI, is taken into custody for being at the wrong place at the wrong time.) Or was it Dan’s search-and-rescue colleague, ex-English-military man Frank Sutter (Nicholas Pinnock), who, after returning home from his tryst with sexy Spanish waitress Elena Ledesma (Verónica Echegui), is shown to have blood smeared all over his shirt? Even if Frank didn’t commit the murder, he still wins the Most Loathsome Fortitude Resident award by the end of the series premiere for the following misdeeds: He cheats on his wife, Jules ( <em>Call the Midwife’</em>s Jessica Raine), and is an all-out creep to her at every moment. Then he abandons his possibly polio-infected son, Liam, to go bang Elena. And did we mention Liam was one of the two kids who found the mammoth tooth that caused all this trouble in the first place?</p> <p>If Hildur was behind the murder, then she’s got balls the size of glaciers. Halfway through the second episode, Detective Chief Inspector Eugene Morton (an outstanding Stanley Tucci) appears on the scene, and Hildur is willing to give him carte blanche to conduct his investigation however he sees fit. Dan, on the other hand, isn’t as welcoming. He’s so intimidated by DCI Morton’s presence that he utters <em>Fortitude’</em>s first instance of what’s presumed to be Norwegian—it is never stated which country Fortitude is supposed to be in, but given the preponderance of Norwegian flags and the word “Politi” emblazoned on the local police officers’ uniforms, it’s a safe assumption—in an effort to, well, ice out the British-American interloper. But since this is Fortitude’s first murder in its entire history and the victim was a British citizen, the investigation cannot be left to a police force that is better equipped to handle bear attacks than calculated killings. Therefore, the London Metropolitan Police have sent along everyone’s favorite fairy godfather, <a href="http://www.imdb.com/character/ch0009663/">Nigel</a>. As Hildur states in a diplomatic yet helpfully expository fashion for the viewers, especially those wondering why a British detective looks and sounds so much like Stanley Tucci, “DCI Morton is a forensics expert. He can provide invaluable analytical skills, skills and experiences that he acquired working with the FBI.”</p> <p>Tucci’s delayed arrival to <em>Fortitude</em> doesn’t give the actor much time to establish his presence as the fish-out-of-water detective prepared to crack this murder case wide open, but it doesn’t matter. He is clearly the best part of the show, whether he’s analyzing a cadaver or sparring with his first of many enemies, Sheriff Anderssen. Gene Morton may need a crash course in frozen-tundra living, as well as an entire new wardrobe—newsboy caps don’t keep out the cold as well as fur-lined ones with ear flaps—but if anyone’s going to solve this murder by the end of 12 episodes, it’s undoubtedly going to be him. So be sure to check your cable provider to see if Pivot is available in your area, because a scheduled weekly date with <em>Fortitude</em>, preferably viewed while covered in a down quilt and sipping a stiff drink, sounds like the best way to ride out any long, cold lonely winter.  </p> <p>Fortitude <em>airs on Thursdays at 10 p.m. on Pivot.</em></p>]]></description><author>Sarene Leeds</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:c216740862aea062b65ad5cebcac36bc" t="1422649001" feed="200847" position="21"><title>'It's Always Sunny's' David Hornsby: 'How do we degrade Rickety Cricket more?'</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/david-hornsby/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/rs_1024x759-131011100903-1024-bones-wedding-18-jl_-101113.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/rickety-cricket_480x360.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/gafsugw.jpg?w=611&amp;h=542" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/iasip_60408_275tvs4259208.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><em>It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia</em>‘s Rickety Cricket—the defrocked priest turned disfigured alley dweller played by David Hornsby—is one of the most twisted characters on the show. Seeing the sheer torture this guy goes through all because of the gang’s antics is just a joy to watch. (That warped statement would only make sense in the context of a show like this.)</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Hornsby, who also serves as executive producer and writer on <em>Sunny</em>, took a break from working on the show to talk shop with the EW Community. <span id="more-33775"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY COMMUNITY: Rickety Cricket is definitely one of the more memorable characters in recent TV history. He’s gone through the wringer. How do you keep coming up with ideas for him?</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>DAVID HORNSBY:</strong> It’s as easy as trying to think of what is the next degradation for him, physically. It’s always something that we ask, “How do we degrade him more?” Cricket falls into an episode somewhere; we don’t lead with a Cricket idea, usually. We fold him into an episode in a kind of fun way to sort of set up this next level of how we can degrade him. It’s one of the fun aspects of him. And people like to degrade me as well. It’s another way of [asking], “What can we do to David that would put him in the makeup chair longer?”</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Actually, one of our readers commented that Rickety looks kind of like Freddy Krueger now. So what was the makeup process for that like?</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">I’m starting to rival the makeup air time of Eddie Murphy, or Steve Carell in <em>Foxcatcher</em>. Every time they degrade me, it ends up being more time in the makeup chair. It’s about two- to three-hour makeup sessions. I have to start growing my goatee early on, so at some point I have a goatee that’s very wolflike … like Wolfman Jack. That very bushy goatee for months that I have to keep. It’s not my wife [ <em>Bones</em> star Emily Deschanel]’s favorite.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img class="" title="Hornsby" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/gafsugw.jpg?w=611&amp;h=542" alt="FXX" width="611" height="542" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sunny has been renewed for two more seasons. Any plans for Rickety Cricket’s life shaping up? Will anything ever go right for that poor guy?</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Well, Cricket reflects the depravity of the main characters. So as long as they stay depraved, his body and mind will suffer the consequences. So probably not. He probably will face just a terrible demise, but you never know. It might be fun to rise from the ashes. We’ll see how it progresses and take it season by season. But I think the fun is watching him go from a very human priest to some sort of dark street rat … that’s kind of the fun of his character. That’s why I keep coming back.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Now about you. You do it all: write, produce, and act. When did you know that’s what you wanted to do?</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">I’ve always enjoyed doing creative things in more than one avenue, so this kind of job is perfect for me, because I’m able to act, write, and sit in a room every day with funny people and laugh and make jokes. So it’s kind of the perfect job. I started young as an actor, but I’ve always enjoyed many creative outlets. Even things from drawing and learning to Photoshop, to writing and acting. It’s all an extension of that creative stuff. This is really the perfect job for me: being able to do those things and do them with friends.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img title="It" src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/iasip_60408_275tvs4259208.jpg" alt="FXX" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Are there any particular writers or actors growing up to now who really influenced you?</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Bruce Hornsby and the Range from very early on. Well, he’s my cousin, so … that was kind of my first creative influence, just because he’s in the family. No, I’m just kidding!</p> <p style="text-align:left;">In terms of writing and acting and all that stuff, James Brooks is someone I’ve always looked up to. I write more jokes about someone [being degraded] for a six-pack, where he wrote more about the human condition. But filmmakers like James Brooks and Albert Brooks from very early on were people I always responded to.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The ability to write things filled with a lot of humanity shows how powerful media, television, and movies can be. And then, I grew up on a lot of TV comedies like <em>The State—</em> and some <em>Saved by the Bell</em>, admittedly.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><a href="http://www.fxnetworks.com/shows/its-always-sunny-in-philadelphia"><strong>It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia</strong></a> <strong><em>airs Wednesdays at 10/9C on FXX.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Morissa Schwartz</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:51ede963a403faae6380f520410d9e90" t="1422649000" feed="200847" position="22"><title>4 best moments from the 'Grey's Anatomy' midseason premiere</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/greys-anatomy-midseason-top-4/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/greys.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Season 11 | Episode 9 | “Where Do We Go From Here?” | Aired Jan 29, 2015</strong><strong><br /> </strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Well. <em>Grey’s Anatomy</em> left us with a lot of big questions that were sure to bring all of its fans to #GreysTears. The hashtag kept appearing throughout the episode—but no matter how many tears were shed, there was no way <em>Grey’s</em> could bring resolution to a power couple’s separation, an inoperable brain tumor, and a breakable baby in just one hour. There’s a whole second half of the season to address those issues.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">But the midseason premiere of <em>Grey’s Anatomy</em> did offer some amazing moments and character development (and maybe the most quotable 7-year-old ever). Here are the four best moments from this week’s episode, “Where Do We Go From Here?” <span id="more-33780"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>4. The Brick Wall Assface</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">I know that singling out a patient as a highlight of an episode is a little crazy, but honestly, when a 7-year-old gets to say “assface” on television (and so snarky, at that), you have to pay attention. For such a little guy, the younger of two brothers involved in a car accident really steps up and steals the show. He repeatedly tells Dr. Bailey that he’s a “brick wall” after his older brother tells him to keep his mouth shut about the accident. He even calls her bluff when she threatens to call child protective services. He only caves when his brother almost dies on the table.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>3. Smart, Brilliant Tumor Versus Smart, Brilliant Surgeon</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Amelia is a tricky broad, but she’s also arrogantly charming in that Shepherd family way. As Dr. Herman discovers that her brain tumor has been put in the art gallery of Seattle Grace Mercy West brain tumors, she flips and tells Arizona and Amelia to shut it down. Amelia responds, “Your tumor is smart and brilliant, but so am I.” And the entire episode shows Dr. Herman pushing back against any idea of a surgery, until the beautiful moment Geena Davis has in the bathroom when we <em>finally</em> see Dr. Herman cry. It takes an impassioned Arizona to finally make Dr. Herman see that hope doesn’t have to be lost.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>2. A Broken Post-it Note</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">So, if you were confused about who was <em>really</em> going all-in with this D.C-forced separation, the Post-it trashing should have made it clear. In the most Ellis Grey way imaginable, Meredith tucks Zola into bed, looks up at the Post-it, rips that trendy shadow box off the wall, and tosses it in the trash like Denny Duquette’s first heart. And what makes it even harder? Derek had the same moment, and <em>left it on the wall</em>. At the end of the episode, Meredith gets one more opportunity to ask him to stay, but she lets him leave for D.C. anyway. Meredith didn’t need Derek to leave—because in her mind, he was already gone. Sure, the Post-it was replaced by the end of the episode, but it’s still got a big chunk missing.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>1. Mother of Faith, Mother of Science</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">We don’t get to hear how Jackson breaks it to April that their “little Buddha” has a rare disease that is almost certainly fatal before birth, but we do get to <em>see it</em>. And as fantastic as every Jesse Williams outburst is, it’s Sarah Drew who really pulls the weight in the midseason premiere. With her maternal duties suddenly shattered, April goes on the warpath: Callie, Stephanie, Maggie, and Owen all end up being casualties. But at the end of the night, April has given up almost all hope. She finally wonders how God can let these things happen. It’s going to be a long, ugly, beautiful season for April Kepner.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">What do you think? Did the midseason premiere live up to your expectations? How crazy do you think Amelia’s plan is? And can we make sure that little kid gets to guest star, like, every episode?</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong><a href="http://abc.go.com/shows/greys-anatomy" target="_blank">Grey’s Anatomy</a> <em>airs Thursdays at 8/7C on ABC.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Justin Kirkland</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2e26edc7462c7e72c7a150ffeff91bc1" t="1422648999" feed="200847" position="23"><title>'Backstrom' fan recap: Some men just want to watch the world burn</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/backstrom-season-one-episode-two-recap-bella/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/backstrom-cover-photo.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/backstrom-photo-2.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/backstrom-photo-3.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Season 1 | Episode 2 | “Bella” | Aired Jan 29, 2015</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">This week, <em>Backstrom</em> battles arsonists, thieves, and <em>How to Get Away With Murder</em>‘s midseason premiere.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Last episode, we met Lt. Everett Backstrom, a jerk with a nose for sniffing out bad guys and a mouth for saying racist stuff. At the end of the show’s premiere, Backstrom was given the all-clear to return to Portland’s Special Cases Unit full time. For his first official job back, he and the rest of his team are tasked with hunting down an arsonist who’s been plaguing Portland’s nicer neighborhoods. <span id="more-33786"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;">As the episode opens, we see our trusty hero smoking a stogie in front of a smoldering residence. A young boy asks, “Are you gonna catch the bad man who burned down my house?” Backstrom tells the kid to back off, and another urban youth loses his faith in the police. Backstrom’s partner, Gravely, shows up and informs the detective that the crime has been upgraded to attempted murder, because there were people inside the house when it was torched.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">They police are in luck, however: An arson investigator from the fire department wants to help. Or just spread the blame around, depending on whether you subscribe to Backstrom’s misanthropic worldview or not. He says the arson expert is suspicious, because of course he does.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Inside the burned remains of the house, he announces that more than one crime has been committed here. (He also finds a bottle of vodka and helps himself.) His theory: Firefighters are setting fires so they can cherry-pick the remains. Did I mention Backstrom <em>hates</em> firefighters?</p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;">Back outside, the two partners run into a couple of firefighters (who look suspiciously like the models who pose as firefighters on sexy calendars, and not actually like real firefighters at all). These guys are the D’Agostino brothers (Eddie McClintock and Matt Battaglia), and they and Backstrom have some beef. Apparently, they all grew up together, and the brothers teased baby Backstrom mercilessly and stole a beloved item from him (more on that later).</p> <p style="text-align:left;">At the office, the team is split on whether they should be looking for arsonists or thieves (or arsonist-thieves, in Backstrom’s case). Niedermayer and Gravely stick with the arson idea, while you-know-who continues to let his irrational hatred of firefighters cloud his judgment. Nadia points out that their case fits the pattern of an arsonist known as the “Green Flame” (so named because the chemicals used to start the fires burn green).</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Back at Backstrom’s apartment, the detective asks his roommate/interior decorator, Valentine (Thomas Dekker), for help locating items that were reported destroyed on the arson insurance forms. Valentine, who happens to specialize in procuring certain items (aka stealing), says he might know a guy.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Next on Backstrom’s list of unlawful search and seizure techniques: He persuades Nadia to forge a warrant so he can get inside the firehouse. He and Almond check out where the enemy lives, and find a dead canary hanging in a firefighter’s locker. It’s a threat: Dead canaries don’t sing, and Backstrom realizes that one of the firefighters must know who’s been stealing from burned homes. His suspect, Dabkey (David Carzell), confirms the theory.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Meanwhile, Valentine does know a guy! He heard that one of the items supposedly destroyed in the fire, a watch, wound up at an antiques dealer. Valentine doesn’t want to blow his cover as a police informant, so he brings Niedermayer along to the store instead of Backstrom. He also brings Niedermayer because he wants to jump his bones. Niedermayer’s like, “No, thanks,” but he does confiscate the watch and place it into evidence.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">At the police station, the arson expert informs Gravely that the Green Flame may also have been active in Seattle, but she can’t tell for sure: The arsonist has switched to a different method of starting the fire, from lighting a flair to botching a fuse (which is the more sophisticated way to commit a felony).</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><img style="float:right;margin:0 0 10px 10px;" title="Backstrom Season 1 Episode 2 photo. Backstrom continues to despise firefighters." src="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/backstrom-photo-3.jpg" alt="Backstrom Season 1 Episode 2 photo. Backstrom continues to despise firefighters. Liane Hentscher/FOX" /></p> <p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;"> </p><p style="text-align:left;">Watch in hand, Backstrom heads to the fire station, where he meets the D’Agostino brothers once again. They reminisce cheerfully about that time they threw baby Backstrom off a bridge, and he responds by planting the watch on younger brother Sam (McClintock) and then arresting him. We also learn that the item the brothers stole from Backstrom was something called “Bella,” though the thing is left pretty vague. (I guess someone in the writers’ room has been watching <em>Citizen Kane</em>.) During Sam’s interrogation, the detective brings up the brothers’ old rivalry over a girl to turn them against each other. It seems to work.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Until it doesn’t. The next day (after a brief episode in which some EMTs—who are in league with the firefighters—defibrillate Backstrom <em>while he’s conscious</em> and then dump him on the side of the road), the lieutenant returns to the firehouse, only to find the brothers reconciled. They confess (basically out of nowhere) that they have indeed been stealing from the houses, but they haven’t been setting the fires (they have standards). They also reveal Bella’s location: a shed in Backstrom’s hometown.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Still on the hunt for the arsonist, Backstrom meets Gravely and Moto at a nice suburban house. Who should be parked outside breathing heavily but … the arson expert! Turns out, Nadia realized that she’d been slipping them false information (in fact, all the fires in Seattle and Portland had been started the same way, with flares), and Gravely did the math. She asks if Backstrom wants to make the arrest, but he says it’s all hers. What a sweetheart. Isn’t it a little early in the season to be humanizing this guy?</p> <p style="text-align:left;">At the end of the episode, Backstrom and Valentine arrive at the shed where the D’Agostinos hid Bella. And—drumroll please—Bella is a kite! A big kite in the shape of a whale that Backstrom made himself as a kid. The friends frolic with Bella in a park, and it is so corny. Roll credits.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><a href="http://www.fox.com/backstrom" target="_blank"><strong>Backstrom</strong></a> <strong><em>airs Thursdays at 9/C on Fox.</em></strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;"></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Ariel Kay</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:9ae6ed5ac3186d983ac439857606c7c2" t="1422648999" feed="200847" position="24"><title>Neil Patrick Harris tries to do a big number in variety show promo</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/neil-patrick-harris-tries-do-big-number-variety-show-promo</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/neil-patrick-harris_0.jpg?itok=_z4T9lbg" t="image/jpeg" author="NBC">NBC</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">With the Oscars coming up, promos starring Neil Patrick Harris are <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/12/26/neil-patrick-harris-oscar-promo">par</a> <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/02/neil-patrick-harris-has-new-years-resolutions-for-you-in-latest-oscar-promo">for</a> the course, but the latest doesn’t have to do with handing out trophies to movie stars. Instead, here’s a promo for Harris’s upcoming NBC variety show, in which he attempts a big production number only to be thwarted by the time limit. Too bad. </span></p> <div itemprop="video" itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/VideoObject"> <iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="270" seamless="seamless" src="//player.theplatform.com/p/NnzsPC/widget/select/media/_QDvSlS_HHuz" width="480"></iframe></div> <div itemprop="video" itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/VideoObject"> Even before the show was <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/10/27/neil-patrick-harris-nbc-variety-show">announced</a>, Harris had publicly discussed wanting to do a variety show, which seems like the perfect fit for multi-talented performer and go-to awards show host. The show will be <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/10/27/neil-patrick-harris-nbc-variety-show">based</a> on the British series <em> Ant and Dec’s Saturday Night Takeaway</em>. </div>]]></description><author>Esther Zuckerman</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:484176e6c06e43345e2095a116c2c775" t="1422648997" feed="200847" position="25"><title>Watch Ben Affleck, Matt Damon confess to 'deflate-gate' on 'Kimmel'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/watch-ben-affleck-matt-damon-confess-deflate-gate-kimmel</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422632426/Jimmy%2520Kimmel%2520Live.jpg?itok=tY2gMUuj" t="image/jpeg" author="ABC">Jimmy Kimmel Live (ABC)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/feuNeJewzDo" width="560"></iframe></p> <p>The deflate-gate controversy has been solved, according to  <em>Jimmy Kimmel Live</em>, as the perpetrators seem to have announced their involvement on Thursday’s epsiode. </p> <p>So who was the “locker room guy?”  <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">A slew of celebrities including Ben Affleck, Matt Damon, John Krasinski, Chris Evans, and Steven Tyler appeared on the show defend Tom Brady. Each revealed (in a thick Boston accent) just how they did it. </span></p> <p>Deflate-gate stems from <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/23/conan-obrien-deflategate-bill-cosby">allegations brought against the Patriots</a> that the game balls used against the Indianapolis Colts during the AFC championship game weren’t adequately filled. The NFL launched an investigation which is now reportedly focusing on a Patriots locker room attendant. </p> <p> </p>]]></description><author>Megan Daley</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:eaa3724e3cc1e5711af5b35f19e80d1f" t="1422648996" feed="200847" position="26"><title>'Two and a Half Men' fan recap: The Wrath of Ms. McMartin</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/29/two-half-men-recap-ms-mcmartin-crazy/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/105886_wb_1800b.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Season 12</strong> <strong>| Episode 12</strong> <strong>| “A Beer-Battered Rip-Off” | Aired Jan 29, 2014</strong></p> <p>It was bound to happen. The Alan we’ve all grown to know and love on <em> Two and a Half Men</em> has yet again found a way to inadvertently wreak havoc on those around him. Once Alan began to date Ms. McMartin, their social worker—who is actually being very cool about Walden and Alan’s secret—it was obvious that things would go awry sooner than later. <span id="more-33790"></span></p> <p>The episode starts out with Ms. McMartin telling Walden that they are ready to begin the process of officially adopting Louis. But before they can go any further, she puts her foot down and says they have to tell Louis they aren’t really gay. Alan says he’s relieved that they can finally give up the charade, right before he compliments her on her “fierce” blouse. They break the news to Louis, but strangely it happens off screen. We only know about it because Berta mentions it to Alan in the next scene.</p> <p>Lyndsey arrives with a box full of Alan’s old things, including a boombox with one of his mix CDs. “Mambo No. 5″ leads to a cringe-worthy Alan-dance. Seriously, Alan dancing to “Mambo No. 5″ is a hard visual to process.</p> <p>Anyway, that’s not all Lyndsey was there for; apparently, she wants to move away and start fresh after recovering from her alcohol problem. Alan doesn’t really know how to feel about it, but they hug it out. They hang on for a bit too long, and before you know it, they are making love to Lou Bega’s hit song. Alan tells Lyndsey he wants to give them another chance. He even lies to her, saying he’s not seeing anyone else, just to get her to stick around. She says she has to take some time to think about it.</p> <p>Walden sees Lyndsey walk out of Alan’s room and immediately knows what’s up. Alan tells Walden he wants to give his relationship with Lyndsey another shot, that he and Ms. McMartin aren’t serious, and that he’ll break it off. Walden is worried, and rightly so, that Ms. McMartin won’t like getting dumped. At dinner, Alan is three seconds into the breakup speech before Ms. McMartin snaps back, surprised and a bit insulted. She blames herself for getting involved, and Alan tells her she dodged a middle-age, lactose-intolerant bullet.</p> <p>A storm hits in the middle of the night and the doorbell rings multiple times, waking both Walden and Alan to see what the trouble is. The trouble is a soaked, mascara-running, hate-filled Ms. McMartin at their door. “Surprise! It’s inspection time,” she says, as the guys react in horror. She finds a boatload of safety issues with the house and is obviously using her power to get back at Alan. Alan believes he can smooth things over, but Walden forbids him from seeing her: He’s afraid he’ll dig an even deeper hole because she still doesn’t even know about Lyndsey.</p> <p>Instead, Alan goes to lunch with Lyndsey to a restaurant an hour’s drive away. Just as Lyndsey tells Alan she’ll stay and give their relationship another chance, guess who shows up? Like a terrifying horror movie, Ms. McMartin actually followed Alan all the way to his lunch date and finds out about Lyndsey. Needless to say, both Ms. McMartin and Lyndsey do not leave happy, and Alan’s shirt does not go unsplashed with wine.</p> <p>Alan breaks the news to Walden, telling him that Ms. McMartin has gone crazy. “No. She hasn’t gone crazy. You drove her crazy! You make people crazy!” he shouts. Alan says he’ll fix this, and Walden loses it. Outside, he shouts to the masses not to worry—”Alan is gonna fix everything!”—and throws all of the chairs off the balcony. “Maybe I do make people crazy,” Alan realizes.</p> <p>Walden shows up at Ms. McMartin’s apartment to apologize and try to fix things himself. He’s worried that she’ll take it out on Walden and Louis. She tells him not to worry; she won’t let her anger prevent a child from being placed in a good home. Relieved, Walden says he never knew how much another person could mean to him. Ms. McMartin cries because she doesn’t have that for herself. He tries to comfort her and tells her she’s way too pretty for Alan. They end up in the bedroom, where Walden looks like he realizes he’s made a grave mistake. Ms. McMartin sure looks happy, though!</p> <p>At the end of the episode, Alan pulls a “Say Anything” boombox move using “Mambo No. 5″ to win back Lyndsey’s heart.</p> <p><strong>Two and a Half Thoughts</strong></p> <ul> <li>It was odd that they didn’t show the guys telling Louis they weren’t gay. There was so much importance put on it from Ms. McMartin, only for it to only be mentioned in passing.</li> <li>Ms. McMartin and Walden together was less expected after she hooked up with Alan.</li> <li>Lyndsey and Alan were made for each other.</li> </ul> <p><strong><a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/two_and_a_half_men/" target="_blank">Two and a Half Men</a> <em>airs Thursdays at 9/8C on CBS.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div>]]></description><author>Francis Santos</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:70907e753d383c3888d6929a78749e12" t="1422648994" feed="200847" position="27"><title>See the cover for Chris Colfer's 'The Curvy Tree'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/see-cover-chris-colfers-curvy-tree</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/curvy-tree-wm.jpg?itok=Av9ulOiO" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><em>Glee</em> star Chris Colfer added “ <em>New York Times</em> bestselling author” to his résumé with his <em>The Land of Stories</em> series, and now, he can also add “picture-book author.”  <em>The Curvy Tree</em> (out Oct. 27) is a companion picture book to the aforementioned series illustrated by Brandon Dorman. <em>EW</em> has a first look at the new cover. (Click “enlarge” up top to see the full image.)</p> <p>Here’s the official description: “Once upon a time, there was a little girl who didn’t quite fit in. When she runs away, she happens upon a curvy tree who helps her understand the importance of being different.” </p> <p>Also available on Oct. 27 is a new boxed set titled <em>Adventures from the Land of Stories: The Mother Goose Diaries and Queen Red Riding Hood’s Guide to Royalty</em>. </p>]]></description><author>Breia Brissey</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:13afa602f8c0ccc77b82055fb0754fa5" t="1422648993" feed="200847" position="28"><title>'Transistor,' 'Rogue Legacy' among free games for PlayStation Plus in February</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/transistor-rogue-legacy-among-free-games-playstation-plus-february</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/transistor-screenshot-01-ps4-us-23apr14.jpg?itok=h7-AlnMV" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;"><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Sony is refreshing the free games available as part of PlayStation Plus next week, and the new selection will include one of 2014’s </span><a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2014/12/26/best-video-games-of-2014" style="line-height: 1.6em;">most memorable games</a><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> and a brand new title.</span></p> <p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">Subscribers to Sony’s PlayStation Plus service on PlayStation 4, PlayStation 3, and PlayStation Vita will be able to pick up  <a href="http://blog.us.playstation.com/2015/01/29/playstation-plus-februarys-free-games/?smcid=pssocial:blog:game:feb_plus_lineup:1_29_15">six new games</a> beginning Feb. 3 for no additional cost. PlayStation 4 players will be able to download  <span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">Supergiant Games’ intriguing and beautiful action game</span>  <em>Transistor</em> and  <em>Apotheon</em>. The second title is making its PlayStation debut and tasks players with climbing Mount Olympus to steal the powers of Greek gods and protect mankind after the gods abandon humanity.</p> <p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;"><em>Yakuza 4</em> and  <em>Thief</em> will be available for PlayStation 3 players to download.  <em>Yakuza 4</em> was released several years ago, but will prep players before  <em>Yakuza 5</em> comes out later this year worldwide after debuting in Japan in 2012.  <em>Thief</em> released early last year, reviving a beloved franchise after a decade out of the spotlight.</p> <p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">Finally, PlayStation Vita players are being offered  <em>Kick &amp; Fennick</em> and  <em>Rogue Legacy</em>.  <em>Fennick</em> is a platformer that follows the adventures of a boy, Kick, and his new robot companion, Fennick, as they venture out for a new energy source to keep Fennick active.  <em>Rogue Legacy</em> tasks players with exploring a castle, which is randomly generated every time a player dies and restarts. And as an added twist, every new character players pick up is actually the descendant of the last character they played, each of whom will have different character traits that affect how they play.  <em>Rogue Legacy</em> will also be available for PS Plus users on PlayStation 4 and PlayStation 3.</p> <p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;"> </p><div id="sc-v-4022848466001-ran742" class="bc-video-player"> </div> <p style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">PlayStation Plus promises subscribers new games available to download every month. These games will be available throughout February to PS Plus users at no extra cost until new games are offered during the first week in March.</p></p>]]></description><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:91e6e00585a795a10da30b5d5d4d22a2" t="1422648993" feed="200847" position="29"><title>Jay Z to take on Spotify, buys streaming music service Aspiro</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/jay-z-take-spotify-buys-streaming-music-service-aspiro</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2013/08/29/jay-z-holy-grail_612x380.jpg?itok=sZOzAP7C" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Noted Beyonce spouse and hip-hop mogul Jay Z is about to throw his hat into the battle for music streaming supremacy. </p> <p>According to  <a href="http://time.com/3689197/jay-z-aspiro-streaming-service/"><em>Time</em></a>, the rapper is in the process of buying streaming music service  <a href="http://www.aspiro.com/">Aspiro</a> for a reported $56 million. While not widely known in the United States, the Scandinavian company has two ad-free streaming services under its belt: the Europe-only WiMP, and the more widely available Tidal high-def audio service. </p> <p>Of course, how successful it would ultimately depend on whether or not Hov can make it more appealing to artists like Taylor Swift and Radiohead, who have very publicly withdrawn from streaming music leader Spotify. </p> <p>If his lyrics are any indication, he’s probably got this all sorted out. As he’s said once before: He’s not a businessman, he’s… <a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Do3iJ6DWvpQ">you know</a>.</p>]]></description><author>Joshua Rivera</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:9ddf2fdb3d699f7aee79791b435036b3" t="1422648993" feed="200847" position="30"><title>George R.R. Martin won't release a new 'Game of Thrones' book this year</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/george-rr-martin-wont-release-new-game-thrones-book-this-year</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422635989/George-RR-Martin_610.jpg?itok=10-48PIo" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>George R.R. Martin’s long-awaited sixth novel in his A Song of Ice and Fire franchise will <em>not</em> be published this year. </p> <p>That’s <a href="http://www.theguardian.com/books/2015/jan/30/george-rr-martin-the-winds-of-winter-publication">officially from</a> Martin’s UK publisher, talking to <em>The Guardian</em>. Furthermore, 2016 might not see the book,  <em>The Winds of Winter, </em>published either.  <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">“I have no information on likely delivery,” said Jane Johnson at HarperCollins. “These are increasingly complex books and require immense amounts of concentration to write. Fans really ought to appreciate that the length of these monsters is equivalent to two or three novels by other writers.”</span></p> <p>Instead, <span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">HarperCollins</span> will publish a “new illustrated compilation of three official prequel novellas to the series, <em>The Hedge Knight</em>, <em>The Sworn Sword</em> and <em>The Mystery Knight</em>.”</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">The last book in Martin’s ASOIAF saga, <em>A Dance with Dragons</em>, was published in 2011 and fans have been extremely eager to read the next book – especially since HBO’s series version  <em>Game of Thrones</em> is expected to catch up to most of the  <em>Dragons</em>’ storylines in the upcoming fifth season (the <a href="http://ew.com/article/2015/01/30/‘game-thrones’-season-5-trailer-leaks-things-we-learned">trailer for which just leaked online today</a>). <em>Thrones</em> showrunners David Benioff and Dan Weiss, who have been told Martin’s long-term narrative plan, have said they want to do two more seasons (and only two) of the show, which still means a couple years of largely paving into virgin story territory and possibly shooting the conclusion to Martin’s saga long before the author’s book-reading fans have any idea how the epic fantasy tale will end. </span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">My take: <em>Thrones</em> is a rare instance in pop culture where a story’s books <em>and</em> filmed version are equally exceptional. The first five seasons were largely “spoiled” by the books. That Martin’s remaining stories will be potentially “spoiled” by the show is a seismic reversal in how book-readers experience the story – just not necessarily a bad one. I’m looking forward to eventually watching the show having no idea what will happen next. And ultimately, if Martin’s books will be of higher quality if he takes more time to write them, okay, take more time. </span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Of course, it’s always possible that <em>Winds</em> could come out just in time for season 6 in early 2016 … just don’t hold your breath. </span></p>]]></description><author>James Hibberd</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e3fd6c575913de3082fbb34a498083e7" t="1422648993" feed="200847" position="31"><title>How 'Parenthood' thrived, despite a spoiler-addicted society</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/parenthood-series-finale</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422635905/Parenthood%2520Bravermans.JPG?itok=nk_bPvFR" t="image/jpeg" author="Justin Lubin/NBC">Justin Lubin/NBC</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>In the age of live-tweeting, the most talked-about shows on television tend to be those that give viewers (and Twitter users) plenty of big, bold moments that inspire strong, immediate reactions. Which, in turn, means that the most talked-about shows inevitably end up being labeled TV’s most successful shows. Think about it: T <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">here’s </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">Game of Thrones,</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> with its Red Wedding, Purple Wedding, and continuous stream of unexpected deaths. We have Shonda Rhimes, who’s arguably the queen of the WTF moment with </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">Scandal</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">, </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">Grey’s Anatomy</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">, and </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">How to Get Away With Murder</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">. And then there’s the ever-more-popular </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">True Detective</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> format, which is built entirely around solving a mystery—preferably one with a surprising result. Essentially, TV’s best dramas must, on some level, be edge-of-your-seat thrillers.</span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">That is, unless they’ve got the Bravermans.</span></p> <p>Heading into <em>Parenthood</em>’s sixth and final season, series creator Jason Katims didn’t hide that the show would deal with losing a loved one. This was never a secret. And by the end of the season’s first episode, beloved patriarch Zeek Braverman had been rushed to the hospital with heart issues. Cut to the second episode, when Zeek’s son Adam asks what he’s supposed to do if his father dies. Zeek’s reply: “If I die, you just take my ashes, you scatter them at center field at Marine Park, and you play a game of baseball over me.”</p> <div itemprop="video" itemscope="" itemtype="http://schema.org/VideoObject"> <iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="270" seamless="seamless" src="//player.theplatform.com/p/NnzsPC/widget/select/media/dnU83VrGkoRD?carouselID=138911" width="480"></iframe></div> <p>At that moment,  <em>Parenthood</em>’s last scene was basically spelled out for fans—yet many still speculated that, at the last moment, Crosby’s motorcycle accident would result in internal bleeding, and he’d be the one to die. Why? Because we’ve been programmed to expect twists, to never believe what seems obvious. But that train of thought never applied to  <em>Parenthood</em>. The “what” was never what made  <em>Parenthood</em> powerful. On this show, it was the “who,” the “how,” and the “why.” </p> <p>Unlike most dramas on television,  <em>Parenthood</em> focused on normal, day-to-day life. The circumstances were the opposite of extreme—there weren’t affairs with Presidents or kidnappings or mass murders.  <em>Parenthood</em> followed the Bravermans as they dealt with bullying, first love, infidelity, money issues, sibling rivalries, and other issues that likely affected the majority of its viewers. In its most dramatic moments, the worst the Bravermans had to face were car crashes, heart attacks, cancer, PTSD, and Asperger’s Syndrome. It was a very human show, a very relatable show—and a rarity. Which raises a question: When did real life become too boring for television?</p> <p>Obviously, extreme circumstances make for good, juicy TV.  <em>Scandal</em>’s  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Id1zIn5_CEA">“bitch baby” speech</a> never would’ve happened without a foundation of murder, prostitution, and blackmail. But as great as that speech was, Zeek telling Amber that  <a href="http://www.hulu.com/watch/233852">she can’t mess up his dream</a> is just as powerful—and all it took to get to <em>his</em> speech was a teenager making a poor choice and getting into a car accident.</p> <p>And in  <em>Parenthood</em>’s final hour, which aired Thursday night, the show ended on the exact note fans expected: Zeek’s ashes being spread on a baseball field, followed by the family playing a game. Once again, the show proved that it didn’t need “spoiler alert”-worthy moments to create scenes worthy of conversation. It’s a testament to both the show’s writers and its actors that they could turn any mundane activity into must-watch television.</p> <p>So yes, the ending of  <em>Parenthood</em> was utterly predictable. But that didn’t affect its impact. This show thrived most between plot points—in the glances shared by these incredibly complex characters, in their everyday tasks, in the moments when life slows down. It was about the connection viewers felt to this family. We all wanted to be a Braverman—not because the family’s life seemed overly exciting, but because they nothing but try to be the very best they could be, always supporting one another along the way.</p> <p>That connection fans felt to these characters—and not the action of the show—is why  <em>Parenthood</em> became known as the drama that made you cry each week, whether you were weeping at something as big as a death or something as small as a Braverman dance party. At  <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">the end of the day, the action—the doing—didn’t matter, so long as the Bravermans were the ones doing it.</span></p>]]></description><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:eb81afc1c452a8cd2900aaabf1ff3bf2" t="1422648993" feed="200847" position="32"><title>Conan O'Brien, Marshawn Lynch, and Rob Gronkowski lose their minds over 'Mortal Kombat'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/conan-obrien-marshawn-lynch-and-rob-gronkowski-lose-their-minds-over-mortal</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/conan-mortal-kombat.jpg?itok=E8Rmh1Sd" t="image/jpeg" author="TBS">TBS</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">For a special Super Bowl edition of Conan O’Brien’s very funny Clueless Gamer segments, the late-night host convinced Marshawn Lynch of the Seattle Seahawks and Rob Gronkowski of the New England Patriots to face each other for a few matches of the yet-to-be-released </span><em style="line-height: 1.6em;">Mortal Kombat X</em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">. </span></p> <p><em>Mortal Kombat X</em>, however, is <em> incredibly </em>violent, and the three of them are completely unprepared for what the game has in store for them. It’s pretty intense—but absolutely worth it. </p> <p><span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;"></span></p> <iframe title="YouTube" class="youtube" width="612" height="345" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MNpkSyryQz4"> frameborder=”0” allowFullScreen&gt;</iframe><p></p> <p> </p>]]></description><author>Joshua Rivera</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:76cd23aeb4d22e66955f8be74b2e039c" t="1422626433" feed="200847" position="33"><title>Podcast: 'Clear Lists, Full Drafts, Can't Lose,' episode 19—Top 10 openings</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/clear-lists-pod-episode-19/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2014/10/clear-lists.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author="NBC">NBC</enclosure><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/brady-bunch-o.gif?w=301&amp;h=226" t="image/jpeg" author="NBC">NBC</enclosure><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/friends-opening-couch-credits.gif?w=385&amp;h=217" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;">Welcome to episode 19 of <em>Clear Lists, Full Drafts, Can’t Lose,</em> the only podcast for fantasy television drafts! Forget fantasy football—join us for fantasy TV.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">We have done a lot of top 10 lists on the podcast, and we’ve finally made our way to one of the first things you see when watching a show: the opening credits. This week, Brooke, Joey, and I count down our top 10 opening credits sequences. <span id="more-33747"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;"><a href="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/brady-bunch-o.gif"></a></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Opening credits can be a tough nut for a show to crack, sometimes coming off too cheesy or tonally different from the show. We discuss what makes a good opening credits sequence, what makes a bad one (looking at you, <em>The Affair</em>), and which ones we think will be considered some of the greats in TV history.</p> <img class=" wp-image-33750" src="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/friends-opening-couch-credits.gif?w=385&amp;h=217" alt="NBC" width="385" height="217" /> <p style="text-align:left;">Listen in as we harshly critique each other’s choices, and Joey and Brooke get in one of the bigger fights in podcast history. Let us know which credits are your favorites!</p> <p><br /> <audio class="wp-audio-shortcode" id="audio-33747-1" preload="none" style="width: 100%; visibility: hidden;" controls="controls"> <source type="audio/mpeg" src="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/episode-19-top-10-opening-credits.mp3?_=1"><a href="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/episode-19-top-10-opening-credits.mp3">https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/episode-19-top-10-opening-credits.mp3</a></source> </audio></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Mike Sorce</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a53ea0b889ab6ad7c10a441af39ffa51" t="1422594212" feed="200847" position="34"><title>'Elementary' fan recap: A dish best served cold</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/30/elementary-recap-one-that-got-away/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/105775_d0002b.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Season 3 | Episode 12 | “The</strong> <strong>One That Got Away” | Aired Jan. 29, 2015</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Throughout season three, and particularly in the last three weeks, <em>Elementary</em> has been building toward a showdown between Kitty Winter and the man who abducted, tortured, and raped her in London.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">We get that confrontation in this week’s episode, “The One That Got Away.” Holmes and Watson find the evidence needed to expose Del Gruner for the monster that he is, and Kitty says goodbye to Sherlock, her friend and mentor, after serving some cold, nutmeg-scented revenge to her attacker. <span id="more-33763"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;">The characters of Kitty Winter and Adelbert Gruner are lifted from Arthur Conan Doyle’s “The Adventure of the Illustrious Client.” In the original story, Gruner is permanently disfigured after Kitty throws vitriol, or sulfuric acid, in his face. The police are forced to bring charges against Kitty, but her sentence is reduced due to extenuating circumstances.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">In <em>Elementary</em>, Kitty was already in legal hot water after physically threatening Violet De Merville in last week’s episode. As for the vitriol, the <em>Elementary</em> writers cleverly introduced us to Kitty’s corrosive acid in episode seven. She whips up a batch of the nutmeg concoction used by that episode’s body-disposal expert, tests it on a steak, and then uses just enough on Gruner to leave him permanently scarred without killing him. As Holmes points out, the police have the evidence they need to put Gruner away.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">And that evidence, in a particularly diabolical twist, is that Gruner fathered a son with one of the women that he murdered. When looking through old case files, Sherlock initially rules out Francine Bianca as a possible Gruner victim because she had been held by her captor for almost a year. But after Watson confronts Gruner at a swanky charity event, and sees the way he reacts to a female colleague, Sherlock discovers the key to the case: the woman’s adopted son, who attends private school thanks to a scholarship overseen by Gruner. The boy’s DNA matches that of the murdered woman, and the NYPD are able to confirm that Gruner is the boy’s father after he is apprehended.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The solution comes just in time. Much like when Holmes thought he had found Irene Adler’s killer, Kitty follows Gruner to his apartment and ties him up in an abandoned warehouse where she plans to torture and kill him.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">“You’re going to die tonight quite horribly,” Kitty says. “And then I’m going to dissolve you in a sink.”</p> <p style="text-align:left;">She led Sherlock to believe she had returned to London in order to go on a mercenary rampage, but he sees through her ruse. After tracking her down via a phone-finder app, Sherlock tells Kitty that he’s been where she is and he won’t try to stop her. No matter what she chooses to do, he says he will still consider her his friend.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The police recover Gruner—or what’s left of him—and Captain Gregson makes it clear that he knows Kitty is responsible for his scarred state. Sherlock receives a call from Kitty, who has actually gone to the airport this time, and she says goodbye. She’s going somewhere she can use the skills that Sherlock taught her and help people.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">It’s an episode that brings an end to Kitty’s story while also providing glimpses of the beginning of her and Sherlock’s partnership. In flashbacks to their time in London, including their first meeting, we learn that Holmes was on the brink of a relapse—until teaching Kitty the art of deduction strengthened his resolve. And a look a predetective Kitty show us that much her work with Holmes helped her to move on from the crimes committed against her.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">“You say that I saved you,” Kitty tells Sherlock, “but the way that I see it, you gave me everything.”</p> <p style="text-align:left;">It will be interesting to see when, if at all, Kitty returns. There are still a lot of questions about what happened to Sherlock in London that could benefit from some more flashbacks. It took me some time to warm up to Kitty, but her presence will be missed. Sherlock told her that he remains at her disposal, so perhaps the <em>Elementary</em> writers will find a way for her to return.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">On the other hand, Sherlock is in need of a new partner, and Joan’s job at the insurance company is a bust. Perhaps Kitty leaving will be the catalyst that brings our detectives back together.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Stray Thought</strong></p> <ul style="text-align:left;"> <li>“Let go, or we’ll find out how you can do against a woman who can actually fight back.” You GO, Joan!</li> </ul> <ul style="text-align:left;"> <li>Am I the only one who feels cheated that the acid throwing happened off screen? I realize that it’s kind of dark, but there’s a part of me that really wanted to see Del Gruner screaming in pain.</li> </ul> <ul style="text-align:left;"> <li>Still no sign of Andrew from 6D. Worst. Relationship. Ever. And I say that as a man who has been in some truly terrible relationships.</li> </ul> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong><a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/elementary/">Elementary</a> <em>airs Thursdays at 10/9C on CBS.</em></strong></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Benjamin Wood</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630:summary" t="1422592298" feed="200847" position="35"><title>'The Hurt Locker, Part Two'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/glee-season-6-episode-5</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/glee.jpg?itok=QtNYy2xl" t="image/jpeg" author="Beth Dubber/Fox">Beth Dubber/Fox</enclosure><author>Lincee Ray</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><contents>urn:onebot:article:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630,urn:onebot:article:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630:269afc1d5cb14b419f8979772961b21a</contents></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630" t="1422592298" feed="200847" contained="1" count="1-2" position="35"><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/glee-season-6-episode-5</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/glee.jpg?itok=QtNYy2xl" t="image/jpeg" author="Beth Dubber/Fox">Beth Dubber/Fox</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>It’s time to dust off all those cassette tapes purchased for that one song you loved, because Glee is returning to its “old school” roots from season one. And by “roots,” I mean iconic songs from the ‘80s and ‘90s we all belt out when no one is looking. New Directions is back people. The magnificent seven pull out all the stops, forcing the Warblers and Vocal Adrenaline to shift uncomfortably in their seats, all contemplating this question: Do I have the same emotional triggers as Sue Sylvester? For the love of George Michael, I think I do.</p> <p>The episode opens with the Vocal Adrenaline team gasping for air. Having just finished their “Whip It” arrangement, the aerialists, dancers, and Clint (he has a name!) hustle to their seats to watch the others perform. Sue announces to the crowd that the Warblers will be performing the next day, followed by New Directions the day after. This change of plans freaks everyone out, except Rachel, who is happy to secure 48 additional hours to recruit members.</p> <p>Kurt convinces Rachel to go after Kitty, before heading to Breadsticks for a second date with Walter. Sue moonlights as a waitress, hurtling geriatric jokes with every breath. The solemn oath she took to reunite Klaine is still as much of a priority as sabotaging the Glee Club. When Walter takes her insults with a grain of salt, she resorts to harsher tactics—kidnapping.</p> <p>It’s a good thing Sue was able to acquire the materials needed to construct a fake elevator, because the next day, Blaine and Kurt fall victim to one of Sue’s creepiest shenanigans. Not only did she successfully lock the pair in a small confined space, but she mentally teases them with a disturbing Sue puppet on a tricycle that looks eerily like a distant cousin of Lady Elaine Fairchild. Puppet Sue warns Klaine that if they don’t make out like banshees, they will suffocate and die. Welcome to Ms. Sylvestor’s neighborhood.</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Meanwhile, the real Sue forces the Warblers to perform, even though their fearless leader is nowhere to be found. The boys straighten their navy blazers, channel the confidence of all Warblers who have gone before them, and nail their “My Sharona” number. In a hyphenated word, they are acca-awesome. When I heard the opening riffs of “You Spin Me Round,” I was a little disappointed, considering this song was brilliantly covered by The Treblemakers. Anything that is showcased on Pitch Perfect should not be touched, in my opinion.</span></p> <p>Another thing that shouldn’t be touched is the annoying hypnotizing storyline. Perhaps this was just a way for Glee writer Ian Brennan to share his opinion of the worst songs on the planet. I’m no expert, but “Justified and Ancient” was probably a huge hit in Mu Mu Land.</p> <p>Sam’s trance leads him to the choir room, where he tries to convince Rachel that “Dear Mr. Jesus,” “Ascension Millennium,” and the aforementioned KLF/Tammy Wynette ditty is just the setlist New Directions needs to take the invitational. Sam leans in for a kiss, but Rachel fends him off. YES! I know it trended on Twitter last week, but let’s not make Samchel a thing.</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Once Sam snaps out of his trance, Rachel asks him to help her find more students to fill the empty Glee Club slots. Sam heads straight to Spencer. Spencer tells him that he can’t afford to join New Directions because if the other football players “smell a little bit of gay on me, everything I worked for is ruined.”</span></p> <p>Time out. Doesn’t everyone know that Spencer is gay? Why did I get the impression that he would “take care” of anyone who had a problem with it? Discuss.</p> <p>Sam reminds Spencer of another great McKinley High quarterback who changed he tapestry of Glee Club forever. I think it’s lovely how the writers continue to pull Finn into each episode. I imagine Corey Monteith would be proud that his legacy lives on.</p> <p>Back in the choir room, Rachel is about to hyperventilate under the pressure, when a tart Cheerio waltzes in. While recruiting her earlier in the day, Rachel promised to never leave Kitty like the vanishing New Directions from season 4. Kitty loves a stage, and is ready to help Rachel find the perfect setlist. All she needs is a bobby pin to infiltrate Sue’s locked office door. Kitty knows that Sue has a secret playlist on her computer, full of emotional songs that have the ability to tug at her cold heart. Since Becky can be bribed with Mexican Twinkies, Kitty was able to secure the password—Thunderbolton69. How can a password be gross and awesome at the same time?</p> <p><strong>NEXT: Roderick is on center stage—finally</strong></p>]]></description><author>Lincee Ray</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:ba3d9a86545ed14c72eaacafe9fd3630:269afc1d5cb14b419f8979772961b21a" t="1422592298" feed="200847" contained="1" count="2-2" position="35"><title/><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/glee-season-6-episode-5</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>It’s time to dust off all those cassette tapes purchased for that one song you loved, because Glee is returning to its “old school” roots from season one. And by “roots,” I mean iconic songs from the ‘80s and ‘90s we all belt out when no one is looking. New Directions is back people. The magnificent seven pull out all the stops, forcing the Warblers and Vocal Adrenaline to shift uncomfortably in their seats, all contemplating this question: Do I have the same emotional triggers as Sue Sylvester? For the love of George Michael, I think I do.</p> <p>The episode opens with the Vocal Adrenaline team gasping for air. Having just finished their “Whip It” arrangement, the aerialists, dancers, and Clint (he has a name!) hustle to their seats to watch the others perform. Sue announces to the crowd that the Warblers will be performing the next day, followed by New Directions the day after. This change of plans freaks everyone out, except Rachel, who is happy to secure 48 additional hours to recruit members.</p> <p>Kurt convinces Rachel to go after Kitty, before heading to Breadsticks for a second date with Walter. Sue moonlights as a waitress, hurtling geriatric jokes with every breath. The solemn oath she took to reunite Klaine is still as much of a priority as sabotaging the Glee Club. When Walter takes her insults with a grain of salt, she resorts to harsher tactics—kidnapping.</p> <p>It’s a good thing Sue was able to acquire the materials needed to construct a fake elevator, because the next day, Blaine and Kurt fall victim to one of Sue’s creepiest shenanigans. Not only did she successfully lock the pair in a small confined space, but she mentally teases them with a disturbing Sue puppet on a tricycle that looks eerily like a distant cousin of Lady Elaine Fairchild. Puppet Sue warns Klaine that if they don’t make out like banshees, they will suffocate and die. Welcome to Ms. Sylvestor’s neighborhood.</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Meanwhile, the real Sue forces the Warblers to perform, even though their fearless leader is nowhere to be found. The boys straighten their navy blazers, channel the confidence of all Warblers who have gone before them, and nail their “My Sharona” number. In a hyphenated word, they are acca-awesome. When I heard the opening riffs of “You Spin Me Round,” I was a little disappointed, considering this song was brilliantly covered by The Treblemakers. Anything that is showcased on Pitch Perfect should not be touched, in my opinion.</span></p> <p>Another thing that shouldn’t be touched is the annoying hypnotizing storyline. Perhaps this was just a way for Glee writer Ian Brennan to share his opinion of the worst songs on the planet. I’m no expert, but “Justified and Ancient” was probably a huge hit in Mu Mu Land.</p> <p>Sam’s trance leads him to the choir room, where he tries to convince Rachel that “Dear Mr. Jesus,” “Ascension Millennium,” and the aforementioned KLF/Tammy Wynette ditty is just the setlist New Directions needs to take the invitational. Sam leans in for a kiss, but Rachel fends him off. YES! I know it trended on Twitter last week, but let’s not make Samchel a thing.</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Once Sam snaps out of his trance, Rachel asks him to help her find more students to fill the empty Glee Club slots. Sam heads straight to Spencer. Spencer tells him that he can’t afford to join New Directions because if the other football players “smell a little bit of gay on me, everything I worked for is ruined.”</span></p> <p>Time out. Doesn’t everyone know that Spencer is gay? Why did I get the impression that he would “take care” of anyone who had a problem with it? Discuss.</p> <p>Sam reminds Spencer of another great McKinley High quarterback who changed he tapestry of Glee Club forever. I think it’s lovely how the writers continue to pull Finn into each episode. I imagine Corey Monteith would be proud that his legacy lives on.</p> <p>Back in the choir room, Rachel is about to hyperventilate under the pressure, when a tart Cheerio waltzes in. While recruiting her earlier in the day, Rachel promised to never leave Kitty like the vanishing New Directions from season 4. Kitty loves a stage, and is ready to help Rachel find the perfect setlist. All she needs is a bobby pin to infiltrate Sue’s locked office door. Kitty knows that Sue has a secret playlist on her computer, full of emotional songs that have the ability to tug at her cold heart. Since Becky can be bribed with Mexican Twinkies, Kitty was able to secure the password—Thunderbolton69. How can a password be gross and awesome at the same time?</p> <p><strong>NEXT: Roderick is on center stage—finally</strong></p>]]></description><author>Lincee Ray</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:b0a93faabb8347b8a43fbd811f43fc5d" t="1422592281" feed="200847" position="36"><title>Casting Net: James Franco to direct, star in Steinbeck adapation 'In Dubious Battle'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/casting-net-james-franco-star-steinback-adaptation-dubious-battle</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/06/10/James-Franco_612x380.jpg?itok=-D0XVm9a" t="image/jpeg" author="Jon Kopaloff/FilmMagic">Jon Kopaloff/FilmMagic</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><ul> <li><strong>James Franco</strong> will be starring in his adaptation of John Steinbeck’s <em>In Dubious Battle. </em>The film, which tells the story of a man who tried to organize a fruit picker strike in Southern California, will star <strong> Selena Gomez</strong>, <strong>Vincent D’Onofrio</strong>, <strong>Robert Duvall</strong>, <strong>Ed Harris</strong>, <strong>Bryan Cranston</strong>, and <strong>Danny McBride</strong>. Principal photography begins in March. [ <a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-james-franco-leads-ensemble-768599">The Hollywood Reporter</a>]</li> <li><strong>Tatiana Maslany</strong> ( <em>Orphan Black</em>) and <strong>Dane DeHaan </strong>( <em>Chronicle</em>) have signed on to star in the indie drama <em>Two Lovers and a Bear</em>. The film is set in a small town near the North Pole where the roads lead to nowhere, where Roman (DeHaan) and Lucy (Maslany) “come together to make a leap for life and inner peace.” Production is scheduled to begin in mid-March. [ <a href="http://www.thewrap.com/tatiana-maslany-dane-dehaan-to-star-in-indie-drama-two-lovers-and-a-bear-exclusive/">TheWrap</a>]</li> <li><strong>Jamie Foxx </strong>and <strong>Michelle Monaghan</strong> will be starring in the Open Roads action thriller <em> Sleepless Night. </em>The film revolves around Vincent Downs (Foxx), a seemingly corrupt Las Vegas cop, whose son is kidnapped by gangsters as ransom for a shipment of cocaine he has stolen. Monaghan plays officer Jennifer Bryant, an Interal Affairs agent investigating Downs.</li> <li>Directors <strong>Andrew Mogel</strong> and <strong>Jarrad Paul </strong>are planning to adapt the  <em>Wired</em> magazine article “Finding a Vegas Poker Bug Made These Guys Rich—Then Vegas Made Them Pay.” <strong>Jonah Hill</strong> is executive producing the film about two hackers who found a glitch in video poker machines which they used to win almost $1 million. [ <a href="http://variety.com/2015/film/news/jonah-hill-d-train-filmmakers-to-adapt-wired-magazine-article-on-vegas-hackers-exclusive-1201418860/">Variety</a>]</li> <li><strong>Frances McDormand</strong>, <strong>Logan Lerman</strong>, <strong>Brit Marling</strong>, <strong>Christian Slater</strong>, and <strong>Jonathan Pryce</strong> have all joined the cast of  <em>The Wife, </em>starring <strong>Glenn Close</strong>. Close plays a flawlessly gracious wife who gives up her writing ambitions for her husband, aphilandering literary giant (Pryce). A startling secret at the heart of their relationship is presented in a “poignant, funny, and emotional journey about the conflicts of love and ambition.” [ <a href="http://variety.com/2015/film/news/berlin-frances-mcdormand-brit-marling-christian-slater-join-the-wife-1201419434/">Variety</a>]</li> <li><strong>Elijah Wood</strong> and <strong>Nicolas Cage</strong> will be teaming up for the cop thriller <em>The Trust</em>. Cage and Wood play crooked cops who discover a hidden safe while working in evidence in the police department. When they try to leave with the contents, “They are faced with even more corruption that leaves them fighting for their lives and questioning their every move.” Production has just begun in Las Vegas. [ <em><a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/elijah-wood-joins-nicolas-cage-768671">The Hollywood Reporter</a></em>]</li> <li><strong>Elle Fanning</strong> and <strong>Diego Luna </strong>will join the cast of the sci-fi film <em>IO.</em> The film, developed at the Sundance Insitute’s Writers Lab, is slated to begin production sometime this year. Fanning will play a teen survivor of a post-cataclyscmic Earth, who is looking to find a cure for her poisoned world before the last shuttle leaving the planet leaves her stranded. Luna will play a complicated refugee on his way to the shuttle launch who makes her question Earth’s fate. [ <a href="http://deadline.com/2015/01/elle-fanning-diego-luna-io-sci-fi-movie-casting-1201363233/">Deadline</a>]</li> <li><strong>Nick Cannon</strong> will direct the independent romantic comedy,  <em>Three Little Words.</em> The film, currently in pre-production, is the story of a group dealing with various romances as they try to say the words “I love you.” [ <a href="http://variety.com/2015/film/news/berlin-nick-cannon-directing-romance-three-little-words-1201419518/">Variety</a>]</li> <li><strong>Zoe Graham</strong> ( <em>Boyhood</em>) has joined the remake of the Argentine thriller  <em>The Secret In Their Eyes</em>. She will play the daughter of Julia Roberts’ character, in a story that centers around a retired criminal investigator who writes a mystery novel in order to deal with one of his unsolved cases. [ <a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-boyhood-actress-joins-secret-768717">The Hollywood Reporter</a>]</li> <li><strong>Katie Holmes </strong>and <strong>Evan Rachel Wood</strong> will join <strong>Zosia Mamet</strong> for  <em>Taxonomy</em>, the upcoming comedy which will see the three play sisters living together in an enormous New York apartment. <strong>Alan Rickman</strong> is set to direct and production will begin this spring. [ <a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-katie-holmes-evan-rachel-768565">The Hollywood Reporter</a>]</li> </ul></p>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797:summary" t="1422591302" feed="200847" position="37"><title>'Cassandra Complex'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/12-monkeys-season-1-episode-3</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/nup_164914_0341.jpg?itok=ZWga8dfA" t="image/jpeg" author="Ben Mark Holzberg/Syfy">OUT OF TIME Cole is pulled back and forth through time as he hunts for the night room. (Ben Mark Holzberg/Syfy)</enclosure><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><contents>urn:onebot:article:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797,urn:onebot:article:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797:d4b4eee37a094c4fe8720fd96d54b0b3</contents></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797" t="1422591302" feed="200847" contained="1" count="1-2" position="37"><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/12-monkeys-season-1-episode-3</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/nup_164914_0341.jpg?itok=ZWga8dfA" t="image/jpeg" author="Ben Mark Holzberg/Syfy">OUT OF TIME Cole is pulled back and forth through time as he hunts for the night room. (Ben Mark Holzberg/Syfy)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>As the title suggests, “Cassandra Complex” is all about the non-time-traveling half of the main duo in  <em>12 Monkeys</em>. The show has paid plenty of lip service to the professional and personal disarray in Cassie’s life following her first run in with Cole in 2005. “Complex” actually takes a look at that phase of her life, specifically during a trip Haiti in 2014.</p> <p>As fate would have it, Haiti is also the location of the only other person other than Jennifer Goines who knows the location of the night room. So while some time is given to exploring Cassie’s state of mind, a task to which Amanda Schull more than lives up, she has to share the spotlight with the fate of mankind.</p> <p>“Complex” opens with the titular character pointing a gun at her partner in time-traveling crime, Cole. The firearm is stocked with blanks, of course—this is just target practice, so Cassie can prepare herself for the duo’s next run-in with the Army of the 12 Monkeys. Training is cut short when the police call Cassie in to discuss the kidnapping of Jennifer in “Mentally Divergent.” The cops show Cassie a picture of Jennifer at work with the team in her father’s lab, which includes the one other person who escaped the 12 Monkeys. There’s a hint of recognition, so she snaps a photo and takes it to Cole.</p> <p>Cassie explains that she worked with the man, a doctor named Henri Toussaint (Lyriq Bent), for a few days in Haiti during a stint assisting the Center for Disease Control and Prevention. Unfortunately, after checking in with another doctor from the CDC, Jules (Jeff Clarke), she learns Henri died there, shot on a search for extra medicine.</p> <p>This trip to the CDC is the first in a series of trying moments for Cassie throughout the episode. Not only does she have to face the CDC headquarters, the building in which she knows she’ll die, but she also blames herself for the death of Henri, having sent him on the search. Schull admirably navigates Cassie and the audience through the mixture of troubling emotions, including when Cole goes against her wishes to travel back to 2014 and talk to Henri himself. </p> <p>Cole confirms his plans with the scientists in 2043, though Jones warns him that solar flares in 2014 will cause some temporal interference. What that exactly translates into… well, she’s not sure, but she wants him on alert for that and to avoid Cassie for fear of fracturing his and her timelines. “Got it. We cross paths, it could kill me,” he replies before jumping back to 2014.</p> <p>But he isn’t the only one destined to have a rough 2014. Cassie argues with her on-again-off-again boyfriend Aaron about going to Haiti—if this is  <em>the</em> virus, she’s the only one in 2014 who would know anything about it.</p> <p>Upon her arrival, she fears the illness sweeping the island could well be the virus she fears. Jules informs her there are too many possible suspects to nail the virus down. She wants to lock the place down for fear of it spreading, but Jules isn’t ready to make that call. In the meantime, she meets Henri, protecting him from a gun-toting man demanding medical attention.</p> <p>Their initial bond after this moment changes from professional to personal, as the two commiserate about fighting the disease later that evening in their hotel. Throw in a little alcohol, some mood lighting, and two attractive people, and by the laws of television, the two have to shack up together for the night. Cole appears in Haiti that same night to begin his reconnaissance.</p> <p>Cole spends the next day keeping tabs on Henri, dealing with the occasional temporal interference. Jones’ concerns seem unnecessary, though—Cole merely glitches in and out of time for a few seconds and sports a subsequent nosebleed. He follows Henri through a few alleyways, but is distracted by a shrine with the sculpture of a screaming monkey head. Before he can investigate it, Henri attacks him, suspecting Cole actually belongs to the Army. The time-traveling hero talks him down—stealing Henri’s gun to ensure his safety—and asks for information about the night room. Henri promises he’ll tell Cole, but only after he delivers the medicine.</p> <p><strong>NEXT: Trouble’s brewing in 2043.</strong></p>]]></description><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:befd0960ab33c2ab60759fe7c2b03797:d4b4eee37a094c4fe8720fd96d54b0b3" t="1422591302" feed="200847" contained="1" count="2-2" position="37"><title/><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/12-monkeys-season-1-episode-3</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>As the title suggests, “Cassandra Complex” is all about the non-time-traveling half of the main duo in  <em>12 Monkeys</em>. The show has paid plenty of lip service to the professional and personal disarray in Cassie’s life following her first run in with Cole in 2005. “Complex” actually takes a look at that phase of her life, specifically during a trip Haiti in 2014.</p> <p>As fate would have it, Haiti is also the location of the only other person other than Jennifer Goines who knows the location of the night room. So while some time is given to exploring Cassie’s state of mind, a task to which Amanda Schull more than lives up, she has to share the spotlight with the fate of mankind.</p> <p>“Complex” opens with the titular character pointing a gun at her partner in time-traveling crime, Cole. The firearm is stocked with blanks, of course—this is just target practice, so Cassie can prepare herself for the duo’s next run-in with the Army of the 12 Monkeys. Training is cut short when the police call Cassie in to discuss the kidnapping of Jennifer in “Mentally Divergent.” The cops show Cassie a picture of Jennifer at work with the team in her father’s lab, which includes the one other person who escaped the 12 Monkeys. There’s a hint of recognition, so she snaps a photo and takes it to Cole.</p> <p>Cassie explains that she worked with the man, a doctor named Henri Toussaint (Lyriq Bent), for a few days in Haiti during a stint assisting the Center for Disease Control and Prevention. Unfortunately, after checking in with another doctor from the CDC, Jules (Jeff Clarke), she learns Henri died there, shot on a search for extra medicine.</p> <p>This trip to the CDC is the first in a series of trying moments for Cassie throughout the episode. Not only does she have to face the CDC headquarters, the building in which she knows she’ll die, but she also blames herself for the death of Henri, having sent him on the search. Schull admirably navigates Cassie and the audience through the mixture of troubling emotions, including when Cole goes against her wishes to travel back to 2014 and talk to Henri himself. </p> <p>Cole confirms his plans with the scientists in 2043, though Jones warns him that solar flares in 2014 will cause some temporal interference. What that exactly translates into… well, she’s not sure, but she wants him on alert for that and to avoid Cassie for fear of fracturing his and her timelines. “Got it. We cross paths, it could kill me,” he replies before jumping back to 2014.</p> <p>But he isn’t the only one destined to have a rough 2014. Cassie argues with her on-again-off-again boyfriend Aaron about going to Haiti—if this is  <em>the</em> virus, she’s the only one in 2014 who would know anything about it.</p> <p>Upon her arrival, she fears the illness sweeping the island could well be the virus she fears. Jules informs her there are too many possible suspects to nail the virus down. She wants to lock the place down for fear of it spreading, but Jules isn’t ready to make that call. In the meantime, she meets Henri, protecting him from a gun-toting man demanding medical attention.</p> <p>Their initial bond after this moment changes from professional to personal, as the two commiserate about fighting the disease later that evening in their hotel. Throw in a little alcohol, some mood lighting, and two attractive people, and by the laws of television, the two have to shack up together for the night. Cole appears in Haiti that same night to begin his reconnaissance.</p> <p>Cole spends the next day keeping tabs on Henri, dealing with the occasional temporal interference. Jones’ concerns seem unnecessary, though—Cole merely glitches in and out of time for a few seconds and sports a subsequent nosebleed. He follows Henri through a few alleyways, but is distracted by a shrine with the sculpture of a screaming monkey head. Before he can investigate it, Henri attacks him, suspecting Cole actually belongs to the Army. The time-traveling hero talks him down—stealing Henri’s gun to ensure his safety—and asks for information about the night room. Henri promises he’ll tell Cole, but only after he delivers the medicine.</p> <p><strong>NEXT: Trouble’s brewing in 2043.</strong></p>]]></description><author>Jonathon Dornbush</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:23e38d6cb8a71b3013e351809e0c8f2c" t="1422589718" feed="200847" position="38"><title>'Mom' react: Instead, I'll say g'day</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/29/kitty-litter-and-a-class-a-felony/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/mom1.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/mom3.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Season 2 | Episode 12 | “Kitty Litter and a Class A Felony” | Aired Jan 29, 2015</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">EW Community contributors are chatting about each new episode of <em style="background-color:initial;">Mom</em> this season. This week, Julia Alexander and Sundi Rose-Holt (sadly without Tamar Barbash) are working through the aftermath of Alvin’s death in “Kitty Litter and a Class A Felony.”</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong style="background-color:initial;">Sundi:</strong> The tone of tonight’s show was considerably lighter, which I appreciated.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I think it was exactly what they needed after last week’s dramatic episode. Do you think they got back to the main story well enough? You know, after Alvin? <span id="more-33759"></span></p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> I like how the writers are still lingering on Bonnie and Christy’s grief, but they are allowing us room to laugh at it. I don’t know if I totally agree with the first step in grieving Alvin being about money. It feels a little cheap. Although, I didn’t expect an inheritance storyline.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I didn’t either, but I thought it was kind of the perfect subplot considering the overall financial tone of the show. And like you said, the comedy seemed to really work. They didn’t just leave the death as a onetime episode and expect us to move on. They let us register that this man who was so important to both of them is gone, and it’s okay to laugh.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> I am afraid it’s going to be a magic wand. I don’t want the money to just magically solve all of the subtext that drives the show. What will Christy’s life look like with money? Remember, it wasn’t that long ago that the whole family was holed up in a ratty motel ducking gunfire. And we loved it.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I was kind of hoping that it would turn out the money was fraudulent, and they weren’t entitled to anything. I don’t think their spontaneous wealth will sustain a major change in the show’s tone for very long. Do you?</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> I fear something terrible is going to happen, and they’ll lose it all. They might deserve it after that “dead-dad-vagina” bit. It was too much, and they knew it. I had to laugh at the writers’ self-awareness, though. They had to know we were going to giggle with our tongues in our cheeks.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> The comedy did feel a little over the top tonight, but I wonder if that was a calculated decision. The comedy has been lacking in the past couple of episodes, while the drama has been increasing. It is really refreshing to have some actual laugh-out-loud moments that I feel instantly guilty about.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> I agree. The volume on the schtick was dialed way up tonight, and I have to think that was on purpose. The scene with Bonnie and Marjorie—come on. That’s pretty funny; Allison Janney, all red-faced, with veins bulging, yelling at her passive, sweet friend. Classic.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"></p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I love how much they work with Allison Janney’s body. She’s got so much physical comedy potential, and they know how to make it work in each scene. It cracks me up every time.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> She does the physical comedy so well, and the differing physicality between her and Christy is as much part of the joke as anything.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> Instead of ignoring their physical traits, they use them to make every scene better. It’s something not many directors and writers do with their actors, and I really appreciate the extra effort.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> Speaking of hilarious pairings, I really enjoy all the scenes with Bonnie and Lorraine. I adore the burgeoning feud that is happening. It’s could be so, so good.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> Yes! And Lorraine is quickly becoming one of my favorite characters whom I love to hate.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> I hope (times a million) that we get more of Alvin’s family, particularly the brothers. The brother Jackie is a standout. He is endearing, and I love a good nerd trope.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> It’s nice to see another family come into the fold instead of just group members, random friends, and terrible dates. I feel like we’re going to see a whole new side to Christy that we haven’t yet.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> The show might be on the verge of real change. The sibling dynamic has a lot of potential, and I really want to see them develop it. I like seeing Jackie and Christy interact, and I think it’s going to be fun to see Christy open up to a male character, in a nonsexual way.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I definitely agree about Christy having that male connection. I think she needs it now more than ever since Alvin is gone.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> What were your high points tonight?</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Julia:</strong> I like that they’re keeping Alvin alive without actually keeping him alive. I think having this extended family could be a great way to keep the dramatic undertones while making sure it’s still funny week after week. You?</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sundi:</strong> The brothers … hands down. They are so supercute, and seeing Christy try to process having another family is so interesting. I am rooting for her little family so hard.</p> <p dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;">What about y’all? What did you love about tonight’s episode?</p> <p class="align center" style="text-align:left;"><strong><em>Note:</em></strong> <em>Contributor Tamar Barbash will rejoin the</em> Mom <em>react crew next week.</em></p> <p class="align center" style="text-align:left;"><strong><a href="http://www.cbs.com/shows/mom/">Mom</a></strong> <em><strong>airs Thursdays at 8:30/7:30C on CBS.</strong></em></p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Sundi Rose-Holt</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:22f9c0dee82aec3f3f6ea12d5a11175c" t="1422587796" feed="200847" position="39"><title>Gorillaz creator confirms group's return on Instagram</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/gorillaz-creator-confirms-groups-return-instagram</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2012/02/08/Gorillaz_2011_510_0.jpg?itok=qZphrWbP" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">Jamie Hewlett,</span><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> artist behind the animated band Gorillaz, confirmed on Friday that the group would be reuniting.</span></p> <p>For the past few months, Hewlett’s co-creator, Damon Albarn, had been hinting at a reunion, but it wasn’t confirmed until Hewlett posted artwork of the animated band members, Murdoc and Noodle, on his Instagram.</p> <p>After a fan’s question regarding whether this signified a reunion, Hewlett answered, “Yes Gorillaz Returns.”</p> <p> </p>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e528d0b65c237023d1bd880c5db174ab" t="1422587612" feed="200847" position="40"><title>'Freaks and Geeks' pilot fan recap: Come sail away</title><link>http://community.ew.com/2015/01/29/freaks-geeks-pilot/</link><enclosure u="https://ewvox.files.wordpress.com/2015/01/freaksandgeeks1x1.jpg?w=612&amp;h=380&amp;crop=1" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Season 1 | Episode 1 | “Pilot” | Aired Sep 25, 1999</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Somehow in my ever-constant TV binging, I never took the time to sit down with <em>Freaks and Geeks</em>. The cult high school show lasted a single season, but it was basically a casting call for all future Judd Apatow stars. Here I am, though, to make amends and to recap all 18 glorious episodes. For those who have watched and for those newbies like me, let’s get started! <span id="more-33753"></span></p> <p style="text-align:left;">The pilot opens, and we quickly get a run-through of the social classes at William McKinley High School, circa 1980. First up, there’s a jock and cheerleader, our obvious popular kids, making out in the bleachers. Then the camera pans below, and the soundtrack promptly changes to rock music, the best way to introduce our resident freaks, Daniel (James Franco), Nick (Jason Segel), and Ken (Seth Rogen). The star of the show, straight-A student, army-jacket-wearing Lindsay Weir (Linda Cardellini), watches them from nearby. Symbolically, she waits at the edge of the bleachers, not belonging to the freaks, but not belonging anywhere else either.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Our geeks are the last to appear, doing their best impressions of Bill Murray until a bully declares, “Bill Murray sucks,” and begins to threaten them. (Side note: Has anyone ever truly said that? Come on, he’s Bill Murray!) The smallest geek of the three, Sam (John Francis Daley) is practically pocket-size and thus the easiest target. But his big sister, Lindsay, comes in to save the day, telling the bully to pick on someone more than 100 pounds.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Sam, for obvious reasons, is embarrassed. “By the way, I weigh 103 pounds,” he says.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">“Man, I hate high school,” says Lindsay, repeating a sentiment felt by most of mankind.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Welcome to <em>Freaks and Geeks</em>, folks.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">This week’s biggest issues revolve around the upcoming homecoming dance and Sam’s bully. Neither of their parents can understand why Lindsay and Sam don’t want to go to the dance. School is about socializing, too, the parents complain. Kids these days, right?</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Lindsay doesn’t want to go to the dance, because who would she go with? When she broaches the idea to the freaks, they laugh. It’s nothing but lame disco music, and Ken has a prior arrangement with some mushrooms (Seth Rogen is still Seth Rogen, it seems). Lindsay’s other option is her geeky friend Millie (Sarah Hagan), who’s currently scandalized about Lindsay starting to hang out with the freaks. That, and Lindsay hasn’t signed up for the academic decathlon yet. Lindsay does her best to quiet Millie and any mentions of her mathlete status.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Kim (Busy Philipps), our resident lady member of the freaks, isn’t pleased with Lindsay moving in on her turf. She denounces Lindsay as a rich kid trying to piss off her parents, and empties her purse out in the school hallway.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">But Lindsay gets her bully-beating mojo back when she defends Eli (Ben Foster), a mentally disabled kid who gets teased mercilessly at school. In front of his bullies, Lindsay asks him to the homecoming dance. This later backfires when she tries defending him against more tormentors and accidentally calls him “retarded” in the process. He breaks his arm trying to run away from her, so that’s not too good. Her school guidance counselor, the super hippie Mr. Jeff Rosso (Dave Allen), can’t understand what’s going on with her. But like Millie, he’s mostly concerned she hasn’t joined the mathletes.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">This leads to Lindsay cutting class with Nick, the nicest of the freaks. He shows her his beloved 29-piece drum set and tells her she needs to find her passion, too. He even works out a plan to take Lindsay to the dance (honoring her parents’ wishes) but then split early and hang out together (honoring their wishes). For a half-second, things seem to be working out. But then Mr. Rosso catches them playing hooky, and Lindsay is now forced to work the homecoming dance refreshment table.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Meanwhile, little Sam needs to figure out a way to ask his crush Cindy Sanders (Natasha Melnick) to the dance. She’s nice to him, but she’s also a popular cheerleader and a good foot taller than him, so the odds look slim. First, though, he needs to stop Alan the bully, who harasses him constantly, crushes his Twinkies at lunch, and constantly Hulk-smashes various lockers.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">So far, Sam hasn’t been getting great advice. Mr. Kowchevski tells him to man up, and his best friend Neal (Samm Levine) suggests avoiding Alan like Han Solo does to Jabba the Hutt. There’s no way for the geeks to avoid Alan, though, and even their gym teacher seems to be against them when he announces a game of dodgeball in class. It’s a massacre for our various geeks, including some significant hits to Bill (Martin Starr) that might impair his ability to have children one day. Miraculously, Sam beats Alan in dodgeball, but this doesn’t exactly help things.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">“You just signed your death warrant,” says Alan, drawing from his extensive list of bully threat cliches.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">Sam, Bill, and Neal eventually seek advice from the upperclassman geek Harris (Stephen Lea Sheppard), who, despite an unfortunate wispy mustache, has wise advice to share. He suggests the Cressman conundrum: If they go ahead and fight Adam, he should then leave them alone. That, at least, was the case with Harris’ former bully, Tom Cressman. “He broke my tailbone, but the results were effective,” says Harris. “He got expelled,” explains Harris’ friend.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">The boys agree to this. The stage is set. “Renegade” by Styx plays as Bill and Neal dramatically walk down an empty street to meet the terrible Alan. Unfortunately, Sam is late when he gets distracted by Cindy and asks her to the dance. Cindy, predictably, already has a date, but she promises a slow dance with him.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">This awkward interaction is intercut with the epic clash between Bill, Neal, and Alan. It’s what you would expect of three pubescent geeks doing their best not to die. In the end, Bill and Neal survive and walk away, extolling each of their heroic fighting moves. Sam catches up and is genuinely happy his friends stood up for him.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">At last, we make it to the dance, and despite the week’s dilemmas, things work out for well for the Weir clan. Sam indeed gets his dance with Cindy, and after initially watching the dance from a distance, Lindsay joins the festivities and makes amends with Eli by apologizing and dancing with him. Another Styx song, “Come Sail Away,” triumphantly plays.</p> <p style="text-align:left;">It’s a great first episode and a refreshing change of pace from the usual teen dramas where schools are populated by abnormally good-looking 30-year-olds.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>NOTABLES</strong></p> <p style="text-align:left;">Papa Weir follows a very specific approach to parenting/teen guidance: If you do something bad, no matter what it is, you will die. A similar method can be seen from Coach Carr in <em>Mean Girls</em>: “Don’t have sex. Because you will get pregnant. And die.”</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Nick</strong>: “You need to find your reason for living. You’ve got to find your big gigantic drum kit.” A true poet on carpe diem, that Nick.</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Bill</strong>, wearing tiny green gym shorts: “These shorts aren’t very flattering, are they?”</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Sam</strong>, somewhat unconvincingly: “Nah, you look good.”</p> <p style="text-align:left;"><strong>Bill</strong>: “Thanks.” Such good buds.</p> <p></p> <div style="clear: both;"></div> <div style="clear: both;"></div></p>]]></description><author>Caroline Reinwald</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d5e70e7797a8f11ba51566620eb148e8" t="1422578788" feed="200847" position="41"><title>Sundance 2015: The 5 best films we saw</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/30/sundance-2015-5-best-films-we-saw</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/b8mi0ntimaakflx.png-large.png?itok=k7uO2LWT" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>I’ve been covering the Sundance Film Festival on and off for the past 15 years. During that time, I’ve had an aisle seatto watch the rise and fall and rise of the independent film movement, I’ve been forced to check under the bed in my hotel room after returning from the first midnight screening of <em>The Blair Witch Project</em>, I’ve had my mind scrambled by a young filmmaker named Christopher Nolan ( <em>Memento</em>), and most recently, I’ve been knocked out by what eventually would become my two favorite films of last year, <em>Whiplash</em> and <em>Boyhood</em>.</p> <p>This year’s festival was no different. There were movies to make your heart swell, movies to make your brain swirl, and movies that left you haunted with cold sweats and night terrors. In short, there was no shortage of films that I look forward to writing about and revisiting until I return to Park City, Utah, next year. So without any further blather, here are the five best things I saw at Sundance 2015…</p> <p></p> <p><strong><em>Kurt Cobain: A Montage of Heck</em> </strong>This year’s edition of the festival hosted no fewer than 118 features. Like anyone else, I only managed to see a fraction of those. But without question the best one I saw was Brett Morgen’s documentary bio of the live-fast-die-young grunge godhead and Nirvana frontman, <em>Kurt Cobain: A Montage of Heck</em>. Morgen, who bowled me over with his rollicking 2002 Sundance documentary about legendarily leathery Hollywood producer Robert Evans, <em>The Kid Stays in the Picture</em>, confirmed why he’s one of the non-fiction genre’s most talented filmmakers. Normally, I’m skeptical when a documentarian gets into bed with his subject as Morgen did here (he had the full cooperation of Cobain’s family, Courtney Love, and his daughter Frances Bean). But in this case, that cozy relationship allowed him to have full access to Cobain’s childhood home movies and his journals. The result is a portrait that’s at turns confessional, confused, and yes, even at times happy, that bring Cobain—a man who’s snowballed into myth since his 1994 suicide—to life in a way that no other film or book has. We finally get to see the man instead of the myth. And, it goes without saying, the music is amazing.     </p> <p> </p> <p><strong><em>It Follows</em></strong> “Park City at Midnight” has always been one of my favorite sections of the festival. It’s where real genre-hounds can get their late-night rocks off after a day of submersing oneself in Sundance’s more earnest and self-serious smorgasbord. There was a lot of buzz this year around Rodney Ascher’s <em>The Nightmare</em>, but unfortunately I didn’t get a chance to catch up with it. I’ll have to wait until it comes to lower altitudes. One of the midnight movies I did catch and really, really dug was David Robert Mitchell’s <em>It Follows</em>. The film is actually being released nationally in March, so I’ll have more to say about it when the time comes. But for now, I’ll just suggest that Mitchell’s atmospheric chiller feels like the kind of movie John Carpenter might have made somewhere between <em>Halloween</em> and <em>The Thing</em>. It’s smart, original, rich with allegory, and has a handful of white-knuckle scares that will creep you out long after you see it. Horror fans have known for decades that teens having sex were lining up for the bodycount, but Mitchell takes that trope and it gives it a smart new twist.  </p> <p><img alt="text" src="https://editor.ew.com/sites/default/files/i/2015/01/20/Dope_0.jpg" /></p> <p><strong><em>Dope</em></strong> If you cross-pollinate <em>Yo! MTV Raps</em> and <em>Risky Business</em>, you might end up with something like Rick Famuyiwa’s inner-city coming of age caper, <em>Dope</em>. Shameik Moore stars as Malcolm, an awkward high-school brainiac who lives in the Inglewood section of L.A. and who’s obsessed with old-school hip-hop. His high-top fade haircut says <em>House Party</em>, but Famuyiwa’s comedy has more on its mind than Kid n’ Play. Narrated by Forrest Whitaker (who’s also one of the film’s producers), the movie kicks into giddy gear when Malcolm and his two best friends (Kiersey Clemons and <em>The Grand Budapest Hotel</em>’s Tony Revolori) get swept into a drug deal gone sour. During a shootout at a club, a local dealer puts his stash into Malcolm’s backpack and now he has to figure out how to unload the goods without jeopardizing his dreams of going to Harvard‑or, at the very least, getting killed. The movie has a real rat-a-tat energy, the retro details are spot-on, and the movie has real style. </p> <p><em>Dope</em> isn’t perfect. It could really use a smart editor to whip some of its shaggier narrative cul de sacs into shape. But it’s smart and it’s got heart and leaves you with an itch to do the Humpty Dance. And how many movies can you say that about?  </p> <p><strong>Jason Segel in <em>The End of the Tour</em></strong> Better known as “The David Foster Wallace movie”, <em>The End of the Tour</em> isn’t a perfect film by any stretch. But it made me see the tall drink of Apatovian water, Jason Segel, in a new light. He’s not just a comedian and a Muppet aficionado. The dude’s a real actor. Directed by James Ponsoldt ( <em>The Spectacular Now</em>), the film chronicles the prickly and poignant relationship between the genius novelist David Foster Wallace (Segel) and <em>Rolling Stone</em> reporter David Lipsky (Jesse Eisenberg) when he went to interview the author for a 1996 magazine profile during the release of his magnum opus, <em>Infinite Jest</em>. The two men are equally insecure and proud in their own ways, and the reporter/subject dynamic gets a real workout and has the ring of truth (at least to this occasional celebrity profiler).</p> <p>I suspect that the movie doesn’t dig deep enough to get at the real Wallace and probably oversimplifies what made him tick and I’m getting a little numb to Eisenberg playing Eisenberg over and over again. But, like the much better but similarly themed <em>Almost Famous</em>, the film is a vehicle for a real headturning turn. In that case it was Kate Hudson. Here, it’s Segel. At first, his performance as Wallace feels like bandana-festooned mimicry. A collection of tics. But he slowly melts into the character and his intelligence comes through loud and clear. I couldn’t take my eyes off of him.        </p> <p><img alt="text" src="https://editor.ew.com/sites/default/files/i/2015/01/16/THE-OVERNIGHT-01_0.jpg" /></p> <p>* <strong>The Return of the Adult Sex Comedy</strong> Although this year’s opening night movie, Bryan Buckley’s <em>The Bronze</em>, was a mixed bag and a remains a bit of a question mark for why it landed that coveted slot, it did contain one of the festival’s most memorable—and acrobatic—scenes. A ridiculously vigorous, raunchy, and bendy sex scene between two gymnasts played by <em>The Big Bang Theory</em>’s Melissa Rauch and Sebastian Stan. It was like the boot-knocking scene in <em>Team America: World Police</em>, but with real people instead of marionettes. It wasn’t the only film to stick its piggy toe into the hard-R grotto of a long-lost genre known as The Adult Sex Comedy. In addition to <em>The Bronze</em>, there were two other films I caught that allowed adults to act like the prurient, pubescent peeping toms from <em>Porky’s</em>. The better of the two was Patrick Brice’s The Overnight, which stars Adam Scott and Taylor Schilling as a married couple whose sex life has gotten routine bordering on dysfunctional ever since they had their son. Maybe even longer. Newly relocated to L.A., they meet a friendly stranger (Jason Schwartzman) with a son the same age as theirs. He invites the couple over to dinner to meet his wife and finally make some friends in their new city. Once there, things go from slightly strange to totally bonkers. It’s not clear whether Schwartzman and his French wife (Judith Godreche) are being nice or if they’re swingers on the make.</p> <p><em>The Overnight</em> takes place over 24 hours and deliriously spirals into a 21 <sup>st</sup> century <em>Bob &amp; Carol &amp; Ted &amp; Alice</em> with full-frontal male nudity. Schwartzman is tornado of funny. The second Adult Sex Comedy I caught up with was Leslye Headland’s <em>Sleeping with Other People</em>. I think I was a little more lukewarm on the film than the packed house I saw it with, but it’s still got plenty of salty laughs. If The Overnight is <em>Bob &amp; Carol &amp; Ted &amp; Alice</em>, then Headland’s film is more like <em>When Harry Met Sally</em> with masturbation gags. Jason Sudeikis and Allison Brie play two sex addicts who reunite years after losing their virginity to each other in college. And the movie is more or less a familiar tap dance of will-they-or-won’t-they tension. I’ve always liked Sudeikis’ brand of smug, smarmy charm and Brie seems to be having fun letting her hair down and be a little naughty here. But the sum of the film isn’t quite as good as its parts. Headland, who previously brought her tamer film <em>Bachelorette</em> to Sundance, is obviously very funny and seems to have first-hand experience with toxic relationships (she admitted as much introducing the film at its premiere). But compared to <em> The Overnight,</em> it felt a bit less dangerous, a bit more predictable. That said, Sudeikis’ tutorial teaching Brie how to masturbate using an empty iced green tea bottle as his model was one the more memorable movie moments I’ve had at Sundance.        </p> <p> </p>]]></description><author>Chris Nashawaty</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:3ecac17cf378e249c27ec48e962fcb53" t="1422574272" feed="200847" position="42"><title>James McAvoy explains why he almost didn't do 'The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/29/james-mcavoy-disappearance-eleanor-rigby</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/09/10/The-Disappearance-of-Eleanor-Rigby_612x380.jpg?itok=yxW_sk1K" t="image/jpeg" author="Sarah Shatz">THE DISAPPEARANCE OF ELEANOR RIGBY Jessica Chastain and James McAvoy (Sarah Shatz)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Ned Benson’s <em>The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby</em> explores the story of Connor Ludlow (James McAvoy) and Eleanor Rigby (Jessica Chastain) as they try to navigate a life together. The film is an unapologetic look at the highs and lows that come with sharing a life with someone else, and at its core, it’s an emotional love story—one that McAvoy believes people should have the chance to experience.</p> <p>“I hope it will find its audience in the way it sort of didn’t in the cinema, unfortunately,” the actor shares. “Because when people watch it, they’re quite often sort of floored by the double bill of it. And even then, without the double-bill aspect, it’s really valid interest of 90 minutes of your life at the cinema.”</p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">Shot as two separate films with differing perspectives of both protagonists ( <em>Him </em>and <em>Her</em>, respectively), <em>The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby</em> was released in theaters as a hybrid version called <em>Them</em>, which offered viewers a more streamlined look at Connor and Eleanor’s stories. Next week, the film comes to DVD in the original way that Benson intended, with the additions of <em>Him </em>and <em>Her</em>.</span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"><em>EW </em>spoke with McAvoy about the challenges of filming two different versions of the same story, his experience working with Chastain, and more.</span></p> <p><em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">The following conversation discusses significant plot details of </span></em><span style="line-height: 1.6em;">The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby.</span></p> <p><strong><em>EW</em>: This is the type of film I wish would get made more. I was blown away by how affected I was after watching it. Did you have responses like that, from people in your own life?</strong><br /><strong>JAMES MCAVOY:</strong> The only people in my life who have actually probably seen the movie are my agent and my wife. I first got offered that script five years ago, maybe even longer ago, and I said no to it because I’d just had a little baby boy. I didn’t want to touch something that had that kind of subject matter. We both went through this whole thing of whether or not I should do it, or whether or not I would be able to do it, and whether it would just be too much like self-harm to have just welcomed this little baby and tell this story about somebody’s baby dying. It was quite an emotional thing for my wife and I to watch it together. So we were touched by it.</p> <p>To be honest, I haven’t got the first actual clue what most people would think of this film, because it’s is so open to interpretation. You’ve got the <em>Them </em>one, you’ve got the <em>Him </em>one, you’ve got the <em>Her </em>one, you’ve got the combination of all three, if you want. It’s such an empowering set of movies for people. I mean, any movie allows you to have a variety of reactions, but this one purposely and willfully inspires an even greater diverse reaction from people. You know what I mean?</p> <p><strong>Absolutely. And although most people have seen the <em>Them </em>iteration, the film is obviously the richest when you can see <em>Him </em>and <em>Her</em> because of the elements it adds to the storytelling. </strong><br /> The <em>Him </em>and <em>Her </em>is what we designed, those two are the films we actually made. <em>Them </em>is a movie that we never planned to make. That’s just a kind of extra. But what’s weird is it’s become the front set of the thing. And so hopefully, that will help bring people to the <em>Him </em>and the <em>Her </em>ones as well.</p> <p><strong>Since these were essentially two different movies, you had to learn two different scripts, right?</strong><br /> Yeah, we had two separate scripts that contained entirely different narratives. So a lot of the times, I wasn’t in her script and likewise, a lot of the times she wasn’t in my script. But even when we were in each other’s scripts, those things that were similar were actually completely contradictory in a lot of ways. You have me saying one thing in my film, and me saying an entirely different thing in her film. So that was quite good fun to do, actually. It’s quite discombobulating and quite a challenge, because you find yourself playing not just your character as you see them, but your character as she sees him. That’s not something that we usually do as actors—play somebody as perceived in the mind of another. So it was a first, I think, for both Jess and I. And while it was kind of weird and strange to begin with, I think we ended up enjoying it, because it meant we got to play with our characters quite a bit.</p> <p><strong>After watching the film, I’m imagining that the production was a little intense, both in what you go through as a character and also with shooting different versions and learning different lines.</strong><br /> And also, you’re trying to play the truth of your character. You’re trying to do the right thing by your character, to make sure his experience comes across, and that he’s understood. And then that becomes completely secondary when you’re in her movie and likewise when she’s in his movie, because you’re there to help her be interested. And even though you’re playing one of the two leads, you’re playing a supporting character as well.</p> <p><strong>You mentioned you had the script for quite some time before you actually started shooting it. Is there something specific that drew you to the project and kept you interested enough to stick with it?</strong><br /> I think it was Ned’s ability to write like an adult, which you don’t get a lot. And to write about the adult experience of love and how subjective that is, and how difficult that is, and yet how beautiful that is. Because regardless of all the brilliantly defined characterization in the adult-like way about how hard it is, he still manages to make it magical somehow. He still manages to inject it with something that transcends the tragedy of childbirth and modern love. He still manages to transcend it with something magical and poetical and just sort of beautiful. And I just thought, “this guy was amazing.” And he wrote it. And he wants to direct it. And whenever you get a writer who writes something that you respond to that much, it gives you such a key into the head and the mind of the person who put the film together, in a way that sort of sitting down with him on set and “talking the talk” could never do.</p> <p><strong>I know you’ve talked a lot about working with Jessica, but given your onscreen relationship, it’s clear you guys really found a groove together.</strong><br /> We had to come up with a whole tragic backstory and fill in all those gaps and agree on a lot of stuff and kind of create a shared history and shared experience. And that experience is so moving and so touching that you can’t kind of help but be vulnerable around that person you’re working with. And that’s a great thing, because it stops you from being afraid around them, and it helps you get that feeling of intimacy on screen that you need to have between two people who have made a child together. That intimacy doesn’t just become about kissing and cuddling and sex, it goes beyond that, and that was something that we really tried to do. And it helps that she’s just a really generous actress. She’s a great actress as well as a nice person. I saw her the other night, we reminisced about our time on set playing each other’s versions of ourselves.</p> <p><strong>I hope it wasn’t a depressing conversation!</strong><br /> Whenever we get together, we just cry [ <em>laughs</em>].</p> <p><strong>This film is an emotional rollercoaster of love and loss in relationships, and I’ve read interviews where actors say that they don’t want to bring their own emotional baggage to a film because chances are, the audience already has a perception of them. And you want them to see you as the character, not the actor.</strong><br /> I don’t mind going to those places. I enjoy examining what it is to be alive and how f—ing hard it is to be alive and I get to do that for my job, and I have a great time every day in my life. I’m quite a happy person, so I don’t need to examine on film what it means to be happy all the time, you know? [ <em>Laughs</em>] But yeah, as much as people go, “I just want a rom-com, I just want a feel-good movie” or whatever, we are obsessed with tragedy and we are obsessed with sadness. We are. Otherwise, we wouldn’t have all those Shakespearean tragedies, we wouldn’t have all that sad poetry, we certainly wouldn’t have all that maudlin horrible music that teenagers and students and even adults listen to nonstop. And drama just continues to be about tragedy, as much as people go, “It’s just feel-good comedies we want!” We do want those, but we are obsessed with tragedy. I am. I love it.</p> <p><strong>What other projects are in the works for you?</strong><br /> I’ve got <em>Frankenstein</em>, which I think is October, and then after that there’ll be another <em> X-Men</em> movie. And then after that, who knows? The world is completely empty of James McAvoy movies after that for a little awhile. [ <em>Laughs</em>]</p> <p><em>The Disappearance of Eleanor Rigby</em> is available on DVD, Blu-Ray and On Demand on Feb. 3.</p>]]></description><author>Andrea Towers</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d81f926d282c4b4854cca6e4acea9768" t="1422571841" feed="200847" position="43"><title>Tom Petty says he's never 'had any hard feelings' toward Sam Smith</title><link>http://www.ew.com/tom-petty-sam-smith-statement</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2013/05/14/tom-petty_612x380.jpg?itok=OUYV5XcT" t="image/jpeg" author="Jeff Kravitz/FilmMagic">Jeff Kravitz/FilmMagic</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Sam Smith and Tom Petty recently settled a copyright dispute that ended with Petty received a co-writing credit on Smith’s “Stay With Me” <span style="color: rgb(84, 84, 84); font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; line-height: 18.2000007629395px;">—</span>but the “Free Fallin’ ” singer says he has “never had any hard feelings toward Sam.”</p> <p>The dispute centered around the similarities between Smith’s 2014 hit ” <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pB-5XG-DbAA">Stay With Me</a>” and Petty’s “ <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nvlTJrNJ5lA">I Won’t Back Down</a>,” released in 1989. “All my years of songwriting have shown me these things can happen,” Petty wrote in a statement <a href="http://www.tompetty.com/blog/statement-tom-petty-423041">on his website</a>. “Sam’s people were very understanding of our predicament and we easily came to an agreement.”</p> <p>He went on to call the incident “a musical accident, no more no less,” and wished “Sam all the best for his ongoing career.” Read the entire statement on <a href="http://www.tompetty.com/blog/statement-tom-petty-423041">his official website</a>.</p>]]></description><author>Ariana Bacle</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:3c208b73e9a63bd61fb6c3efff6d54ce" t="1422571836" feed="200847" position="44"><title>Discovery expands Shark Week to biggest event yet -- exclusive</title><link>http://www.ew.com/shark-week-2015-discovery</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422544735/gal-shark-1-jpg.jpg?itok=o4lS99Ka" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Discovery is ready to announce its annual Shark Week plans. And the cable channel is going bigger than ever for 2015.</p> <p>First, the date: Shark Week will kick off this year on July 5 – earlier than ever before.</p> <p>And Shark Week won’t just be a mere week. Discovery is calling 2015 the “Summer of the Shark,” with programming events in early July and also at the end of August. There will be no escape from the cable channel’s toothy eating machines.  </p> <p>Discovery says this year – the 28th incarnation of the programming event – will mark the most themed hours in Shark Week history (the exact total hasn’t yet been determined – but it’s a lot). Expeditions will include the first Shark Week trip to Cuba,  <span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">plus global locations that include New Zealand, South Africa, Taiwan and the Arctic, as well as numerous U.S. destinations. </span></p> <p>Shows will include new sequels to Shark Week favorites –  like the Great White-filed  <i style="line-height: 1.6em;">Air Jaws,</i><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> and </span><i style="line-height: 1.6em;">Great White Serial Killer</i><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"> featuring Jeff Kurr, Andy Casagrande and Brandon McMillan; and programming starring 10-year-old </span><span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">shark conservation activist Sean Lesniak (who helped get a law passed last year banning the possession and sale of shark fins in </span><span style="color: rgb(84, 84, 84); font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; line-height: 18.2000007629395px;">Massachusetts). </span></p> <p><span style="color: rgb(84, 84, 84); font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; line-height: 18.2000007629395px;">The only thing you won’t see: A fake-shark specials like last year’s controversial Megalodon: The Monster Shark Lives, which Discovery’s new programming president <a href="http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/08/discovery-anaconda-sharks">has vowed to avoid in the future</a>. </span></p>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2a91d4232cb49acd34214f6698e148e4" t="1422570681" feed="200847" position="45"><title>Jason Katims on 'Parenthood' finale montage, that surprise guest, more</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/29/jason-katims-parenthood-finale-montage-surprise-guest-more</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422553180/Parenthood%2520Series%2520Finale.JPG?itok=qraLtA9I" t="image/jpeg" author="Colleen Hayes/NBC">Colleen Hayes/NBC</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Nine innings later, the Bravermans have left the field and walked out of our lives forever. (Or at least until we start re-watching <em>Parenthood</em> on Netflix.) And in honor of the final hour, which saw Sarah find happiness with Hank, Zeek’s death, and a number of surprising cameos, we spoke with series creator Jason Katims about some of the episode’s most noteworthy moments. </p> <p><strong>On that Scott Porter cameo:</strong> “We had this idea for all these flashforwards in the finale and one idea we had was Amber meeting somebody else,” Katims said. “It was a tough role to cast because I didn’t just want it to be like, ‘Oh we’re casting an actor who we really didn’t know for such an important moment.’ But on the other hand, it was literally  just a moment on screen with no lines so we couldn’t really go out to just anybody to do it. It occurred to me the idea of going to somebody that I knew and had a relationship with. And then I thought of Scott and to me, it was a favor that I was asking him to do this because it was obviously not a tremendous amount of stuff he got to do. I reached out to him and he without hesitation said he would love to do it. I knew that he was also a Parenthood fan and so that was meaningful to me that he wasn’t just walking onto a show that he had no connection to himself. I knew that he really liked the show and that meant a lot and it was great. He came on, he did it. He was fantastic.”</p> <p><strong>On the Amber scene that was cut: “</strong>Actually, in the original version there was another montage piece that we just didn’t have time for in the cut but there’s another beat where the two of them first meet and you see they’re both with their kids at one of those indoor gyms. He’s a single dad and she’s a single mom and the two of them meet and it’s the very first moment of them seeing each other. And we didn’t have time for that unfortunately but I think it still sort of lands.”</p> <p><strong>On why Amber and Ryan didn’t work out: </strong>“ <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">We considered everything because the Ryan and Amber story is one of those stories that was kind of like Hank versus Mark Cyr where everybody was divided on it, including everybody in the writers room. So we had many conversations about where to go with that particular story but when the idea came up of Amber getting pregnant, I was interested in the idea of her doing it on her own. For whatever reason that appealed to me. It might’ve been because it lent itself to stories with the rest of our Braverman family and since I knew we were in our last season, I wanted to see, as much as possible, stories that brought our family together and interconnected them all. So that’s how I wound up there.”</span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"><strong>On losing Zeek:</strong> “I never knew exactly what the ending was going to be. Over the course of the series I’ve wanted to tell the story of losing a family member but I never wanted to do it because I didn’t want to lose any of those great actors, honestly. Even the way we broke the story of Zeek dying kept him in the show until the last possible minute, because I thought the most powerful way to tell that story would be by watching this family deal with this over time, which is how it happens a lot. It’s not just suddenly somebody has a heart attack and immediately passes. I went through this with both of my parents. Sometimes things happen over time and so we wanted to tell the story in that way. So when we knew that this was the final season, I felt like this was our moment to deal with this very intense subject and when we did decide to do it, I felt like that was the story that was the glue of the season, and everybody else’s stories weaved in and out around that.”</span></p> <p><strong>On Joel and Julia’s fourth child:</strong> “ <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">What was in my head was that was a child that they conceived. I’ve heard [of this happening] where a couple is struggling to get pregnant, decide to adopt and then the minute their adoption goes through, the woman learns that she’s pregnant. To me, those flashforwards were about being able to be a fly on the wall a couple of years down the road at these people that we’ve come to feel so close to, at least I know I have, and the other thing that I liked about the symmetry of that is that they now have four children. This has been a show that’s been about a family of four children so I liked the symmetry there.</span></p> <p><strong>On the Seth scene they had to cut: </strong>“W <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">e had a brief scene of John Corbett who played Amber and Drew’s dad. [It was] him coming in and meeting the baby and also finding out that Sarah was getting married and wishing her luck. That was a scene that had to be cut for time, and that was one I regret having to cut because it was a moment that, if you were a fan of the show over the years, John Corbett has done such great work, so it was a shame to have to lose that.” </span></p>]]></description><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:321325d47ba60565d2fc5176cd941c5d" t="1422569824" feed="200847" position="46"><title>Who bought what at Sundance</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/29/who-bought-what-sundance</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/30/dope.jpg?itok=yknQEYex" t="image/jpeg" author="Rick Famuyiwa ">Rick Famuyiwa </enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>With Sundance almost over, a number of the festival’s buzzy titles have been picked up for distribution.</p> <p><em>Me and Earl and the Dying Girl</em>, a film about a girl with cancer who develops a friendship with a boy who remakes movies with his friend, inspired studios to offer up $12 million, the most ever paid for a Sundance film. However,  <em>The Hollywood Reporter</em>  <a href="http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sundance-why-me-earl-dying-767545">reported</a> that instead the movie sold to Fox Searchlight for a lesser number—mid-seven figures—because the studio had what a source told <em>THR</em> was a “really creative deal.”’ ( <em>Variety</em>  <a href="http://variety.com/2015/film/news/sundance-sales-are-booming-but-will-filmgoers-respond-1201417300/">pegged</a> the price at $6 million.)</p> <p>Fox Searchlight, however, did pay <span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">a </span><a href="http://deadline.com/2015/01/brooklyn-fox-searchlight-sundance-film-festival-1201360864/" style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;">reported</a><span style="line-height: 20.7999992370605px;"> $9 million</span> for  <em>Brooklyn</em>, the adaptation of the Colm Tóibín novel, starring Saoirse Ronan. Meanwhile,  <em>Dope</em>, about teens in Inglewood, was the subject of a bidding battle that involved, according to  <a href="http://deadline.com/2015/01/dope-seven-million-dollars-open-road-sundance-film-festival-1201357907/">Deadline</a>, The Weinstein Company, A24, and Fox Searchlight. It ended up being acquired by Open Road Films and Sony Pictures for a reported $7 million. Open Road has announced that the film will open in the U.S. on June 12.</p> <p>This year’s buying has been a promising sign independent film business,  <a href="http://variety.com/2015/film/news/sundance-sales-are-booming-but-will-filmgoers-respond-1201417300/">reports</a> noted. <em>The New York Times</em>, for instance, <a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/27/business/media/pace-of-deals-picks-up-at-sundance-festival.html?_r=0">explained</a> that “while Sundance is nothing close to the buying free-for-all that it was at its peak a decade ago — at least so far — this year’s strong bidding signals a counterintuitive return to health for independent film.”</p> <p>See some of the other films studios bought in our list below.</p> <p> </p><div id="sc-v-3993236054001-ran2532" class="bc-video-player"> </div> <p><strong><em>Me and Earl and the Dying Girl</em></strong> (Worldwide rights)  <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Alfonso Gomez-Rejon <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Thomas Mann, Olivia Cooke, R.J. Cyler, Nick Offerman, Molly Shannon, Jon Bernthal and Connie Britton <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Fox Searchlight and Indian Paintbrush</p> <p><strong><em>Brooklyn</em></strong> (U.S. and various international territories rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> John Crowley <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Saoirse Ronan, Domhnall Gleeson, and Jim Broadbent <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Fox Searchlight</p> <p><strong><em>Dope</em></strong> (Open Road - U.S. rights and Sony - international rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Rick Famuyiwa  <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Shameik Moore, Tony Revolori, and Kiersey Clemons <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Open Road and Sony </p> <p><strong><em>The Diary of a Teenage Girl</em></strong> (North American and other rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Marielle Heller <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Kristen Wiig, Alexander Skarsgård, Christopher Meloni, and Bel Powley <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Sony Pictures Classics</p> <p><strong><em>Grandma</em></strong> (Worldwide rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Paul Weitz <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Lily Tomlin, Julia Garner, Marcia Gay Harden, Judy Greer, Laverne Cox, and Sam Elliott <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Sony Pictures Classics</p> <p><strong><em>Tangerine </em></strong>(Worldwide rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Sean Baker <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Mya Taylor and Kitana Kiki Rodriguez <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Magnolia Pictures</p> <p><strong><em>The Overnight</em></strong> (North American rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Patrick Brice <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Adam Scott, Taylor Schilling, Jason Schwartzman, and Judith Godrèche <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> The Orchard</p> <p><strong><em>The Witch</em></strong> (U.S. rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Robert Eggers <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Anya Taylor-Joy, Ralph Ineson, Kate Dickie <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> A24, DIRECTV</p> <p><strong><em>Mistress America</em></strong> (Worldwide rights)  <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Noah Baumbach <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Greta Gerwig and Lola Kirke <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Fox Searchlight</p> <p><strong><em>Cop Car</em></strong> (U.S. and U.K. rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Jon Watts <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Kevin Bacon, Shea Whigham, and Camryn Manheim <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Focus World</p> <p><strong><em>The Bronze</em></strong> (U.S. rights)  <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Bryan Buckley <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Melissa Rauch, Thomas Middleditch, and Sebastian Stan <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Relativity</p> <p><strong><em>The End of the Tour</em></strong> (U.S. rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> James Ponsoldt <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Jason Segel and Jesse Eisenberg <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> A24</p> <p><strong><em>Results</em></strong> (Worldwide rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Andrew Bujalski <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Cobie Smulders, Guy Pearce, and Kevin Corrigan <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Magnolia Pictures</p> <p><strong><em>Mississippi Grind</em></strong> (U.S. rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Ryan Fleck and Anna Boden <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Ryan Reynolds, Ben Mendelsohn, Sienna Miller, Annaleigh Tipton, and Robin Weigert <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> A24 and DIRECTV</p> <p><strong><em>Don Verdean</em></strong> (North American rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Jared Hess <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Sam Rockwell, Jemaine Clement, Amy Ryan, and Danny McBride <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Lionsgate</p> <p><strong><em>Strangerland</em></strong> (North American rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Kim Farrant <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Nicole Kidman, Joseph Fiennes, and Hugo Weaving <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Alchemy</p> <p><strong><em>The D Train</em></strong> (U.S. rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Jarrad Paul and Andrew Mogel <br /><strong>Stars:</strong> Jack Black, James Marsden, and Kathryn Hahn <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> IFC Films</p> <p><b><i>Knock Knock</i></b> (North American rights)  <br /><strong>Director: </strong>Eli Roth <br /><strong>Stars: </strong>Keanu Reeves, Lorenza Izzo, and Ana de Armas <br /><strong>Studio: </strong>Lionsgate</p> <p><strong><em>Digging for Fire</em></strong> (North American rights)  <br /><strong>Director: </strong>Joe Swanberg <br /><strong>Stars: </strong>Jake Johnson, Rosemarie DeWitt, Orlando Bloom, and Anna Kendrick <br /><strong>Studio: </strong>The Orchard</p> <p><strong><em>Reversal </em></strong>(U.S. rights)  <br /><strong>Director: </strong>JM Cravioto <br /><strong>Stars: </strong>Tina Ivlev and Richard Tyson <br /><strong>Studio: </strong>IFC Midnight</p> <p><strong>Documentaries</strong></p> <p><strong><em>Misery Loves Comedy</em></strong> (North American rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Kevin Pollak  <br /><strong>Subjects:</strong> Includes Tom Hanks, Whoopi Goldberg, Larry David, Judd Apatow <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Tribeca Films</p> <p><strong><em>City of Gold</em></strong> (North American rights) <br /><strong>Director:</strong> Laura Gabbert <br /><strong>Subject:</strong> Jonathan Gold <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Sundance Selects</p> <p><strong><em>The Wolfpack</em></strong><br /><strong>Director:</strong> Crystal Moselle <br /><strong>Subjects:</strong> The Angulo brothers <br /><strong>Studio:</strong> Magnolia Pictures</p>]]></description><author>Esther Zuckerman</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:949cdefa3409898749f1e9e76d37db72" t="1422567987" feed="200847" position="47"><title>Jason Katims on 'Parenthood' finale montage, that surprise guest, more</title><link>http://www.ew.com/article/2015/01/29/jason-katims-parenthood-series-finale</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422553180/Parenthood%2520Series%2520Finale.JPG?itok=qraLtA9I" t="image/jpeg" author="Colleen Hayes/NBC">Colleen Hayes/NBC</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Nine innings later, the Bravermans have left the field and walked out of our lives forever. (Or at least until we start re-watching <em>Parenthood</em> on Netflix.) And in honor of the final hour, which saw Sarah find happiness with Hank, Zeek’s death, and a number of surprising cameos, we spoke with series creator Jason Katims about some of the episode’s most noteworthy moments. </p> <p><strong>On that Scott Porter cameo:</strong> “We had this idea for all these flashforwards in the finale and one idea we had was Amber meeting somebody else,” Katims said. “It was a tough role to cast because I didn’t just want it to be like, ‘Oh we’re casting an actor who we really didn’t know for such an important moment.’ But on the other hand, it was literally  just a moment on screen with no lines so we couldn’t really go out to just anybody to do it. It occurred to me the idea of going to somebody that I knew and had a relationship with. And then I thought of Scott and to me, it was a favor that I was asking him to do this because it was obviously not a tremendous amount of stuff he got to do. I reached out to him and he without hesitation said he would love to do it. I knew that he was also a Parenthood fan and so that was meaningful to me that he wasn’t just walking onto a show that he had no connection to himself. I knew that he really liked the show and that meant a lot and it was great. He came on, he did it. He was fantastic.”</p> <p><strong>On the Amber scene that was cut: “</strong>Actually, in the original version there was another montage piece that we just didn’t have time for in the cut but there’s another beat where the two of them first meet and you see they’re both with their kids at one of those indoor gyms. He’s a single dad and she’s a single mom and the two of them meet and it’s the very first moment of them seeing each other. And we didn’t have time for that unfortunately but I think it still sort of lands.”</p> <p><strong>On why Amber and Ryan didn’t work out: </strong>“ <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">We considered everything because the Ryan and Amber story is one of those stories that was kind of like Hank versus Mark Cyr where everybody was divided on it, including everybody in the writers room. So we had many conversations about where to go with that particular story but when the idea came up of Amber getting pregnant, I was interested in the idea of her doing it on her own. For whatever reason that appealed to me. It might’ve been because it lent itself to stories with the rest of our Braverman family and since I knew we were in our last season, I wanted to see, as much as possible, stories that brought our family together and interconnected them all. So that’s how I wound up there.”</span></p> <p><span style="line-height: 1.6em;"><strong>On losing Zeek:</strong> “I never knew exactly what the ending was going to be. Over the course of the series I’ve wanted to tell the story of losing a family member but I never wanted to do it because I didn’t want to lose any of those great actors, honestly. Even the way we broke the story of Zeek dying kept him in the show until the last possible minute, because I thought the most powerful way to tell that story would be by watching this family deal with this over time, which is how it happens a lot. It’s not just suddenly somebody has a heart attack and immediately passes. I went through this with both of my parents. Sometimes things happen over time and so we wanted to tell the story in that way. So when we knew that this was the final season, I felt like this was our moment to deal with this very intense subject and when we did decide to do it, I felt like that was the story that was the glue of the season, and everybody else’s stories weaved in and out around that.”</span></p> <p><strong>On Joel and Julia’s fourth child:</strong> “ <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">What was in my head was that was a child that they conceived. I’ve heard [of this happening] where a couple is struggling to get pregnant, decide to adopt and then the minute their adoption goes through, the woman learns that she’s pregnant. To me, those flashforwards were about being able to be a fly on the wall a couple of years down the road at these people that we’ve come to feel so close to, at least I know I have, and the other thing that I liked about the symmetry of that is that they now have four children. This has been a show that’s been about a family of four children so I liked the symmetry there.</span></p> <p><strong>On the Seth scene they had to cut: </strong>“W <span style="line-height: 1.6em;">e had a brief scene of John Corbett who played Amber and Drew’s dad. [It was] him coming in and meeting the baby and also finding out that Sarah was getting married and wishing her luck. That was a scene that had to be cut for time, and that was one I regret having to cut because it was a moment that, if you were a fan of the show over the years, John Corbett has done such great work, so it was a shame to have to lose that.” </span></p>]]></description><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:summary" t="1422564005" feed="200847" position="48"><title>'Getting Prickly in Mexico'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/top-chef-season-12-episode-13</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422512227/top-chef-recap_612x380.jpg?itok=sdVbkFx3" t="image/jpeg" author="David Moir/Bravo">David Moir/Bravo</enclosure><author>John Vilanova</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><contents>urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222,urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:20fc058d0fcd94b7eac01ac9e92e6b57,urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:561e5fc0dc71dba2145645cb799a5a74</contents></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222" t="1422564005" feed="200847" contained="1" count="1-3" position="48"><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/top-chef-season-12-episode-13</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/1422512227/top-chef-recap_612x380.jpg?itok=sdVbkFx3" t="image/jpeg" author="David Moir/Bravo">David Moir/Bravo</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">If there’s one thing that might be harder to describe in written words than food, it’s art. Asking an artist what their work is “about” is like asking your dad what goes into his secret family meatball recipe or querying a barbecue restaurant on what spices go into their rub. You might be able to glean a thing or two from the placard (or menu) that accompanies the piece, but cooking and eating are both personal mediums. They have the potential to touch you deeply, but you have to experience them for yourself to know.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Before we put the finishing touches on the first piece the  <em>Top Chef</em> finale triptych (that’s “trio” for the less artsy fartsy folks), there’s some serious sketching to do. The remaining cheftestants have literally covered a lot of ground since we last saw them sweating out the final elimination in Beantown, decamping for a few weeks of R&amp;R in their hometowns before meeting in Mexico to crown a champion. The break is always an interesting time—chefs study up on the flavors they’ll be expected to work with during the finale, spend time with family, and get gussied up for the cameras again. While no one’s “finale makeover” quite compares to Kevin Gillespie’s hairdo in Vegas, Gregory’s looking fresh with a new cut, and Mei’s rocking some new lipstick. How about that?</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In between scrutinizing shades, Mei spent the break interning with Brian Voltaggio and studying up on Mexican flavor profiles (Sidenote: Is there a more intimidating boss than Michael Voltaggio?). If such a thing is possible, Melissa might have been hurt by the break—her hot streak over the final Boston weeks had reached supernova status. Will she be able to regain her momentum? Besides the aforementioned haircut, Gregory needed the break the most—hopefully he used the time off to right the ship and figure out what brought on his crumbling second half in Boston. He’s not unique here—Jen Carroll had a similar slow burn in Vegas in the run-up to the finale—but confidence in your cookery seems like the hardest thing to regain in this competition. To wit, Jen only lasted the one week before elimination.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">People generally seem to be split on Last Chance Kitchen, but for me, in its short run, it has served an important purpose—allowing chefs who probably “belong” in the final to redeem themselves after a slip-up. The most obvious example, of course, is Kristen, who was undone by the “Chef-and-Josie Show” in Seattle. Kristen was clearly the “best” chef that year, and LCK allowed the producers the ability to rectify a culinary wrong. It still wasn’t a cakewalk—she had to win five weeks in a row to earn her slot in the finale, but the final result would’ve been tainted if she hadn’t factored into it.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Unsurprisingly, Doug(ie) has dispatched with a few of his lesser competitors to meet George the Greek, who’s working on life three of nine for those of you keeping track at home. While not as obviously deserving as Kristen, Doug dealt himself a raw deal with his inedibly undercooked foie gras lobes, a dish that even a true master of French cooking wouldn’t have been able to pull off. He’d won three of the previous five weeks, though, and I can’t really buy any other eliminated chef’s case for reconsideration.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In his previous “lives,” George was undone by clams and octopus, so, as it often is on LCK, the eliminated chef is forced to confront his demons in dish form. Doug gets the final say between the two, chooses clams, and the last Last Chance Kitchen cook-off begins. Given the setting, requiring the dish to have a Mexican style is fitting, so, in what will probably a recurring theme over the final three weeks, the chefs break out the veggies, peppers, and cilantro immediately. Doug’s Mexican steamers with grilled pineapple butter, lime juice, tomatillos, roasted onions have the sweet-and-sour thing working for them; George goes smoky with a salsa verde-style soup with epazote-influenced tomatillos, Serrano chilis, garlic, beets, zucchini, and apple accompanying his clams.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">The remaining competitors return just in time to say, “Hola” to the last-chancers—there’s some funny banter in the online version for those of you who don’t typically watch—and, as has often been the case this season, it comes down to which dish is “most good.” George’s looks a bit more appetizing, but ultimately it’s Dougie’s day, and he returns to complete the final final four.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;"><strong>NEXT: Prickly pears and painter pairings</strong></p></p>]]></description><author>John Vilanova</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:20fc058d0fcd94b7eac01ac9e92e6b57" t="1422564005" feed="200847" contained="1" count="2-3" position="48"><title/><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/top-chef-season-12-episode-13</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">If there’s one thing that might be harder to describe in written words than food, it’s art. Asking an artist what their work is “about” is like asking your dad what goes into his secret family meatball recipe or querying a barbecue restaurant on what spices go into their rub. You might be able to glean a thing or two from the placard (or menu) that accompanies the piece, but cooking and eating are both personal mediums. They have the potential to touch you deeply, but you have to experience them for yourself to know.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Before we put the finishing touches on the first piece the  <em>Top Chef</em> finale triptych (that’s “trio” for the less artsy fartsy folks), there’s some serious sketching to do. The remaining cheftestants have literally covered a lot of ground since we last saw them sweating out the final elimination in Beantown, decamping for a few weeks of R&amp;R in their hometowns before meeting in Mexico to crown a champion. The break is always an interesting time—chefs study up on the flavors they’ll be expected to work with during the finale, spend time with family, and get gussied up for the cameras again. While no one’s “finale makeover” quite compares to Kevin Gillespie’s hairdo in Vegas, Gregory’s looking fresh with a new cut, and Mei’s rocking some new lipstick. How about that?</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In between scrutinizing shades, Mei spent the break interning with Brian Voltaggio and studying up on Mexican flavor profiles (Sidenote: Is there a more intimidating boss than Michael Voltaggio?). If such a thing is possible, Melissa might have been hurt by the break—her hot streak over the final Boston weeks had reached supernova status. Will she be able to regain her momentum? Besides the aforementioned haircut, Gregory needed the break the most—hopefully he used the time off to right the ship and figure out what brought on his crumbling second half in Boston. He’s not unique here—Jen Carroll had a similar slow burn in Vegas in the run-up to the finale—but confidence in your cookery seems like the hardest thing to regain in this competition. To wit, Jen only lasted the one week before elimination.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">People generally seem to be split on Last Chance Kitchen, but for me, in its short run, it has served an important purpose—allowing chefs who probably “belong” in the final to redeem themselves after a slip-up. The most obvious example, of course, is Kristen, who was undone by the “Chef-and-Josie Show” in Seattle. Kristen was clearly the “best” chef that year, and LCK allowed the producers the ability to rectify a culinary wrong. It still wasn’t a cakewalk—she had to win five weeks in a row to earn her slot in the finale, but the final result would’ve been tainted if she hadn’t factored into it.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Unsurprisingly, Doug(ie) has dispatched with a few of his lesser competitors to meet George the Greek, who’s working on life three of nine for those of you keeping track at home. While not as obviously deserving as Kristen, Doug dealt himself a raw deal with his inedibly undercooked foie gras lobes, a dish that even a true master of French cooking wouldn’t have been able to pull off. He’d won three of the previous five weeks, though, and I can’t really buy any other eliminated chef’s case for reconsideration.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In his previous “lives,” George was undone by clams and octopus, so, as it often is on LCK, the eliminated chef is forced to confront his demons in dish form. Doug gets the final say between the two, chooses clams, and the last Last Chance Kitchen cook-off begins. Given the setting, requiring the dish to have a Mexican style is fitting, so, in what will probably a recurring theme over the final three weeks, the chefs break out the veggies, peppers, and cilantro immediately. Doug’s Mexican steamers with grilled pineapple butter, lime juice, tomatillos, roasted onions have the sweet-and-sour thing working for them; George goes smoky with a salsa verde-style soup with epazote-influenced tomatillos, Serrano chilis, garlic, beets, zucchini, and apple accompanying his clams.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">The remaining competitors return just in time to say, “Hola” to the last-chancers—there’s some funny banter in the online version for those of you who don’t typically watch—and, as has often been the case this season, it comes down to which dish is “most good.” George’s looks a bit more appetizing, but ultimately it’s Dougie’s day, and he returns to complete the final final four.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;"><strong>NEXT: Prickly pears and painter pairings</strong></p></p>]]></description><author>John Vilanova</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:372ca43d19f727a8a7e2a6efc69f6222:561e5fc0dc71dba2145645cb799a5a74" t="1422564005" feed="200847" contained="1" count="3-3" position="48"><title/><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/top-chef-season-12-episode-13</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">If there’s one thing that might be harder to describe in written words than food, it’s art. Asking an artist what their work is “about” is like asking your dad what goes into his secret family meatball recipe or querying a barbecue restaurant on what spices go into their rub. You might be able to glean a thing or two from the placard (or menu) that accompanies the piece, but cooking and eating are both personal mediums. They have the potential to touch you deeply, but you have to experience them for yourself to know.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Before we put the finishing touches on the first piece the  <em>Top Chef</em> finale triptych (that’s “trio” for the less artsy fartsy folks), there’s some serious sketching to do. The remaining cheftestants have literally covered a lot of ground since we last saw them sweating out the final elimination in Beantown, decamping for a few weeks of R&amp;R in their hometowns before meeting in Mexico to crown a champion. The break is always an interesting time—chefs study up on the flavors they’ll be expected to work with during the finale, spend time with family, and get gussied up for the cameras again. While no one’s “finale makeover” quite compares to Kevin Gillespie’s hairdo in Vegas, Gregory’s looking fresh with a new cut, and Mei’s rocking some new lipstick. How about that?</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In between scrutinizing shades, Mei spent the break interning with Brian Voltaggio and studying up on Mexican flavor profiles (Sidenote: Is there a more intimidating boss than Michael Voltaggio?). If such a thing is possible, Melissa might have been hurt by the break—her hot streak over the final Boston weeks had reached supernova status. Will she be able to regain her momentum? Besides the aforementioned haircut, Gregory needed the break the most—hopefully he used the time off to right the ship and figure out what brought on his crumbling second half in Boston. He’s not unique here—Jen Carroll had a similar slow burn in Vegas in the run-up to the finale—but confidence in your cookery seems like the hardest thing to regain in this competition. To wit, Jen only lasted the one week before elimination.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">People generally seem to be split on Last Chance Kitchen, but for me, in its short run, it has served an important purpose—allowing chefs who probably “belong” in the final to redeem themselves after a slip-up. The most obvious example, of course, is Kristen, who was undone by the “Chef-and-Josie Show” in Seattle. Kristen was clearly the “best” chef that year, and LCK allowed the producers the ability to rectify a culinary wrong. It still wasn’t a cakewalk—she had to win five weeks in a row to earn her slot in the finale, but the final result would’ve been tainted if she hadn’t factored into it.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">Unsurprisingly, Doug(ie) has dispatched with a few of his lesser competitors to meet George the Greek, who’s working on life three of nine for those of you keeping track at home. While not as obviously deserving as Kristen, Doug dealt himself a raw deal with his inedibly undercooked foie gras lobes, a dish that even a true master of French cooking wouldn’t have been able to pull off. He’d won three of the previous five weeks, though, and I can’t really buy any other eliminated chef’s case for reconsideration.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">In his previous “lives,” George was undone by clams and octopus, so, as it often is on LCK, the eliminated chef is forced to confront his demons in dish form. Doug gets the final say between the two, chooses clams, and the last Last Chance Kitchen cook-off begins. Given the setting, requiring the dish to have a Mexican style is fitting, so, in what will probably a recurring theme over the final three weeks, the chefs break out the veggies, peppers, and cilantro immediately. Doug’s Mexican steamers with grilled pineapple butter, lime juice, tomatillos, roasted onions have the sweet-and-sour thing working for them; George goes smoky with a salsa verde-style soup with epazote-influenced tomatillos, Serrano chilis, garlic, beets, zucchini, and apple accompanying his clams.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;">The remaining competitors return just in time to say, “Hola” to the last-chancers—there’s some funny banter in the online version for those of you who don’t typically watch—and, as has often been the case this season, it comes down to which dish is “most good.” George’s looks a bit more appetizing, but ultimately it’s Dougie’s day, and he returns to complete the final final four.</p> <p style="font-family: Georgia, &apos;Times New Roman&apos;, &apos;Bitstream Charter&apos;, Times, serif; font-size: 16px; line-height: 24px;"><strong>NEXT: Prickly pears and painter pairings</strong></p></p>]]></description><author>John Vilanova</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:7b376af1e2e60d396d0bc88bd572ac33" t="1422564005" feed="200847" position="49"><title>The Terminator's back in Super Bowl 'Genisys' teaser</title><link>http://www.ew.com/terminator-genisys-super-bowl-teaser</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2014/12/02/Terminator-Poster_612x380.jpg?itok=8UHlrvPu" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/N4zhBQfqVCc" width="560"></iframe></p> <p>Arnold Schwarzenegger said he’d be back <span style="color: rgb(84, 84, 84); font-family: arial, sans-serif; font-size: small; line-height: 18.2000007629395px;">—</span>and here he is in the new trailer for  <em>Terminator Genisys </em>set to air during the Super Bowl.</p> <p><em>Terminator Genisys </em>is the fifth film in the franchise, but isn’t exactly a sequel: Because of the time-traveling in the  <em>Terminator </em>series, the movie is being considered a sequel  <em>and </em>a prequel  <em>and </em>a reboot. </p> <p>Alan Taylor, who must recently directed 2013’s  <em>Thor: The Dark World, </em>is directing. Schwarzenegger is reprising his role as the Terminator and will star alongside  <em>Terminator </em>newcomers Jason Clarke, Emilia Clarke, and Jai Courtney.</p> <p>The 30-second teaser will air during the Super Bowl, which kicks off Sunday at 6:30 p.m. ET on NBC.</p>]]></description><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6:summary" t="1422564003" feed="200847" position="50"><title>'Prayer for the Dying'</title><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/the-vampire-diaries-season-6-episode-12</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/vampire-diaries-recap.jpg?itok=f59W5e_G" t="image/jpeg" author="Tina Rowden/The CW ">Tina Rowden/The CW </enclosure><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><contents>urn:onebot:article:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6,urn:onebot:article:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6:0536565bf2ca7eddd1e37388378d26b6</contents></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6" t="1422564003" feed="200847" contained="1" count="1-2" position="50"><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/the-vampire-diaries-season-6-episode-12</link><enclosure u="http://www.ew.com/sites/default/files/styles/tout_image_612x380/public/i/2015/01/29/vampire-diaries-recap.jpg?itok=f59W5e_G" t="image/jpeg" author="Tina Rowden/The CW ">Tina Rowden/The CW </enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><em>The Vampire Diaries</em> has always been filled with death. Heck, the entire show started because a girl lost her parents, lost her way, and then fell in love with a (very dreamy) dead guy. So tonight, it wasn’t a real shocker that the episode once again dealt with the topic of death and how it can affect surrounding relationships. Let’s face it: Death is one of the things this show does best, and even though tonight’s death didn’t necessarily impact us the ways others have in the past—I’m looking at you, Ric—it still gave us a highly dramatic hour.</p> <p>We kick things off in Liz’s room at home, when Caroline wakes up after hearing something downstairs—or rather someone. Suddenly, at her back door, a bloody Colin shows up. Don’t know who Colin is? Oh, just the guy she fed her blood last week and effectively killed. But really, she <em>killed</em> him. When Stefan shows up, he figures out that her blood turned him into a vampire, which means that he had to have died after she gave him her blood. Yeah, it’s not good news for Liz.</p> <p>I do have to say that this opening felt like a real throwback to me, and I liked it. I miss the days of <em>TVD</em> opening like a scary movie. It was all very season 1, in a way.</p> <p>Back to the action: Elena, who’s apparently sleeping at Alaric’s—where is Alaric?—is on her way to class when Damon shows up with a sandwich and a proposal. He wants to take her out to dinner tonight. It involves something about eggplant. Elena is in… until she figures out that Damon is recreating a date they already had. Refusing to pick up where they left off, Elena shuts down the eggplant. But they’re still on for the date. She’ll see him at six!</p> <p>Except not really, because pretty quickly, they all arrive at the hospital to see if Jo can figure out what happened to Colin. The verdict? Caroline’s blood sped up his cancer and killed him. In other words, he’s a stage 10 cancer patient, which doesn’t even exist. It’s <em>that </em>bad.</p> <p>Nobody really knows what to do, but after Elena expresses her disappointment in Stefan for not knowing better and doing more research before Caroline gave Liz her blood, Jo has an idea: A full blood transfusion might get the vamp blood out of Liz’s system. At this point, anything is worth a shot.</p> <p>Across town, Liv and Tyler are getting comfortable in a twin bed, planning their spring break, when Liv’s dad shows up and informs everyone that it’s Liv’s birthday. So basically, she and Luke have to convince their father/leader that they aren’t going to merge, like, now. And shockingly, he’s not a fan of the plan.</p> <p>Back at the hospital, Damon tries to catch Elena up on his relationship with Liz: “As far as humans go, she’s tolerable.” Translation: He loves her the mostest, probably only second to Alaric at this point. And that kind of explains his behavior when he overhears poor Colin trying to kill himself in the other room.</p> <p>While Caroline tries to talk Colin down, Damon does the guy a favor and rips his heart out. It’s not he craziest thing he’s done, however, he did not need to rip Caroline’s heart out with this Liz update: “Transfusion didn’t work, so you didn’t just kill <em>him</em>, blondie.” I know you’re emotional Damon, but that’s her <em>mom</em>.</p> <p>On that note, Caroline runs away, leaving Elena to break the bad news to Liz. The transfusion didn’t work. But Liz is less concerned about that, and more concerned about her daughter, who Stefan finds trying to pick the right flowers for her mother’s memorial. Ever the planner, Caroline has decided to spend her time doing something she’s good at before she screws up again.</p> <p>But once Stefan tells her the story of his mother—the mysterious mother Salvatore!—we learn that Stefan kept himself occupied during his mother’s illness out of fear of seeing her that way, and before he knew it, his dad had sent his mom away and then she was dead. Long story short: He’d do anything to have another day with her.</p> <p>After Caroline reaches for Stefan’s hand—this particular hand hold is kind of becoming their thing—she agrees to head back to the hospital. But could she be too late?</p> <p><strong>NEXT: How many times can we say the word “merge”?</strong></p>]]></description><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:8e2084fe4b3396865b034515b27d91a6:0536565bf2ca7eddd1e37388378d26b6" t="1422564003" feed="200847" contained="1" count="2-2" position="50"><title/><link>http://www.ew.com/recap/the-vampire-diaries-season-6-episode-12</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><em>The Vampire Diaries</em> has always been filled with death. Heck, the entire show started because a girl lost her parents, lost her way, and then fell in love with a (very dreamy) dead guy. So tonight, it wasn’t a real shocker that the episode once again dealt with the topic of death and how it can affect surrounding relationships. Let’s face it: Death is one of the things this show does best, and even though tonight’s death didn’t necessarily impact us the ways others have in the past—I’m looking at you, Ric—it still gave us a highly dramatic hour.</p> <p>We kick things off in Liz’s room at home, when Caroline wakes up after hearing something downstairs—or rather someone. Suddenly, at her back door, a bloody Colin shows up. Don’t know who Colin is? Oh, just the guy she fed her blood last week and effectively killed. But really, she <em>killed</em> him. When Stefan shows up, he figures out that her blood turned him into a vampire, which means that he had to have died after she gave him her blood. Yeah, it’s not good news for Liz.</p> <p>I do have to say that this opening felt like a real throwback to me, and I liked it. I miss the days of <em>TVD</em> opening like a scary movie. It was all very season 1, in a way.</p> <p>Back to the action: Elena, who’s apparently sleeping at Alaric’s—where is Alaric?—is on her way to class when Damon shows up with a sandwich and a proposal. He wants to take her out to dinner tonight. It involves something about eggplant. Elena is in… until she figures out that Damon is recreating a date they already had. Refusing to pick up where they left off, Elena shuts down the eggplant. But they’re still on for the date. She’ll see him at six!</p> <p>Except not really, because pretty quickly, they all arrive at the hospital to see if Jo can figure out what happened to Colin. The verdict? Caroline’s blood sped up his cancer and killed him. In other words, he’s a stage 10 cancer patient, which doesn’t even exist. It’s <em>that </em>bad.</p> <p>Nobody really knows what to do, but after Elena expresses her disappointment in Stefan for not knowing better and doing more research before Caroline gave Liz her blood, Jo has an idea: A full blood transfusion might get the vamp blood out of Liz’s system. At this point, anything is worth a shot.</p> <p>Across town, Liv and Tyler are getting comfortable in a twin bed, planning their spring break, when Liv’s dad shows up and informs everyone that it’s Liv’s birthday. So basically, she and Luke have to convince their father/leader that they aren’t going to merge, like, now. And shockingly, he’s not a fan of the plan.</p> <p>Back at the hospital, Damon tries to catch Elena up on his relationship with Liz: “As far as humans go, she’s tolerable.” Translation: He loves her the mostest, probably only second to Alaric at this point. And that kind of explains his behavior when he overhears poor Colin trying to kill himself in the other room.</p> <p>While Caroline tries to talk Colin down, Damon does the guy a favor and rips his heart out. It’s not he craziest thing he’s done, however, he did not need to rip Caroline’s heart out with this Liz update: “Transfusion didn’t work, so you didn’t just kill <em>him</em>, blondie.” I know you’re emotional Damon, but that’s her <em>mom</em>.</p> <p>On that note, Caroline runs away, leaving Elena to break the bad news to Liz. The transfusion didn’t work. But Liz is less concerned about that, and more concerned about her daughter, who Stefan finds trying to pick the right flowers for her mother’s memorial. Ever the planner, Caroline has decided to spend her time doing something she’s good at before she screws up again.</p> <p>But once Stefan tells her the story of his mother—the mysterious mother Salvatore!—we learn that Stefan kept himself occupied during his mother’s illness out of fear of seeing her that way, and before he knew it, his dad had sent his mom away and then she was dead. Long story short: He’d do anything to have another day with her.</p> <p>After Caroline reaches for Stefan’s hand—this particular hand hold is kind of becoming their thing—she agrees to head back to the hospital. But could she be too late?</p> <p><strong>NEXT: How many times can we say the word “merge”?</strong></p>]]></description><author>Samantha Highfill</author><category>Entertainment</category><source>Entertainment Weekly</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2280</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 Entertainment Weekly Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item></channel>