<channel xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:bc="http://www.brightcove.com/link" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:fn="http://www.w3.org/2005/xpath-functions" xmlns:functx="http://www.functx.com" id="Rminutemag1.2311" token="1422747011" name="feed" domain="http://feed" requestUrl="/xslt/transform?template=time-to-mpp&amp;bucket=golf&amp;order=published&amp;before=now&amp;limit=150&amp;f=200853&amp;cid=Rminutemag1.2311&amp;bit=Golf"><item id="urn:onebot:article:4b8db9c9e882e996702402c705a5530b" t="1421784037" feed="200853" position="1"><title>Gil Hanse to Design Third Streamsong Course</title><link>http://www.golf.com/courses-and-travel/gil-hanse-design-third-streamsong-course</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/20/Streamsong%2520Black%2520%25281%2529.jpg?itok=BVpSgYbl" t="image/jpeg" author="Al Hurley">Gil Hanse's Streamsong (Black) is expected to open in the fall of 2017. (Al Hurley)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Two’s good company, but three still won’t feel crowded at Streamsong Resort, which announced today that it has tapped Gil Hanse to design a third course on its sprawling central Florida property.</p> <p>Opened in 2013, Streamsong already sports a pair of acclaimed layouts, the Blue and Red Courses, designed by Tom Doak and the Bill Coore and Ben Crenshaw duo respectively.</p> <p>Both tracks wind through a dramatic landscape marked by heaving dunes that phosphate mining left behind. Walker-friendly, with few forced carries and no homes in sight, the layouts stand in architectural contrast to golf-as-usual in Florida, a state better known for flat, bomb-and-gauge designs.</p> <p>The Red Course ranks 12th on <a href="http://www.golf.com/courses-and-travel/top-100-courses-you-can-play-1" target="_blank">Golf Magazine’s list of Top 100 Course You Can Play</a>, and the Blue Course sits just four places below it at No. 16.</p> <p>In hiring Hanse, Streamsong has enlisted one of the busiest men in the business. Along with Castle Stuart in Scotland and the renovated Blue Monster course at Doral, Hanse’s recent design credits include the Olympic Golf Course in Rio de Janeiro. He is also in line to build a sixth Oregon course for Mike Keiser, four miles south of Keiser’s Bandon Dunes Resort, though a launch date for that project has not been set.</p> <p>At Streamsong, a 16,000-acre property 90 minutes from Orlando and 60 minutes from Tampa, Hanse should have plenty of space to work with. Unlike the Red and Blue Courses, which stretch side by side and at times intermingle, Hanse’s design -- the Black Course -- will sit on its own, southeast of its siblings. According to Hanse, that stand-alone location will help lend the layout an expansive sense of scale.</p> <p>“It’s similar to the other sites in that it’s sand-based, with dunes and wild-looking native grasses,” Hanse said. “But I think it’s going to feel wider and broader, with longer flowing ridges as opposed to more abrupt undulations.”</p> <p>Though Hanse has yet to finalize his blueprint for the Black Course, he said he was especially excited about dunes-strewn section of the site known as The Glove, which calls to mind just that when viewed from the air.</p> <p>“It has a ton of possibilities,” Hanse said. “We should be able to do something pretty cool and linksy-feeling there.”</p> <p>Construction on the Black Course is set to begin this summer, with completion expected in the fall of 2017.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Josh Sens</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:714e1a7d375885a5816a2b17c8f0a309" t="1421784036" feed="200853" position="2"><title>Forget IHOP: Brooke Pancake Signs Deal With Waffle House</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/20/forget-ihop-brook-pancake-signs-deal-waffle-house</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Brook%2520Pancake%2520Waffle%2520House.jpg?itok=oe__qO8F" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2014/11/29/gallery_images/LydiaKo_690_0.jpg?itok=6egwBAF4" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>What&apos;s in a name? Not one&apos;s allegiance to breakfast food, apparently.</p> <div>  </div> <p>LPGA golfer Brooke Pancake announced her new endorsement deal with Waffle House on Jan. 20.</p> <p>Pancake will be spending part of her third season on the tour at various Waffle House franchises, as well as sporting the restaurant&apos;s logo on her bag.</p> <p>While at the University of Alabama, Pancake helped the team to win its first NCAA National Championship in program history in 2012, and was an individual runner-up. She was also the first athlete and first female golfer to be named the Academic All-America Team Member of the Year, the top student-sportsperson for her senior year.</p> <div> </div> <p>She is currently ranked 214th and posted a best T53 at the 2014 LPGA Championship.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d773554b57f816b089b7f3d28f303b63" t="1421713955" feed="200853" position="3"><title>OnCore Golf Balls, Toothless Tiger and More in the Van Cynical Mailbag</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/oncore-golf-balls-toothless-tiger-and-more-van-cynical-mailbag</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/20/OnCore-golf-ball.jpg?itok=cOkQQxex" t="image/jpeg" author="Courtesy of OnCore Golf">Gary looks into the revolutionary new OnCore golf balls. (Courtesy of OnCore Golf)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> ORLANDO, Fla. -- The category is, Things Nobody Says in the Golf Business. <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>The answers are:</p> <p><b>a.</b> Hey, let&apos;s start a company and make golf balls.</p> <p><b>b.</b> Since Cleveland is the Heart of Rock &apos;n Roll, let&apos;s locate our new business in the Home of Golf -- Buffalo, N.Y.</p> <p><b>c.</b> Let&apos;s come up with an equipment innovation that the United States Golf Association, which is deathly afraid of missing yet another revolutionary game-changing idea, is almost sure to outlaw.</p> <p><b>d.</b> All we need is a way to make golf harder, slower and more expensive and we&apos;ll be rich.</p> <p>Give yourself a low five for guessing that &quot;d&quot; is the only wrong answer. And give the guys at <a href="http://www.oncoregolf.com/" target="_blank">OnCore Golf</a> credit for still being here despite a business plan that&apos;s as simple as a, b, c.</p> <p>Golf balls? Trying to get in the ball business almost sank Callaway Golf when it was at the peak of its success. How are you going to compete against the big boys -- Titleist, TaylorMade and Nike -- who have millions in marketing dollars?</p> <p>Buffalo? The home of golf business headquarters is Carlsbad, Calif., where TaylorMade, Callaway and Cobra are located. Even Titleist, which is based in Massachusetts, has a test center in Carlsbad. Buffalo is where lake-effect snow goes to be shoveled.</p> <p>The USGA? Does anybody, even if they&apos;re right, win an argument with the USGA?</p> <p>Steve Coulton laughs at every scenario. He and OnCore co-founder Bret Blakely have heard it all already. <a href="http://www.oncoregolf.com/" target="_blank">OnCore Golf</a> is still alive and kicking, even if sometimes it seems like an old Jeff Bridges-James Woods movie, &quot;Against All Odds.&quot; No doubt, Coulton figures, the guy who started UnderArmour heard the same dire predictions about going up against Nike and all the other big sportswear companies.</p> <p>&quot;Sons don&apos;t necessarily want to wear or play what their father or grandfathers are wearing,&quot; Coulton said. That is definitely true in fashion. But Buffalo? OK, it&apos;s actually a pretty good golf city, like a lot of northern cities where a short season somehow makes the golfers even more avid. But why not move south to someplace &quot;warmer&quot; like Harrisburg or Scranton? Rumor has it that Dunder Mifflin has warehouse space available in the latter.</p> <p>Coulton laughs again. &quot;With technology now, you can start a company from a boat on the middle of the ocean,&quot; he said.</p> <p><a href="http://www.oncoregolf.com/" target="_blank">OnCore Golf</a> is still in business, despite the odds, because it has, indeed, come up with a technological innovation. Its product is a golf ball with a hollow metal core. That&apos;s right, in the space where that squishy liquid center was 50 year ago, the OnCore ball is all air around a high-performance polymer shell. The original OnCore working model had a 1.1 inch diameter hollow center. After testing and fine-tuning, OnCore settled on a .9-inch hollow-core center.</p> <p>Why did any of this happen? Because an engineer, Doug DuFaux, got tired of hitting big hooks and missing fairways so he wanted to design a ball that had less sidespin and flew straighter. Golfer, heal thyself.</p> <p>The OnCore story comes in three parts. One, design and build a ball. Two, get it approved. Three, figure out how to sell it.</p> <p>Blakely and Coulton were unlikely golf company founders. They met through New York University. Coulton was working in finance, Blake had a job in international marketing. Coulton was a pretty good golfer and Blakely mentioned that his father, Keith, had a company (Nano Dynamics) that had a side project that was creating a new golf ball (designed by DuFaux) with better spin and flight characteristics. The basic idea was that if perimeter weighting made better golf clubs, why wouldn&apos;t it make a better golf ball, too? What better way to perimeter-weight a ball than by having no weight in the center?</p> <p>The first prototype had a stainless steel shell around a 1.1 inch hollow core.</p> <p>&quot;It had this thin layer of rubber around it, it felt like a rock,&quot; Coulton said. &quot;But it was wicked straight, It was 70 percent straighter but lost a lot in distance, so it wasn&apos;t going to be a commercial success.&quot;</p> <p>Months of prototypes and testing led OnCore to the current .9-inch diameter.</p> <p>&quot;It&apos;s got more cushion now,&quot; Coulton said. &quot;We lost some of the accuracy advantage but it&apos;s still more accurate than traditional balls.&quot;</p> <p>His usual explanation of the technology is to liken it to an ice skater who spins faster with arms tucked in and when it&apos;s time to slow down, the skater extends the arms. &quot;The weight is centered in a rubber-core ball so you have an increase in side spin,&quot; he said. &quot;The hollow metal core pushes that weight to the perimeter, so you&apos;re slowing down that sidespin.&quot;</p> <p>Long story, short: Blakely and Coulton licensed the technology and went off on their own, starting OnCore Golf, and eventually bringing DuFaux on board.</p> <p>It took about two years from start to finish. Designing and building the ball was the first challenge. The ball is manufactured through partnerships in the U.S. and in Asia (China), by the way.</p> <p>The bigger challenge may have been getting the USGA to put the OnCore ball on the list of conforming golf balls. That took a year by itself.</p> <p>OnCore submitted its ball and the USGA denied it, saying the ball did not meet their requirements as &quot;being of traditional and customary form and make.&quot;</p> <p>&quot;They created that rule in 2008 and they had it for clubs,&quot; Coulton said. &quot;Historically, there were always just five metrics for balls -- weight, total distance, symmetry, diameter and initial velocity. We knew we met all of those standards so we appealed.&quot;</p> <p>There had been golf balls, Coulton said, that were approved and the companies who marketed the balls used phrases such as &quot;never-before seen materials,&quot; a &quot;hammer-blow to tradition,&quot; and &quot;revolutionary.&quot; &quot;So if they&apos;re saying that, they couldn&apos;t have been traditional, either,&quot; he said. &quot;It seemed arbitrary.&quot;</p> <p>How do you tell the USGA they&apos;re being hypocritical a--holes? You keep appealing.</p> <p>That meant a lot of paperwork and letters. OnCore&apos;s first appeal went to the USGA&apos;s equipment committee, which denied the appeal. Then it went to the executive committee, which heard a 15-minute presentation from OnCore over the phone, which was followed by documents of supporting evidence that included information provided by the USGA that a version of a hollow-core ball had been approved once in the past.</p> <p>&quot;I thought we had a 50-50 chance, Bret thought we had a one percent chance,&quot; Coulton said.</p> <p>In October 2013, an email from the USGA arrived that said a rules change had been made that a ball with rigid cores of .9 inch or less will be deemed permissible. OnCore was in business.</p> <p>&quot;They said it was only the second time in history, since the liquid core ball in 1921, that they made an exception or allowance for a golf ball,&quot; Coulton said. &quot;It was a big moment in the company&apos;s history.&quot;</p> <p>When Coulton got the news, he was at a fund-raiser at a church on the Canisius College campus.</p> <p>&quot;I&apos;m not super-religious but I was in a church and I looked up and gave thanks,&quot; he said. &quot;I had a celebration internally. It was the best feeling in the world.&quot;</p> <p>Later, he and Blakely went to Tappo, a Buffalo restaurant and bar that used to be a coffee distribution center, and celebrated with a few drinks.</p> <p>&quot;Just beer,&quot; Coulton said. &quot;Craft beer. That symbolized us because we&apos;re a craft golf ball company.&quot; Now, OnCore is in the selling and distribution part of the program. The balls go for $45 a dozen. Getting them on shelves in stores or golf shops is an equally daunting task but they&apos;re making slow progress. A successful appearance on CNBC&apos;s &quot;Power Pitch&quot; show helped. You can <a href="http://www.oncoregolf.com/" target="_blank">check them out online at www.OnCoreGolf.com</a>.</p> <p>The OnCore balls have a little different sound to them at impact, a slightly more metallic tink, but they seem to perform comparably to other popular brands. My limited testing was done in November with chilly temperatures and soft course conditions so I couldn&apos;t make any conclusions about how the ball checked up on the greens. I kind of liked the sound the ball made once I got used to it and I busted a couple of drives that went suitably far, so I didn&apos;t see any issue with distance.</p> <p>&quot;We had a pro win a section event here in Buffalo with it,&quot; Coulton said, &quot;and we had an 80-year-old woman write in. She made a hole-in-one with the ball, which she&apos;d just found on the course. You hear that kind of thing, it makes you feel good.&quot;</p> <p>It provides a warm feeling. In Buffalo, the Home of Golf, that&apos;s a good thing.</p> <p>And now for your Van Cynical Mailbag questions:</p> <p><b>VanCynical, Isn&apos;t Tiger&apos;s missing tooth the same one that turned brown after the hydrant incident?-Bustinpar via Twitter</b></p> <p>You mean the one that required oral surgery to repair and he had to leave town to get it done and wasn&apos;t seen for a few days? Nah, that never happened, remember?</p> <p><b>Van the Man Cynical, Think Tiger gets his intimidation aura back with skull mask and missing tooth? Maybe if he sharpened the other to a point?-Kris B via Twitter</b></p> <p>That might be worth trying, wearing a skull mask in competition. It would scare me if I was in that threesome. I think Tiger was just trying to escape the trappings of fame and wear a mask so he wouldn&apos;t be recognized and bothered. He just wanted to mingle with the people, probably. Big fame will wear you out.</p> <p><b>Van Cynical, Does a non-contending Tiger WD from Phoenix if the Sunday round won&apos;t finish in time to make the Super Bowl?-Brian Bailey via Twitter</b></p> <p>Not to worry. They&apos;ll hold up the kickoff until Tiger gets there. Or face Lindsey Vonn&apos;s wrath!</p> <p><b>Van Sickle, You&apos;re still pressuring me over my lack of progress on &quot;The Robot Who Won the Masters after WW III&quot;?-John Garrity via Twitter</b></p> <p>That&apos;s right, John. You&apos;d better hurry up and finish it that novel before WWIII actually starts. Clock is ticking, buddy.</p> <p><b>Vans, I gave up. Did they ever find anything?-Mark Greenhalgh via Twitter</b></p> <p>This was in response to my suggested T-shirt, &quot;I dug for treasure on Oak Island and all I got was this crummy TV show.&quot; They think they found something, Greenie, in the season two finale-a cavern and two rectangular-shaped possible entrances into tunnels, plus a rectangular object and something that looks like a box or chest. And now we&apos;ve got to wait until next season to find out if our favorite geniuses can figure out a way down there. My guess is, no. But I keep watching the show, thinking that something has to happen sooner or later, doesn&apos;t it?</p> <p><b>Van Comical, Since players can&apos;t throw stuff into the crowd now, who is the best choice to lead the #Yes chant on 16 in Phoenix?-Brian Baily via Twitter</b></p> <p>Bubba Watson and Ben Crane aren&apos;t afraid to put on a show at 16. I&apos;ll nominate them. If you can&apos;t throw stuff into the crowd, can you hand things carefully to spectators? Hold a raffle? Invite a fan down to play Plinko? Juggle stuff? Rule needs more clarity, man.</p> <p><b>Sickle, The tour says no swag-throwing at Phoenix&apos;s 16th hole. What&apos;s the penalty for ignoring this guidance?-kokomice via Twitter</b></p> <p>Probably a substantial fine, two knuckle raps and three demerits for misbehavior-but since it&apos;s pro golf, it&apos;s three Jimmy Demarets.</p> <div> <div class="component-video-player ui-video-player" data-componentid=""> <div class="video-player-content"> <div class="video-ratio"> <div class="video-wrapper" data-id="myExperience3993657816001" data-category="" data-subcategory="" data-title="tour-confidential-should-pga-be-worried-about-missing-big-names-phil-mickelson" data-bcid="3993657816001" data-width="300" data-height="100" data-playerid="2538399922001" data-playerkey="AQ~~,AAAAABjSC6U~,4Z3U_tH-Vly48f0a5CdEkba_lR7W0vMj" data-videoid="3993657816001" data-auto-start="false" data-https="" data-forcehtml="false" data-adtags="" data-nid="" data-vdprm="" data-vdins="" data-teach="" data-year="" data-tour="" data-feat="" data-brand="" data-ads_title="" data-zone=""> </div> </div> </div> <div class="inline"> <div class="inline-headline"> Tour Confidential: Should the PGA Be Worried About Missing Big Names? </div> <div class="inline-description"> With Phil Mickelson&apos;s announcement that he&apos;ll miss two consecutive tournaments, should the PGA be worried about missing out on the big-name players? </div> </div> </div> </div> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Gary Van Sickle</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:39bd58d879017391ea15916a101aa320" t="1421713952" feed="200853" position="4"><title>This Week's Hero? Tiger's Tooth. Zero? The World Ranking</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/heroes-and-zeros-sony-open</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/tiger-heroes-zeros_0.jpg?itok=wj31qCXG" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Jimmy-Walker.jpg?itok=LkEEW0Pb" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/MatiasDominguez_AP.jpg?itok=tJdfzj_f" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/PGA-Tour.jpg?itok=HOS26VXh" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Keegan-Bradley.jpg?itok=ETNqNDF4" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Phil-Mickelson.jpg?itok=ixWWVO_7" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Martin-Kaymer.jpg?itok=d7s_FKVx" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Jim-Furyk.jpg?itok=YFoOLrK-" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Pinevalley10_Larrylambrecht.jpg?itok=2J-HRhjp" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Anthony-Kim.jpg?itok=3xtFE5qx" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded">  <p><strong>1. <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/phil-mickelson-will-sit-out-pebble-pro-am-riviera" target="_blank">Phil’s schedule</a>. Is it too much to ask that just once his kids are on break the week of the Masters?</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Phil-Mickelson.jpg?itok=ixWWVO_7" /> </div> <p><strong>2. The Kayminator. There’s no middle ground in this guy’s game. When he blows a tournament, <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/martin-kaymer-blows-10-shoot-lead-gary-stal-wins-abu-dhabi-championship" target="_blank">he goes big</a>.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Martin-Kaymer.jpg?itok=d7s_FKVx" /> </div> <p><strong>3. <a href="http://www.owgr.com/" target="_blank">The World Ranking</a>. So JWalk and PReed have won a combined eight times in the last two years but neither is in the top 10, while Furyk and Sergio both are even though they specialize in not winning. If a system rewards numbing consistency over victories, something needs to change.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Jim-Furyk.jpg?itok=YFoOLrK-" /> </div> <p><strong>4. Pine Valley members. Their course got bumped from No. 1 in Golf Digest’s latest ranking of America’s best courses. My heart bleeds for them.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Pinevalley10_Larrylambrecht.jpg?itok=2J-HRhjp" /> </div> <p><strong>5. Anthony Kim. Are we sure he wasn’t in Honolulu <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/robert-allenby-kidnapped-beaten-and-robbed-honolulu-his-caddie-says" target="_blank">the night Robert Allenby got roughed up</a>?</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/20/Anthony-Kim.jpg?itok=3xtFE5qx" /> </div> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Alan Shipnuck</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:86a0ab9c48a4cf00e4e445425a2a5bfe" t="1421713951" feed="200853" position="5"><title>European Tour: What to Watch For at the Qatar Masters</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/european-tour-what-watch-commericial-bank-qatar-masters</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/20/sergio-garcia.jpg?itok=Now7FL9k" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Sergio Garcia is looking to defend his title this week at the Qatar Masters. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>The European Tour stays in the Middle East this week for the Commercial Bank Qatar Masters at Doha Golf Club.</p> <p>The tournament - the second of the three-event Desert Swing - has once again attracted a strong field, with many players making the short journey from Abu Dhabi to Qatar&apos;s capital.</p> <p>Indeed, three of the world&apos;s top six - Henrik Stenson, Justin Rose and Sergio Garcia - will be vying for glory when the event starts on Wednesday.</p> <p>Garcia overcame Fin Mikko Ilonen in a playoff at last year&apos;s Qatar Masters with a birdie at the third extra hole.</p> <p>In 2013, Chris Wood made a sensational eagle at the 72nd hole to deprive Garcia and South Africa&apos;s George Coetzee of a playoff berth.</p> <p>The Qatar Masters was staged for the first time in 1998 and Commercial Bank came on board as title sponsor in 2006.</p> <p>Adam Scott, Ernie Els, Stenson and Retief Goosen are among the players to have triumphed at Doha Golf Club during its 18-year association with the tournament.</p> <p>It&apos;s a course that yields a number of birdies when conditions are calm but a challenging layout when the wind blows, with numerous water hazards and a strong selection of par 3s to overcome.</p> <p><b>Four things to watch for at the Commercial Bank Qatar Masters</b></p> <p><b>Sergio Garcia: </b></p> <p>Doha Golf Club is a horses-for-courses type venue, and that statement is particularly applicable to the defending champion. Garcia has played the Qatar Masters every year since 2007 and his record in the event is exemplary. In the last eight years, he&apos;s recorded three top-five finishes, three further top 10s and two top 25s. The Spaniard also comes into the tournament in a rich vein of form. Impressively, he hasn&apos;t finished outside the top 30 on the PGA or European Tour since August 2014.</p> <p><b>Aggressive golf: </b></p> <p>The Qatar Masters is an event that typically sees a lot of birdies. Doha GC is a relatively open layout so the more aggressive players in the field will look to hit a lot of drivers and take the challenge to the golf course. Bigger hitters will also have an advantage on the long selection of par 5s, with three measuring in excess of 589 yards. If conditions are placid, look out for some low scores.</p> <p><b>The South Africans: </b></p> <p>It wouldn&apos;t be at all surprising if someone from South Africa lifted the trophy come Saturday evening. Charl Schwartzel comes into the tournament off the back of two top 10s in South Africa and Abu Dhabi, Branden Grace has a win and two top 20s in his last three starts, Ernie Els - a past winner in Qatar - returned a final-round 65 last week and George Coetzee has finished 5th and 2nd at Doha GC in the last two years.</p> <p><b>Form carrying over: </b></p> <p>With many parallels between the golf courses in Abu Dhabi and Qatar and similar conditions in both places, form often transfers between the two. As such, look out for those who fared well last week to play well once again. Thomas Pieters - who finished in a tie for 4th last week and looks like a real prospect - and Tyrrell Hatton are two to keep an eye on. Elsewhere, Rose, Morten Orum Madsen and Bernd Wiesberger will all be heading to Qatar full of confidence after top-12 finishes in Abu Dhabi.</p> <p> </p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Nick Bonfield/GOLF Monthly</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:4744d38c88c1ff7818eaf872303a8ef4" t="1421713934" feed="200853" position="6"><title>Brandt Snedeker: How to Rock a Visor on the Golf Course</title><link>http://www.golf.com/instruction/brandt-snedeker-how-rock-visor-golf-course</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/brandt-snedeker.jpg?itok=g1HYcEKT" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Brandt Snedeker is a visor-wearing regular on the PGA Tour. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>There are three good reasons to wear a visor rather than a baseball-style or bucket hat:</p> <p><strong>1.</strong> It lets heat escape the top of your head, instead of trapping it in.</p> <p><strong>2.</strong> A visor fits better if you have a lot of hair, like I do.</p> <p><strong>3.</strong> They&apos;re cool! Visors are modern and classic, if you wear the right one.</p> <p>A couple of pointers: <strong>Get the right size</strong>. Make sure the front of the visor [where the logo is] is proportionate to the size of your forehead. The bigger your forehead, the bigger the front of your visor should be. <strong>Set it straight</strong>. Pull the visor down so the brim sits just above your eyebrows, and check that the strap is parallel to the ground. If your visor tilts up, you won&apos;t get maximum sun protection -- a sunburn goatee looks bad on anyone. If it angles down, you&apos;ll resemble a riverboat blackjack dealer. Get the fit just right and you&apos;ll look like a true pro.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Brandt Snedeker</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:f1178dbb5b79ce2dba8b8c20c168d50b" t="1421697703" feed="200853" position="7"><title>The Club That Won: Jimmy Walker's Scotty Cameron Putter</title><link>http://www.golf.com/equipment/jimmy-walkers-winning-scotty-cameron-putter</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/19/WalkerPutterOpener.jpg?itok=tLbaRNG8" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images/Andy Lyons">Jimmy Walker won for the fourth time on the PGA Tour at the Sony Open in Hawaii. (Getty Images/Andy Lyons)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2014/12/01/video_imagesScottyCameronVideoTout_640.jpg?itok=xq1RLp5r" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Walkerputter_0.jpg?itok=6hdtn_nR" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Walkerputter2.jpg?itok=dsuswV4X" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Jimmy Walker’s victory at the Sony Open Sunday was a display in putting perfection. En route to a nine-shot win and a successful title defense, Walker finished first in strokes gained/putting, distance of putts made and putts per green in regulation. He also made four putts of 10 feet or longer on the back nine Sunday in Hawaii.</p> <p>Walker has been one of the best putters on the PGA Tour, finishing 11th in the stat in 2013-14 when he won three times throughout the season. However, Walker recently made a putting switch that has paid off hugely.</p> <div> </div> <p>Walker had been using a Scotty Cameron Tour Rat 2 Prototype for the majority of last season, but switched to a putter he had initially used in 2003-04 to begin 2015. The new (old) stick is a Scotty Cameron Newport 2 that had been one of Walker’s favorite putters, but became obsolete as his specs changed over time. The Newport 2 was restored and refurbished at the Scotty Cameron Custom Shop, a process that included adding 10-gram tungsten weights to the sole.</p> <p>Here’s a look at Walker’s Newport 2 that helped him win the Sony Open in Hawaii.</p> <div>  </div> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Walkerputter2.jpg?itok=dsuswV4X" /> </div> <p> </p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Brendan Mohler</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:95a971b8f2e1a29381d9ce565f4b4903" t="1421657436" feed="200853" position="8"><title>Tiger Woods Surprises Lindsey Vonn at Ski Race in Italy</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/19/tiger-woods-surprises-lindsey-vonn-ski-race-italy</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/19/tiger-woods-italy.jpg?itok=gUKPZ3mA" t="image/jpeg" author="Elvis Piazzi/AP">Tiger Woods, right, leaves the finish area of an alpine ski, women's World Cup super-G, in Cortina d'Ampezzo, Italy. Lindsey Vonn won a super-G Monday for her record 63rd World Cup victory (Elvis Piazzi/AP)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2014/11/29/gallery_images/tigerwoodslindseyvonn1_600.jpg?itok=3Ie3FC52" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Surprise, Lindsey!</p> <p>Tiger Woods was supposed to be practicing for his return to competition at the Phoenix Open, but instead, he was fulfilling his role as a supportive boyfriend, surprising girlfriend and professional skier Lindsey Vonn at the Olympia delle Tofane super-G event in Italy.</p> <p>This wasn&apos;t just any other event for Vonn. The 30-year-old won her 63rd World Cup event, breaking Austrian Annemarie Moser-Proell&apos;s 35-year-old record of 62 WC wins. Not bad for an athlete who missed nearly two years of competition -- including the 2014 Olympics in Sochi -- due to serious knee injuries.</p> <p>Woods had told Vonn that he would be watching online from Florida, where it was 5 a.m. at the time. But instead, a skeleton mask-clad Woods showed up in the finish area, where the two shared an emotional moment.</p> <p>According to the Associated Press:</p> <blockquote> <p><em>Vonn&apos;s boyfriend, Tiger Woods, surprised her in the finish area, where the pair shared an emotional embrace. Vonn exclaimed: &quot;No way!&quot; when she saw him.</em></p> <p><em>&quot;I didn&apos;t think this could get any better than yesterday with my entire family here but now with Tiger here this is unbelievable,&quot; Vonn said. &quot;I said, &apos;I can&apos;t believe you came.&apos; And he said, &apos;I told you.&apos;&quot;</em></p> </blockquote> <p>Both Woods and Vonn have demanding schedules ahead of them but have vowed to support each other in person as much as possible.</p> <p>&quot;It&apos;s tough to have two athletes competing at the same time, but he&apos;s definitely going to make something work,&quot; Vonn told the AP.</p> <p></p> <p>The trip wasn&apos;t without its mishaps. Woods&apos; agent, Mark Steinberg, <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/tiger-woods-front-tooth-knocked-out-videographer-agent-says" target="_blank">told the Associated Press that a videographer knocked out Woods&apos; front tooth during the event</a>.</p> <blockquote> <p class="p1"><em><span class="s1">He says during a crush of photographers at the awards podium, a media member with a shoulder-mounted video surged toward the stage, turned and hit Woods in the mouth. That&apos;s what knocked out the tooth.</span></em></p> </blockquote> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> <p> </p> <div class="media_embed" height="360px" width="640px"> <em height="360px" width="640px"><object classid="D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,47,0" height="360px" id="flashObj" width="640px"><param name="movie" value="http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&amp;isUI=1"></param><param name="bgcolor" value="#FFFFFF"></param><param name="flashVars" value="videoId=3998091336001&amp;playerID=2869183374001&amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAB9mw57HE~,xU4DCdZtHhuIakVdyH5VnUosMOtC9a9v&amp;domain=embed&amp;dynamicStreaming=true"></param><param name="base" value="http://admin.brightcove.com"></param><param name="seamlesstabbing" value="false"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><param name="swLiveConnect" value="true"></param><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always"></param><embed allowfullscreen="true" allowscriptaccess="always" base="http://admin.brightcove.com" bgcolor="#FFFFFF" flashvars="videoId=3998091336001&amp;playerID=2869183374001&amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAB9mw57HE~,xU4DCdZtHhuIakVdyH5VnUosMOtC9a9v&amp;domain=embed&amp;dynamicStreaming=true" height="360px" name="flashObj" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/shockwave/download/index.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash" seamlesstabbing="false" src="http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&amp;isUI=1" swliveconnect="true" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640px" /></object></em> </div> <p> </p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:08e9bed46e137dec9169297a4bbd8049" t="1421627557" feed="200853" position="9"><title>Tiger Woods' Front Tooth Knocked Out by Videographer, Agent Says</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/tiger-woods-front-tooth-knocked-out-videographer-agent-says</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Tiger-Woods-Tooth_0.jpg?itok=ChKarMNb" t="image/jpeg" author="Andrea Solero / EPA">Tiger Woods at the FIS Alpine Skiing World Cup in Cortina d'Ampezzo, Italy. (Andrea Solero / EPA)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>CORTINA D&apos;AMPEZZO, Italy (AP) -- Tiger Woods has another reason not to like cameras - his agent said it cost him a tooth.</p> <p>Woods made a surprise visit to Italy on Monday to watch girlfriend Lindsey Vonn capture her record 63rd World Cup race. The photo that generated all the buzz was Woods missing his front tooth.</p> <p>The culprit, according to his agent, was a camera.</p> <p>&quot;During a crush of photographers at the awards podium at the World Cup event in Italy, a media member with a shoulder-mounted video camera pushed and surged toward the stage, turned and hit Tiger Woods in the mouth,&quot; Mark Steinberg of Excel Sports said in an email. &quot;Woods&apos; tooth was knocked out by the incident.&quot;</p> <p>Race organizers said this was not reported to them. They added that Woods did request extra security and a snowmobile to exit the finish area, and organizers met both requests.</p> <p>&quot;I was among those who escorted him from the tent to the snowmobile and there was no such incident,&quot; Nicola Colli, the secretary general of the race organizing committee, told The Associated Press. &quot;When he arrived he asked for more security and we rounded up police to look after both him and Lindsey.&quot;</p> <p>Woods had been wearing a scarf with a skeleton pattern over the lower part of his face, sunglasses and a stocking cap. The photo was taken when the scarf was lowered.</p> <p>Woods first showed up in the athletes&apos; area when Vonn&apos;s father, Alan Kildow, escorted him in shortly after Vonn took the lead. The golfer then surprised Vonn and gave the skier an emotional hug.</p> <p>After about 10-15 minutes of standing near Vonn with her family, Woods was escorted into a white tent usually reserved for measuring athletes&apos; skis. He stayed there for nearly an hour, while the last lower-ranked skiers came down and during the podium celebration.</p> <p>After the podium celebration, Woods was escorted by police to a waiting snowmobile and taken away.</p> <p>Steinberg was traveling and did not say when Woods would have the tooth replaced. Golf&apos;s biggest -- and most photographed -- star returns to competition next week in the Phoenix Open, and his smile is sure to produce a stream of shutters from the cameras.</p> <p>Woods has a long history with cameras, often frustrated when shutters go off in the middle of his swing. One notable episode came during the Skins Game in 2002 when a corporate photographer clicked his camera as Woods was hitting a shot from the bunker on the final hole. His former caddie, Steve Williams, took the camera and set it on a steep bank of a pond so that it tumbled into the water.</p> <p>Another time, Woods was on the verge of his first bogey-free tournament at a World Golf Championship in Ireland when a camera clicked at the top of his tee shot. He made bogey, but still won.</p> <object classid="D27CDB6E-AE6D-11cf-96B8-444553540000" codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=9,0,47,0" height="360" id="flashObj" width="640"><param name="movie" value="http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&amp;isUI=1"></param><param name="bgcolor" value="#FFFFFF"></param><param name="flashVars" value="videoId=3998091336001&amp;playerID=2869183374001&amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAB9mw57HE~,xU4DCdZtHhuIakVdyH5VnUosMOtC9a9v&amp;domain=embed&amp;dynamicStreaming=true"></param><param name="base" value="http://admin.brightcove.com"></param><param name="seamlesstabbing" value="false"></param><param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"></param><param name="swLiveConnect" value="true"></param><param name="allowScriptAccess" value="always"></param><embed allowfullscreen="true" allowscriptaccess="always" base="http://admin.brightcove.com" bgcolor="#FFFFFF" flashvars="videoId=3998091336001&amp;playerID=2869183374001&amp;playerKey=AQ~~,AAAB9mw57HE~,xU4DCdZtHhuIakVdyH5VnUosMOtC9a9v&amp;domain=embed&amp;dynamicStreaming=true" height="360" name="flashObj" pluginspage="http://www.macromedia.com/shockwave/download/index.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash" seamlesstabbing="false" src="http://c.brightcove.com/services/viewer/federated_f9?isVid=1&amp;isUI=1" swliveconnect="true" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" width="640" /></object> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:61d7ee598caae3be7c7b8cd844a9153b" t="1421627544" feed="200853" position="10"><title>European Tour: 4 Things We Learned in Abu Dhabi</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/european-tour-4-things-we-learned-abu-dhabi</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/19/Gary-Stal-Main.jpg?itok=X7WzDgvb" t="image/jpeg" author="AP Photo">Gary Stal following his victory at the 2015 Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship. (AP Photo)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Martin-Kaymer-collapse.jpg?itok=eM0Cy3E5" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Gary-Stal.jpg?itok=JYicpurZ" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Rory-McIlroy-Abu-Dhabi.jpg?itok=fhEmcF2Y" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Thomas-Pieters.jpg?itok=sSK35BCK" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Gary Stal overcame an eight-shot 54-hole deficit to land his maiden European Tour title at the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship.</p> <p>The Frenchman played some fine golf at Abu Dhabi Golf Club and capitalized on an uncharacteristic collapse from Martin Kaymer, who snatched defeat from the jaws of victory.</p> <p>The German -- a three-time winner of the event -- led by ten strokes at one stage during the final round, but dropped five shots over the last 10 holes.</p> <p>That brought a host of players back into contention on an enthralling final day in Abu Dhabi, but Stal was the one who seized the initiative.</p> <p>After making six birdies in the first 11 holes, he sank a 20-footer at the 16th to move to the top of the leaderboard at 19-under-par.</p> <p>Rory McIlroy, playing in the group in front, needed an eagle at the last to reach the same mark, and almost holed his third from the sand on the closing par 5.</p> <p>He had to settle for birdie, though, and when Stal two-putted from the fringe on 18, only Kaymer could force a playoff.</p> <p>But the two-time major champion missed the fairway with his tee shot and failed to hole his third from 146 yards, handing the title to a tearful 22-year-old.</p> <p>&quot;It&apos;s really crazy and I&apos;m very happy to win this tournament. This morning, I was thinking about second place,&quot; said Stal. &quot;When I saw my name on the leaderboard, I started thinking, well, don&apos;t get excited, but I&apos;m very happy obviously. It&apos;s an incredible feeling.&quot;</p> <p><b>Four things we learned at the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship:</b></p> <p><b>1. It&apos;s not over until it&apos;s over</b></p> <div>  </div> <p>As we all know, golf is an inherently unpredictable and capricious sport. Still, no one was expecting Kaymer -- a two-time major champion and someone who&apos;d played inspired golf over the first 60 holes -- to implode like he did. After the three-time Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship winner birdied the fifth to move to 23-under-par, he was 1/500 with some bookmakers. Stal, meanwhile, was 1000/1. The rest, as they say, is history.</p> <p><b>2. Surreal win for Stal</b></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Gary-Stal.jpg?itok=JYicpurZ" /> </div> <p>Before the start of the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship, Gary Stal was 357th in the Official World Golf Ranking. Now, he&apos;s 102nd. The 22-year-old earned €379,798 for his victory in the desert, some €340,000 more than his previous biggest European Tour cheque. He&apos;s also added his name to the list of hugely talented Frenchmen to keep an eye on over the coming years, alongside the likes of Victor Dubuisson, Romain Wattel and Alex Levy. The latter, though, endured a torrid finish at Abu Dhabi Golf Club. He three-putted from no more than three feet on the final hole, costing himself more than €20,000 in the process.</p> <p><b>3. McIlroy&apos;s driving prowess</b></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Rory-McIlroy-Abu-Dhabi.jpg?itok=fhEmcF2Y" /> </div> <p>Rory McIlroy may have finished in second place -- his fourth top 5 in Abu Dhabi in the last five years -- but there were many positives to take from his performance. He hit 88.9% of greens in regulation and he continues to drive the ball better than anyone in the world. He struggled somewhat on the greens, but if he finds some form with the flatstick over the coming months, he&apos;ll be extremely difficult to beat at Augusta.</p> <p><b>4. The future&apos;s bright</b></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/Thomas-Pieters.jpg?itok=sSK35BCK" /> </div> <p>There&apos;s some exciting young talent developing on the European Tour at this moment in time. In fact, four of the top six players on the final Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship leaderboard were 24 years old or younger. Stal (22) claimed his first European Tour title, Thomas Pieters (22) earned the biggest cheque of his career, Dubuisson (24) continues to impress and Tyrrell Hatton (23) looks poised to register his first victory sooner rather than later.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Nick Bonfield / Golf Monthly</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:0b186138f016231de9b5597bd5615899" t="1421627544" feed="200853" position="11"><title>Dustin Johnson Has New Outlook, With Assist From Wayne Gretzky</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/dustin-johnson-has-new-outlook-his-game-and-his-life</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/19/Johnson-Gretzky.jpg?itok=EtjDqzqf" t="image/jpeg" author="Robert Beck / SI">In Wayne Gretzky, Dustin Johnson has a father figure who can teach him a thing or two about handling fame. (Robert Beck / SI)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/19/DJ-Wayne.jpg?itok=vsFISGjW" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>In a gated community northwest of Los Angeles, at an out-of-the way table at Sherwood Country Club, Dustin Johnson arrives for his first interview since he disappeared from the PGA Tour under murky circumstances five months ago. He comes prepared. His longtime agent, David Winkle, sits on one side. A public relations consultant sits on the other. A list of talking points Johnson has written down on a white sheet of paper sits in front of him. They include family, simple life and dedication. Between spits of dip, he delivers his lines with conviction. “Over these past four or five months I’ve really grown up,” he says, “and I am starting to become the person I want my kids to look up to.”</p> <p>Johnson, 30, is about to return from a leave that reminded everyone of the immaturity that’s undermined his development. He has won eight PGA Tour events and nearly $25 million, displaying boundless length off the tee, Houdini shotmaking and arguably the most pure talent this side of Tiger Woods. But Johnson has been defined as much by his failures as his victories: a meltdown while leading on Sunday at the 2010 U.S. Open; a penalty that cost him a spot in a playoff at the PGA Championship later that year; and a squandered chance at the ’11 British Open when he hit a ball out of bounds at the 14th hole on Sunday.</p> <p>Johnson’s recent hiatus began days before <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/dustin-johnson-suspended-pga-tour-after-positive-test-cocaine" target="_blank">a report from Golf.com last August</a> that he had been suspended by the Tour for failing a third test for recreational drugs -- two of which were for cocaine. Johnson and his p.r. team say he wasn’t suspended and are indignant that reports continue to circulate despite a denial from the Tour. Depending on when his fiancée, Paulina Gretzky, gives birth to their son, Johnson will return at Torrey Pines on Feb. 5 or the following week at Pebble Beach. “I’ll tell you this unequivocally,” says Paulina’s dad, NHL legend Wayne. “It’s the first time I can see him say, ‘Gosh, I really miss it, and when I get back I want it to be something special.’”</p> <p>Yet questions remain about the actual reason for Johnson’s absence, just as there were when he took a three-month break in 2012, which he said was because he tweaked his back while lifting a JetSki. His most recent exit also came less than two months before the Ryder Cup, and at fifth in the standings, he had all but locked up a spot on the U.S. team. Johnson says this respite was a choice to address “personal challenges.” He adds that he did not enter any kind of rehab, instead hiring a team of experts -- a life coach and several clinicians among them -- to help him better understand what drives him, how to handle stress and how to unlock his latent potential. “I did not have a problem,” he says when asked explicitly about cocaine. “It’s just something I’m not going to get into. I have issues. But that’s not the issue.”</p> <p>A day in the new life of Dustin Johnson typically begins around 6:30, when he and Paulina head up the street from their rented townhouse to her parents’ house for breakfast. They bring their dogs, Charlie, a black Labradoodle, and Daisy, a goldendoodle, for the half-mile drive along Sherwood’s immaculately manicured course, which sits at the base of the Santa Monica Mountains in Thousand Oaks.</p> <p>After some coffee and eggs Johnson works out with a trainer, hits the range and plays golf with a regular group of five to 10 friends that includes Wayne and his wife, Janet, who ride a cart reading &quot;Mr. and Mrs. Sherwood&quot; on the back. Dustin and Paulina return to her parents’ most nights for dinner. It’s a world away from the couple’s days as social-media superstars, their Instagram accounts filled with jet-setting adventures. Paulina, a model, is mostly known for racy pictures on Twitter and Instagram that often made their way to click-bait websites. These days she stays close to home and Dustin spends his free time running to the store to fulfill her pregnancy craving -- celery. Lots of celery. Their evenings typically end with a heavy dose of State of Affairs, Homeland or Sons of Anarchy. “Really simple,” Johnson says, hitting that talking point. “That’s what I’ve been working on, really simplifying everything. And her being pregnant makes it that much more easy to simplify things.”</p> <p>The simple question that will be answered when Johnson returns to the Tour will be whether, after mentoring from the Great One, he can become golf’s next great one. Johnson has been taking notes. How does Wayne act when fans approach him in a restaurant? (Graciously.) How does he handle the guys waiting at the private airport with 10 jerseys to sign? (He finds another exit.) How have he and Janet sustained a high-profile marriage for 26 years -- and raised five kids -- with little drama? (They work at it.) Gretzky laughs off a report that he sat Johnson down, scolded him and demanded he change his partying ways. He says anyone who knows him realizes that’s not his style. “People ask me now, ‘What do you do to replace hockey?’” Gretzky says. “I don’t. I can’t. And I tell Dustin, ‘You can’t replace golf or what you do and bring to the sport. Make sure you understand that, and don’t mess that up.’ ”</p> <p>In October, Wayne told Dustin on the 1st tee at Sherwood, “You should shoot the course record today, let’s do this.” Gretzky was so confident he made Johnson putt out his four-footers early in the round, so the score would be official. By the back nine Johnson was playing so well the other members stopped making small talk, treating him like a pitcher in the dugout working on a no-hitter. He finished with a course-record 61, shot 63 the next day and came back with another 61 the day after that. Johnson shrugs off the run, saying, “I wish I was playing in a golf tournament.”</p> <div>  </div> <p>What has most impressed the Sherwood group is Johnson’s demeanor. He has befriended kids on the driving range, giving them full-blown lessons. (Many have no idea who he is.) He is engaging with the members. Johnson has been characterized in the media as being quiet and aloof, but Janet believes he finally may be finding himself. “Maybe he wasn’t comfortable in his own skin before,” she says. “Maybe he felt a little alone out there. He’d go off with certain people and groups, and you don’t understand if they’re really your friends. Now, there’s no mistaking. Paulina loves him to death. We love him and support him. We don’t judge him. No one is perfect. What is perfect is if you can do it the right way.</p> <p>“Whether he made a few mistakes, that’s not my business. What the outcome is, that’s my business.”</p> <p>Growing up in South Carolina, Dustin Johnson drove a red Honda Civic hatchback. It was a stick shift with no radio, so he kept a boom box in the back seat to blast Nelly. “Had to have some tunes,” he says with a smile. He didn’t know how to drive a stick, but his father, Scott, told him, “If you want to go somewhere, you’ll learn real quick.”</p> <p>Johnson has done the same on the course, figuring things out as he goes along, stalling here and there. He was raised by divorced parents, bouncing between houses, asking Scott for things when his mother, Kandee, said no. “I knew how to get what I wanted,” he says. He wasn’t a great student at Dutch Fork High near Columbia, S.C., or at Coastal Carolina University. Instead, he took perverse pride in doing the minimum. “I could’ve made the time and got straight A’s,” he admits, “but I did just enough to make sure I was eligible to play golf.”</p> <p>No one has ever questioned Johnson’s athleticism: He has an effortless swing, his broad jump would be among the top percentile of NBA players and he could run drills at the NFL combine alongside elite receiver prospects. “I wasn’t doing everything I could, and it’s totally a parallel,” he says, referring to his lackluster approach in the classroom. “I was succeeding, but not to the potential I could if I really want. That’s a big reason why I needed to sit back and take a look at everything in my life.”</p> <p>Along the way he has had two significant legal issues. At 16, he was involved in the burglary of a handgun that was used in a murder. (He testified at trial, paid restitution for the burglary and was pardoned.) And in 2009 he was arrested for DUI. (The charge was dismissed, but he pleaded guilty to reckless driving.) The legal issues, the suspicious breaks from the Tour, the careless play on the golf course -- after being penalized at the 2010 PGA for grounding his club in a bunker, he said he had neglected to read the local rules sheet -- make skeptics question whether he can change.</p> <p>Last fall Johnson started by getting his body right. He was carrying 220 pounds -- “not a good 220” -- on his 6&apos; 4&quot; frame, so he dropped 20 through daily workouts with his trainer and has since put on 13 pounds of muscle. In sessions with his life coach and clinicians, Johnson discovered that he didn’t handle stress and anxiety well. “My way of getting rid of it was drinking or partying,” he says. “Yeah, that might work for that day or the next week, but eventually everything keeps piling up.” Johnson has sought other releases, from skiing to fishing to free diving. He cites a few examples of his changed behavior, such as turning down shots at Paulina’s baby shower. “Before I would’ve been like, Yep, I’m in, and let’s do another one.” He drank a beer or two at the Rose Bowl, but the night didn’t spiral into a party; he admits the DJ of old would have turned those two into a dozen. He says he has gone months without vodka -- his vice was Grey Goose and soda with a lime. He even ponied up $1,000 for a competition with Wayne and eight other Sherwood members to see who could go through January without drinking. So far, so good. “I don’t miss waking up with a hangover, and I didn’t drink very often,” Johnson says. “It was just when I did it was a little too much.”</p> <p>Part of Johnson’s self-evaluation involved tightening his inner circle -- Team Dustin, he calls it. He declines to say who was cut out, but he’s proud he has eliminated some of the clutter from his life. He gave his tricked-out 1976 Pontiac to his younger brother, Austin. He plans to store if not sell his black Aston Martin, which he paid nearly $300,000 for. His two Jet Skis and one of his boats are going up for sale.</p> <p>As he sheds his material items, Johnson hopes he can rid himself of the reputation of being an underachiever who never fully dedicated himself to the game. Until he delivers a major title and stretches of dominant play, the talking points will remain just that -- talk. “The mentality of being invincible is great when I’m playing golf,” he says. “But where I was struggling was when I wasn’t playing golf.”</p> <p>So why should we believe that Johnson is finally ready to become one of the world’s truly elite golfers? He’s 30 now. He’s in love. He’s about to become a father. He has guidance from and the support of a hockey legend and his wife. The Grey Goose has been shelved. The biggest obstacle in Johnson’s quest to become the best golfer in the world remains a familiar foe -- Johnson himself. “I don’t think I’ve even scratched the surface,” he says. “And that was a really big part of what I’ve been doing, to help myself reach that potential.”</p> <p>He has the talking points down. Now it’s time for his actions -- on and off the course -- to speak louder.</p> <p><em>This article appeared in the Jan. 26, 2015, issue of Sports Illustrated. Click <a href="http://subscription-assets.si.com/prod/assets/themes/magazines/SUBS/templates/velocity/site/si-digitaledition/login.html" target="_blank">here</a> for instant access to this week&apos;s issue.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Pete Thamel</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:430740306942a0f5d3afcb0f3efe379e" t="1421625600" feed="200853" position="12"><title>Nike Lunar Control 3 Golf Shoes: A Few of Our Favorite Things</title><link>http://www.golf.com/equipment/nike-lunar-control-3-golf-shoes-few-our-favorite-things</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2014/12/10/Nike-Lunar-Control-3-Shoes.jpg?itok=7TGxByr0" t="image/jpeg" author="Courtesy of Nike">Nike Lunar Control 3 Golf Shoes (Courtesy of Nike)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>With the advice and counsel of Rory McIlroy -- world No. 1 and owner of one of the game&apos;s most aggressive turns -- Nike has created a lightweight shoe with the kind of perimeter stability required to support players with swing speeds of 100 mph and up.</p> <p>To increase traction, an extra spike has been added toward the front of the foot, and the base has been widened to maximize contact with the ground. A synthetic microfiber upper helps repel water, while a full-length foam sole provides a soft, snug foundation.</p> <p>Available on Jan. 1. Consumers can begin to customize their Nike Lunar Control 3 <a href="http://www.nike.com/us/en_us/c/nikeid" target="_blank">via NIKEiD</a> on Jan. 12. <b>$210</b>.</p> <p><a href="http://www.golfsmith.com/search/nike-golf-shoes/_/N-69893+1132?tcode=gcom&amp;scode=GOLF14Q1&amp;utm_source=golf-com-shop&amp;utm_medium=partners" target="_blank"><span><strong>BUY your own Nike gear in our online store</strong></span></a></p> <p><em>This article appeared in the most recent issue of <b>SI Golf+ Digital</b>, our weekly e-magazine. Click <a href="http://subscription-assets.golf.com/prod/assets/themes/magazines/SUBS/templates/velocity/site/gf-digitaledition/library.html" target="blank">here</a> to read this week&apos;s issue and sign up for a free subscription.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:9bd161d69c08dab5d16657a30a029f71" t="1421541158" feed="200853" position="13"><title>Tour Confidential: The Return of Phil Mickelson</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/tour-confidential-return-phil-mickelson</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/Rory-McIlroy.jpg?itok=pCEDGU5u" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/Padraig-Harrington.jpg?itok=enIwLM8f" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p><em>Every Sunday night, Golf.com conducts an e-mail roundtable with writers from Sports Illustrated and Golf Magazine. Check in every week for the unfiltered opinions of our writers and editors and join the conversation in the comments section below.</em></p> <p><strong>1. Phil Mickelson starts his 2015 season this week at the Humana Challenge, but <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/phil-mickelson-will-sit-out-pebble-pro-am-riviera" target="_blank">he announced that he&apos;s skipping the AT&amp;T at Pebble Beach and the Northern Trust at Riviera</a>, two of his favorite events at two of his favorite courses. Is this a sign that Mickelson&apos;s easing into semi-retirement?</strong></p> <p><strong>Cameron Morfit, senior writer, Golf Magazine ( <a href="https://twitter.com/CameronMorfit" target="_blank">@CameronMorfit</a>)</strong>: I&apos;d say this is merely a sign that it&apos;s a very long season. Phil doesn&apos;t have to play Riviera and Pebble, just because he&apos;s won there, just like Tiger doesn&apos;t have to play Torrey Pines. These guys are of the age where even they realize it&apos;s not all about them. It&apos;s about vacations, rest, who has the kids that week, things like that. I&apos;d guess one or both will still be in the hunt late Sunday at the Masters.</p> <p><strong>Michael Bamberger, senior writer, Sports Illustrated</strong>: No, it&apos;s Phil making a grand family-first statement, and showing what we already know: that he is independently owned and operated.</p> <p><strong>Josh Sens, contributing writer, Golf Magazine ( <a href="https://twitter.com/JoshSens" target="_blank">@JoshSens</a>)</strong>: He&apos;s a professional golfer. He&apos;s been semi-retired for decades. Seriously, though, this is a progression of the cutbacks he&apos;s been making. But given that he&apos;s chosen these two events, you have to wonder if his health problems are flaring up again.</p> <p><strong>Jeff Ritter, senior editor, Sports Illustrated Golf Group ( <a href="https://twitter.com/Jeff_Ritter" target="_blank">@Jeff_Ritter</a>)</strong>: I see it as a sign that Phil cares about the U.S. Open, and completing a career grand slam, above all else this year. He normally rips up the West Coast Swing (he has six wins combined at Pebble and Riv, both of which he&apos;s skipping) in order to arrive at Augusta in peak form. I&apos;m sure he&apos;d still love to win Augusta, but it looks to me like he&apos;s saving something in the tank to peak mid-summer.</p> <p><strong>Joe Passov, senior editor, Golf Magazine ( <a href="https://twitter.com/joepassov" target="_blank">@joepassov</a>)</strong>: Not quite. I&apos;ll invoke what Chi Chi Rodriguez once said about Jack Nicklaus: &quot;He&apos;s a legend in his spare time.&quot; Jack cut back to the bare minimum number of PGA Tour events at an even younger age than Lefty, so this isn&apos;t unprecedented. It&apos;s puzzling that the best West Coast player since Johnny Miller would omit Pebble, where he&apos;s a four-time champ and L.A., where he&apos;s won twice, but he&apos;s citing &quot;family&quot; and that&apos;s fine by me. Phil&apos;s 44 years old, and has faced all kinds of issues in recent years. He&apos;s earned the right to do exactly what he wants.</p> <p><strong>Gary Van Sickle, senior writer, Sports Illustrated ( <a href="https://twitter.com/GaryVanSickle" target="_blank">@GaryVanSickle</a>)</strong>: No, it&apos;s a sign that Phil has a Super Secret Plan in motion. What&apos;s his plan? We&apos;re not smart enough to understand it. Trust in Phil.</p> <p><strong>2. Martin Kaymer <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/martin-kaymer-blows-10-shoot-lead-gary-stal-wins-abu-dhabi-championship" target="_blank">blew a 10-shot lead with 14 holes to play</a> to lose the Abu Dhabi Championship this week. Is this the biggest meltdown ever?</strong></p> <p><strong>BAMBERGER</strong>: It&apos;s way up there, but I will still take Palmer at the &apos;66 U.S. Open, leading by seven with nine to play, because the stakes were so much more significant. But Martin&apos;s thing here is epic and a definite keeper.</p> <p><strong>PASSOV</strong>: As impressively awful as Kaymer&apos;s implosion was, this won&apos;t make the Meltdown Hall of Shame. This was Abu Dhabi, not Augusta, and he found a couple of bushes with tee shots on the back nine. You need a bigger stage to earn &quot;biggest ever&quot; meltdown status. Arnold Palmer wasting a 7-shot lead with nine to play at the 1966 U.S. Open remains the standard, and Greg Norman&apos;s six-shot squandering at the 1996 Masters is a close second.</p> <p><strong>MORFIT</strong>: Biggest meltdown ever? That&apos;s a big title to be throwing around willy-nilly, and I think you have to consider the occasion, not just the size of the lead blown. I&apos;ll still take Greg Norman at Augusta.</p> <p><strong>VAN SICKLE</strong>: It&apos;s one thing for Jean Van de Velde to melt down but for a former World No. 1 and the current U.S. Open champion? That&apos;s remarkable. For now, we&apos;ll have to write it off to being early in the year -- this is still the golf season&apos;s equivalent to spring training. But, yikes.</p> <p><strong>RITTER</strong>: It&apos;s certainly the biggest meltdown for Kaymer, who historically has been an excellent front-runner. But the all-time list probably needs to come from the majors. Faldo over Norman at the ‘96 Masters still stands alone for me.</p> <p><strong>SENS</strong>: It was pretty colossal. But it&apos;s diminished by the stage. In that regard, I&apos;ll stick with Norman&apos;s meltdown at Augusta as the biggest.</p> <div>  </div> <p><strong>3. Rory McIlroy ended up second to winner Gary Stal in Abu Dhabi. He also <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/rory-mcilroy-makes-first-professional-hole-one-abu-dhabi" target="_blank">made his first hole-in-one in competition ever this week</a>. Do you expect McIlroy to pick up where he left off last year, and does anyone have a chance of catching him at No. 1?</strong></p> <p><strong>VAN SICKLE</strong>: I don&apos;t see anyone with enough firepower out there to match Rory and win enough to catch him in the world rankings. It would take a Kaymer or a Bubba Watson or someone to rack up three, four or five wins. It&apos;s always possible, of course, but who out there looks that potentially dominant? Not Kaymer at this moment.</p> <p><strong>BAMBERGER</strong>: Oh, sure -- if he stumbles and Patrick Reed or Jordan Spieth or Adam Scott do a Jimmy Walker imitation. But I&apos;d be surprised. Rory looks primed to pick up where he left off.</p> <p><strong>PASSOV</strong>: I fully expect Rory to keep the petrol pedal floored. Unless his legal issues derail him temporarily, I see no one catching him or even coming close. Tiger, please prove me wrong, and help catapult golf tournament results onto Page 1 again!</p> <p><strong>RITTER</strong>: Rory had a nice debut and certainly seems ready to pick up where he left off. His biggest hurdle to holding No. 1 all year might be the potential distraction around the court trial with his former management company. If he can handle that, he&apos;s your No. 1 on Dec. 31.</p> <p><strong>MORFIT</strong>: I&apos;d guess Rory will have a great year again, because he&apos;s pretty much past the most seismic upheaval in his life: total equipment change, moving to South Florida, etc. As soon as the lawsuit with Horizon is over with, he&apos;s free to think about nothing but his golf. That&apos;s a scary thought.</p> <p><strong>SENS</strong>: Anything can happen. But I think what used to applies to Woods applies to McIlroy&apos;s No. 1 ranking. The only thing that can stop him is a bad injury or a bad relationship.</p> <p><strong>4. Jimmy Walker <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/jimmy-walker-cruises-record-9-shot-victory-sony-open-hawaii" target="_blank">returned to his winning ways of early 2014 at the Sony Open in Honolulu</a>. What’s the reason for Walker’s emergence in his mid-30s as one of the Tour’s top American players?</strong></p> <p><strong>MORFIT</strong>: I credit his wife, Erin, for forcing the issue when Walker couldn&apos;t seem to get together with Butch Harmon to start transforming his game and taking him to the next level. And of course I credit Harmon himself. Walker&apos;s been a different player since the start of last season.</p> <p><strong>VAN SICKLE</strong>: Walker was slowed up by some injuries. You can credit his success to his driver -- he hits it fairly long and fairly straight -- and he&apos;s one of the better putters on tour. And, the biggest reason of all, he started working with Butch Harmon. The knowledge and the confidence he gained from Butch made the difference.</p> <p><strong>SENS</strong>: Two words: Butch Harmon</p> <p><strong>RITTER</strong>: Walker&apos;s emergence is hardly unprecedented. Three years ago we celebrated the mid-30s rise of Jason Dufner. Phil didn&apos;t win a major until he was 33. Some guys just take longer to figure it out. One thing is clear: Walker is here to stay.</p> <p><strong>BAMBERGER</strong>: I&apos;m not sure, but <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/jimmy-walker-tours-cut-making-machine-rocketing-world-rankings">it may have something to do with the alignment of Jupiter and Mars</a>.</p> <p><strong>PASSOV</strong>: The answer is in the stars.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/Padraig-Harrington.jpg?itok=enIwLM8f" /> </div> <p><strong>5. The PGA Tour <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/golfers-and-caddies-banned-throwing-stands-phoenix-open" target="_blank">won’t let players throw gifts to fans on the 16th hole at the Waste Management Phoenix Open</a>, two years after it banned caddie races on 16. Does the Tour need to bring more decorum/safety back to rowdy TPC Scottsdale or is it sucking the fun out of one of its most popular events?</strong></p> <p><strong>SENS</strong>: The latter. Silly decision. If the Tour were a frat party on turf every week, that would be another story. This is an entertaining exception. We have the other 51 weekends a year to keep our knickers in a bunch.</p> <p><strong>PASSOV</strong>: I haven&apos;t spoken to any of the sponsoring Thunderbirds in Phoenix yet, but this decision is a head-scratcher. I&apos;ve attended 25 Phoenix Opens, and everyone who competes or attends understands that the 16th hole is mayhem. It&apos;s one hole, in one tournament, all year. The recent tradition of tossing items into the crowd showed players&apos; creativity, it helped them connect with fans in a unique way and it added further to the tournament&apos;s aura. I heard nothing in the last 12 months to indicate that there were safety issues, though when you combine 80-degree sunshine and alcohol, hey, anything&apos;s possible. What would have been better than celebrating Phil Mickelson tossing footballs, with the city hosting the Super Bowl the same weekend?</p> <p><strong>MORFIT</strong>: No one will ever fault the WMPO for being &quot;not rowdy enough.&quot; The Tour rightly recognizes this party is always on the verge of being out of control, and could easily detract from the golf if not held somewhat in check.</p> <p><strong>BAMBERGER</strong>: It&apos;s tricky whenever there are issues of public safety, but I&apos;d let it all hang out at Phoenix and try to maintain some vestige of the game as it was played by Byron Nelson and Leonard Thompson everywhere else.</p> <p><strong>RITTER</strong>: This is only a guess, but I&apos;d bet a dollar that Scottsdale made this move in response to Tiger&apos;s participation in the event. Not that Woods asked for it, but imagine the frenzy in the bleachers if Woods tossed out a few stuffed Tigers? Someone could easily get hurt. Now imagine the backlash against Tiger if he didn&apos;t throw anything. Doubt Woods would sign up for that. In general the Tour could inject more fun in just about every other event on the schedule, but I think Scottsdale made the right move here.</p> <p><strong>VAN SICKLE</strong>: We&apos;ve seen a few bad things happen in others sports -- like baseball -- when fans fight for objects thrown into the stands. It&apos;s probably better to err on the side of safety. But in Phoenix, with a hole surrounded by mostly corporate boxes, they are walking a fine line between it being Fun City and it being just a boring par-3 surrounded by a bunch of box seats where nobody goes to anymore to have fun.</p> <p><strong>6. Jack Nicklaus turns 75 on Wednesday. Besides his surprising 1986 Masters victory, what&apos;s the most memorable Nicklaus moment?</strong></p> <p><strong>PASSOV</strong>: I was obsessed with Jack&apos;s 1978 British Open win at St. Andrews, simply because I coveted the sweater he was wearing in the final round, an argyle number of dark blue, light blue and white diamonds against a darker blue background. I vowed that if I ever saw a version of that sweater for under $300, I&apos;d buy one. Alas, another broken promise to myself. In truth, I&apos;ll go with the &quot;Jack is Back&quot; U.S. Open win at Baltusrol in 1980, when he outdueled Aoki, both men playing brilliantly. Of course, his five consecutive birdies -- including two chip-ins -- on 14-18 to win the 1978 Jackie Gleason Inverrary Classic is a close second.</p> <p><strong>SENS</strong>: It didn&apos;t endear him to the masses, but his U.S. Open win at Oakmont in &apos;62, beating the King in his home state.</p> <p><strong>VAN SICKLE</strong>: It wasn&apos;t that big in America at the time because the Ryder Cup wasn&apos;t that big over here, but his conceding the putt to Tony Jacklin to allow GB&amp;I to tie the U.S. in 1969 in an event that the Americans had laughably dominated was one of the game&apos;s most important moments in the 20th century. The Ryder Cup might have been in danger of going away for good if Jack hadn&apos;t conceded that putt. It was a gutsy call and a controversial call but history shows it was a brilliant call.</p> <p><strong>MORFIT</strong>: Two acts of sportsmanship also define Jack: The putt he gave at the Ryder Cup, and the draw he and Gary Player agreed to at the 2003 Presidents Cup. Nicklaus kept in mind that golf is a game, and he did whatever he could to make sure everyone went home with dignity intact. That&apos;s not a bad legacy to have, next to the 18 majors.</p> <p><strong>RITTER</strong>: My favorite Jack moments are the only times I&apos;ve seen him play in person -- the Masters Par-3 Contest and ceremonial opening tee shots. I always try to find a few quiet corners where I can hear him b.s. with Arnie and Gary, and interact with the fans. It&apos;s great. That reminds me, how many days until the Masters?</p> <p><strong>BAMBERGER</strong>: Four quickies: His play in the &apos;60 U.S. Open, in position to win as a 20-year-old amateur; everything about the Saturday finale at the &apos;77 Open at Turnberry; his T6 finish at Augusta at age 58; his let&apos;s-call-it-a-tie 2003 captaincy of the U.S. team at the Presidents Cup in South Africa. Plus, his response to Tiger&apos;s lady problems: &quot;It&apos;s none of my business.&quot; Pure class, for about 55 years now. He&apos;s about as sharp at 75 as a person can be. Mazel tov, Jack.</p> <p><em>The Tour Confidential roundtable continues Monday on our weekly show hosted by Jessica Marksbury. Tweet her your questions <a href="https://twitter.com/Jess_Marksbury" target="_blank">@Jess_Marksbury</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Golf.com Staff</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:014f1de3ef4ac4ea7f967224241cb868" t="1421541155" feed="200853" position="14"><title>Meet Bailey Mosier, the New Face of Golf Channel's Morning Drive</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/meet-bailey-mosier-new-face-golf-channels-morning-drive</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/18/010715_MD_MorganPressel_321.JPG?itok=ZhDKybPr" t="image/jpeg" author="Jessica Danser / Golf Channel">LPGA Tour pro Morgan Pressel (second from left) joins Lauren Thompson, Paige Mackenzie and Bailey Mosier on the set of 'Morning Drive.' (Jessica Danser / Golf Channel)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p><em>Bailey Mosier, the new face of &apos;Morning Drive,&apos; Golf Channel&apos;s flagship program, sounds off on her first few days on set, rookie hazing and the state of her golf game.</em></p> <p><strong>How have your first few days at Morning Drive been?</strong></p> <p>Exciting! I mean, I was really nervous for the first morning, and then I got out there on the set, and it was really nice that I already new Damon [Hack] and Lauren [Thompson] and Paige [Mackenzie] and Chris [DiMarco] and had a rapport with them, so once I was actually on the set, within 10 minutes of going live, I really didn’t feel nervous at all. So, surprisingly, it was not as intimidating as I would have thought. And everyone had really positive feedback, which is super nice and amazing that everyone’s reached out and been so happy for me.</p> <p><strong>You have a great cast of characters on the show, and there seems to be a lot of good-natured ribbing that goes on. Has there been any rookie hazing that you wish to report?</strong></p> <p>[Laughs] I was expecting it, and I did not get it. So I am thrilled about that. I was prepared, and I thought it was coming, but it hasn’t yet.</p> <p><strong>You’re new to Morning Drive, but you’ve been with Golf Channel for quite some time as an editor on the website. How would you say your day-to-day working life has changed, and what’s it going to look like going forward?</strong></p> <p>I’m actually doing everything that I did last year in addition to appearing on Morning Drive. So I’m still editing and writing for the website on certain days, and I’m still doing “Grill Room” and “Big Breakdown,” but I’m hoping that as the year goes on, and as I get more comfortable and better, that my duties will narrow to really only focus on on-air stuff. So, hopefully that day is coming, but right now I’m still juggling everything.</p> <p><strong>As the newest cast member, what do you think you bring to the show? Where does your personality fit in?</strong></p> <p>That’s a good question. I think I’m kind of a 50/50 split of serious and fun. I’m writing everything that I’m saying myself, and they’ve already said that they love my writing, and they love that it’s fun, and it’s loose, and it’s kind of quirky. But I can be serious too, so I don’t know what role I actually fill. Maybe it’s still evolving, and we’ll have to ask other people how they would characterize me.</p> <p><strong>You played four years of college golf at Old Dominion, you were team captain, and you still play. How’s your game at the moment?</strong></p> <p>A couple of months ago I shot 75. That’s not normal, but it happened! So, you know, I can do that. I play maybe a couple times a month. I don’t practice. I’m not a ball beater. It’s not my thing. I can still break 80 every once in a while, which is fun enough. I still love to play.</p> <p><strong><a href="https://twitter.com/BirdieBaileyGC" target="_blank">If your social media channels are any indication</a>, you seem to have an affinity for puns. Where does that come from?</strong></p> <p>Having worked at Golf Channel writing headlines for four years, it’s really what kind of started that, and the more I did it, and the better I got, the more I fell in love with it. And, you know, people compliment me on that, and it encourages me to be as punny and clever as I can. So it’s a snowball effect. A lot of them are on the spot, but any time I read or see something, and I think, “Ooh, that’s funny or clever,” I store it away.</p> <p><strong>What’s the best part about hosting a morning show on Golf Channel?</strong></p> <p>Morning Drive is really cool because it’s kind of the premiere show on Golf Channel, and it’s the show that a lot of resources are put into, and we really want to make it a destination show for players. It’s just fun to be a part of what everyone’s talking about. The whole golf world watches the show, and that’s where [the players] want to be. As much as we’re excited to have them on, they are equally as excited to be here with us.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Jessica Marksbury</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a57f120dc678bc27b4769f6b66be92a4" t="1421541154" feed="200853" position="15"><title>Martin Kaymer Blows 10-Shot Lead in Abu Dhabi; Gary Stal Wins</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/martin-kaymer-blows-10-shoot-lead-gary-stal-wins-abu-dhabi-championship</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/kaymer.jpg?itok=PE6EN9CO" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Martin Kaymer takes a drop on the ninth hole during the final round of the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship. He made a double-bogey 6 on the hole. (Getty Images)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/stal.jpg?itok=D-QReqKZ" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates -- Gary Stal of France came from 10 shots back to capitalize on an improbable meltdown by Martin Kaymer and win the Abu Dhabi Championship after a frantic final round on Sunday.</p> <p>Kaymer looked like cruising to a fourth title in Abu Dhabi after making three birdies in his opening four holes to extend his six-stroke lead from overnight, only to drop six shots in seven holes around the turn.</p> <p>The No. 357-ranked Stal pounced with six birdies from Nos. 4-11 and held himself together down the stretch, picking up another shot at the 16th to capture his first European Tour title. He shot a 7-under 65 and was 19-under 269 overall.</p> <p>Kaymer shot 75 for a 17-under total and third place. When he teed off on No. 6, he was 10 shots clear on 23 under -- and only a shot off his record score around the National Course.</p> <p>&quot;A little shocked, surprised,&quot; Kaymer said. &quot;I don&apos;t know how to put it into words.&quot;</p> <p>Top-ranked Rory McIlroy had a 66 to finish a shot behind Stal in second, where he has now placed four times in Abu Dhabi.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://www.golf.com/leaderboard/tourney/L562/yr/2014" target="“blank”">LEADERBOARD: Final Results From The Abu Dhabi Championship</a></strong></p> <p>Kaymer, a two-time major winner, is renowned as one of the best front-runners in golf and had been in supreme form in his first tournament of the year with rounds of 64, 67 and 65. He hadn&apos;t made a bogey since the 12th hole on Thursday and McIlroy even said Kaymer was &quot;playing his own tournament.&quot;</p> <p>After birdies at Nos. 1, 2 and 4, Kaymer&apos;s final round started to unravel when he made a bogey at No. 6 and then a double bogey at No. 10 after being forced to take a drop when his drive landed under a bush.</p> <p>Kaymer lost the lead he had held since the first round when another drive wound up at the base of a bush on No. 13. A drop gave him a poor lie in the sandy wasteland and after chipping out into the fairway, he scuffed his approach shot 10 yards short of the green. He two-putted for a triple bogey and Stal was in front for the first time.</p> <p>&quot;When I saw the leaderboard on the fifth hole, I saw Martin Kaymer on 23-under par,&quot; said a stunned Stal. &quot;I couldn&apos;t believe it when I saw he was (17 under) after 15 holes.&quot;</p> <p>Stal, playing in the group in front of Kaymer, sank a 25-foot birdie putt on the 16th to move two shots ahead of Kaymer and McIlroy. Stal&apos;s approach to the 18th was tentative and landed in the rough to the right of the green, but he got up and down in two.</p> <div>  </div> <p>Kaymer, who won in Abu Dhabi in 2008, &apos;10 and &apos;11, needed to eagle the last for a playoff but he only managed a par.</p> <p>&quot;I can&apos;t believe this,&quot; said Stal, whose best previous finish was fifth.</p> <p>Belgium&apos;s Thomas Pieters (70) and Victor Dubuisson (67) tied for fourth on 16 under.</p> <p><em>Is Martin Kaymer blowing a 10-shot lead the biggest Sunday golf collapse ever? Join the conversation in the comments section below.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:dd858aee1a4f1d436308cb12d4717e0d" t="1421541153" feed="200853" position="16"><title>Jimmy Walker Cruises to 9-Shot Victory at Sony Open in Hawaii</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/jimmy-walker-cruises-record-9-shot-victory-sony-open-hawaii</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/18/Jimmy%2520Walker.jpg?itok=5QjDqT-q" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Jimmy Walker tees off on the third hole during the final round of the Sony Open in Hawaii. (Getty Images)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2015/01/16/SonyOpenwide_0.jpg?itok=J3WTAwCO" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>HONOLULU (AP) -- At least Jimmy Walker is leaving Hawaii with one trophy.</p> <p>Six days after losing a tournament on Maui he felt he should have won, Walker turned in a command performance Sunday on Oahu. He blew away the field with a 7-under 63 to win the Sony Open for the second straight year.</p> <p>His fourth career victory was the most impressive of all. On a course that lends itself to a free-for-all, Walker shot 62-63 on the weekend and never gave anyone much of a chance, winning by a tournament-record nine shots. The previous record was seven shots, last set in 2000 by Paul Azinger.</p> <p>Walker became the first repeat winner at the Sony Open since Ernie Els in 2004.</p> <p>Scott Piercy closed with a 66 to finish alone in second. Matt Kuchar, who started the final round two shots out of the lead, didn&apos;t make a birdie and shot 71 to tie for third with Harris English and Gary Woodland, who each had a 67. Kuchar ended his streak of 255 rounds on the PGA Tour with at least one birdie.</p> <p>But this was Walker&apos;s show, and it couldn&apos;t have happened at a better time. Walker had a three-shot lead with five holes to play at Kapalua last Monday when he wound up losing to Patrick Reed in a playoff at the Tournament of Champions. With a quick turnaround, he quickly put it behind him.</p> <p>&quot;I really wanted to finish out the day like I didn&apos;t do last week,&quot; Walker said.</p> <p>He finished at 23-under 257.</p> <p>The text message Sunday morning from swing coach Butch Harmon was the same thing caddie Andy Sanders said over every putt: &quot;Don&apos;t let up.&quot;</p> <div> </div> <p>The decisive moment came at the par-4 eighth hole. Walker and Kuchar both opened with seven straight pars, and Walker stuffed his approach to 3 feet for birdie. Kuchar pulled his tee shot into the royal palms, punched out short of the green and made bogey.</p> <p>That two-shot swing gave Walker a four-shot lead, and he was on his way.</p> <p>Walker made all seven of his birdies over the final 11 holes, and he couldn&apos;t miss on the back nine. He took a total of 20 putts on the back nine at Waialae in the third and fourth rounds. And even with a big lead, he kept grinding away over putts he didn&apos;t need to make.</p> <p>It was the largest margin of victory on the PGA Tour since Brian Gay won at Hilton Head by 10 shots in 2009. This was more reminiscent of the last time someone lost in a playoff, and then won the next week. That was Kyle Stanley in 2012, though the circumstances were entirely different.</p> <p>Stanley made triple bogey on the last hole at Torrey Pines and then lost in a playoff. He won Phoenix the following week with a great rally. Walker didn&apos;t do that much wrong at Kapalua except for one bad swing off the tee and failing to make a few putts. Still, the loss stung, and he was more than happy to head home to Texas for a two-week break with another trophy.</p> <p>&quot;He&apos;s one of the hottest players in the world,&quot; Piercy said after his round, when Walker was pulling away. &quot;What he&apos;s done the last year or two years, nobody&apos;s catching him. It&apos;s just a cake walk.&quot;</p> <p>Walker didn&apos;t treat it like one, which might be why he won by such a healthy margin.</p> <p>It was his fourth win in his last 32 starts, and he should move up to No. 13 in the world ranking. During his two-week stay in Hawaii, Walker averaged 66 each round and picked up just under $1.7 million. Most importantly, he&apos;s going home with another trophy.</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:cc984703d56a4ccc53b3a695caadbbe8" t="1421541152" feed="200853" position="17"><title>The Right Way to Fist-Pump on the Golf Course</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/jason-day-right-way-fist-pump-golf-course</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/18/jasonday_fistbump.jpg?itok=h6_PEb04" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Jason Day celebrates his win at the 2014 Match Play Championship with a fist pump. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>I stay pretty calm during the course of play, but there&apos;s no harm in wearing your emotions on your sleeve following a great shot. For the cool way to celebrate, try the &quot;biceps-curl&quot; fist pump. Keep your elbow close to your side, clench your fist, and pump slightly–just enough to savor the moment, but without showing up your opponent. Your fist should remain below your shoulder unless you win a major, otherwise, you&apos;ll lose friends fast. Some other celebratory guidelines:</p> <p>1. Don&apos;t celebrate bogeys. That&apos;s complete bush league.</p> <p>2. You can get pumped about pars, but do it internally. We tip caps on pars, but mostly to acknowledge the applause. If your playing partners offer praise, a simple &quot;thanks&quot; is respectful.</p> <p>3. Celebrate away from your opponent.</p> <p>If you do it straight to his face, you may have an adversary for life.</p> <p>4. Once you celebrate -- five to 10 seconds, max --stop! Let it go and move to the next shot. Good emotions can cloud your focus as easily as bad ones.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Jason Day</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a4f4c40ed54b41f29a90d25e0f65d10e" t="1421541144" feed="200853" position="18"><title>Adam Scott on How to Look Cool in Sunglasses on the Course</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/adam-scott-how-look-cool-sunglasses-course</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/18/scott_shades.jpg?itok=oPK58kwi" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Adam Scott at the 2014 Australian PGA Championship. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Sunglasses are cool. With the right pair, you can miss 14 fairways and still look every bit the &quot;player.&quot; I&apos;ve been wearing them for about three seasons, and it&apos;s catching on. Even Justin Rose—about as traditional as you can get—plays with shades. They seem to match the athletic-driven style of today&apos;s clothing, and there&apos;s a big benefit to shielding your irises from six hours of direct sunlight.</p> <p>My advice: Save your Wayfarers for non-golf days. Go with a modern frame style that&apos;s both lightweight and wide enough to provide full protection. I wear several models from Oakley, mostly the Flak Jacket [left]. When trying on a pair, make sure the bottom edge of the frame or lens doesn&apos;t cut off your view of the ball when you look down at address. And ask if the lenses are polarized. Some lenses are so good they can actually increase depth perception, making it easier to read greens.</p> <p>Oh, and never rest your shades on the bill of your cap when you take them off. Wrap them around the back instead. That&apos;s the Tour way. It looks cool, and it avoids covering your cap&apos;s logo—critical for keeping sponsors happy.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Adam Scott</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:9eaf5d48d84f1ba57054c3d60f8e8c70" t="1421524822" feed="200853" position="19"><title>Bubba Watson's General Lee Signed by 'Bo Duke' at Scottsdale Car Show</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/17/bubba-watsons-general-lee-signed-bo-duke-barrett-jackson-car-show-3</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/17/generallee_1.jpg?itok=JfNHqa4f" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">The 'General Lee' owned by Bubba Watson during the second round of the 2012 Waste Management Phoenix Open at TPC Scottsdale. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>If Bubba Watson’s favorite week of the year is the Masters, where he’s won twice, his second favorite might be the Barrett-Jackson Collectible Car Auction in Scottsdale, Ariz., <a href="http://www.golf.com/scorecard/2012/01/23/bubba-watson-buys-dukes-hazzard-car-110000/" target="_blank">where he famously bought the “Dukes of Hazzard” General Lee 1969 Dodge Charger for $110,000 in 2012</a>.</p> <p>Watson was back at the 2015 car show this week and this time <a href="http://www.golf.com/2015/01/09/bubba-watson-auction-classic-car" target="_blank">he auctioned off his 1939 Cadillac LaSalle C-Hawk Custom Roadster</a> for $410,000 to raise money for <a href="http://birdiesforthebrave.org/" target="_blank">Birdies for the Brave</a>, an organization founded in 2006 by Phil Mickelson and Amy Mickelson to help military families. Watson’s father was a Green Beret who served in Vietnam.</p> <p>&quot;It&apos;s an honor to support the Green Beret Foundation and Birdies for the Brave, who do so much to give back to members of our U.S. Armed Forces and their families,&quot; Watson said when he donated the car.</p> <p>At the show, Watson also got his “General Lee” signed by the original Bo Duke boy -- actors John Schneider. Here are some highlights from the car show via Watson’s Instagram posts:</p> <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-version="4"> <div> <div> <div>   </div> </div> <p><a href="https://instagram.com/p/x7cDgJBH4s/" target="_top">The General Lee getting signed by Bo Duke/John Schneider today at @barrett_jackson! #wahooo #dukesofhazzard #notforsale</a></p> <p>A photo posted by Bubba Watson (@bubbawatson) on Jan 16, 2015 at 12:45pm PST</p> </div> </blockquote> <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-version="4"> <div> <div> <div>   </div> </div> <p><a href="https://instagram.com/p/x5jPJOBH51/" target="_top">Played golf with &quot;BO Duke&quot; today... I mean John Schneider!! #Legend</a></p> <p>A photo posted by Bubba Watson (@bubbawatson) on Jan 15, 2015 at 7:09pm PST</p> </div> </blockquote> <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-version="4"> <div> <div> <div>   </div> </div> <p><a href="https://instagram.com/p/x8FgDShH7T/" target="_top">Said goodbye to my 39&apos; Cadillac tonight but raised some good money for @BirdiesfortheBrave #BarrettJackson #410Ktomilitarycharities #givingback #greatnight</a></p> <p>A photo posted by Bubba Watson (@bubbawatson) on Jan 16, 2015 at 6:47pm PST</p> </div> </blockquote> <p> </p> <p>Watson will start his season at the Humana Challenge in Palm Springs, Calif., next week. No word yet on what he’ll be driving.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Mike Walker</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a5b566733fdc97fb06a551207755852d" t="1421454759" feed="200853" position="20"><title>Jimmy Walker shoots 62 and takes Sony Open lead</title><link>http://www.golf.com/walker-shoots-62-and-takes-sony-open-lead-0</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/17/ap_images/201501172113763944383.jpg?itok=uGOzLEhm" t="image/jpeg" author="AP Photo/Hugh Gentry">Jimmy Walker hits out of a bunker on the 17th green during the third round of the Sony Open golf tournament on Saturday. (AP Photo/Hugh Gentry)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2015/01/16/SonyOpenwide_0.jpg?itok=J3WTAwCO" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>HONOLULU -- Defending champion Jimmy Walker one-putted his last 11 holes Saturday on his way to an 8-under 62, giving him a two-shot lead in the Sony Open and a chance to become the first back-to-back winner since 2004.</p> <p>On a day in which six players had at least a share of the lead at some point, Walker began his surge with a wedge to 5 feet on the eighth hole. He twice saved par, escaped with a bogey after two shots from a plugged lie in a bunker on the 17th and made birdie everywhere else.</p> <p><strong><a href="http://www.golf.com/leaderboard/2015/pga/sony-open-hawaii-0" target="“blank”">LEADERBOARD: JIMMY WALKER LEADS SONY OPEN</a></strong></p> <p>It was reminiscent of his final round at Waialae a year ago when he raced past a crowded field with key putts. That gave him a victory. This only gave him a chance to become the first repeat winner of the Sony Open since Ernie Els.</p> <div> </div> <p>Matt Kuchar, one of three players tied for the lead at the start of Saturday, birdied two of his last three holes for a 68 and was two shots behind.</p> <p>Walker was at 16-under 194, and he knows as well as anyone that this tournament is just getting started.</p> <p>&quot;Somebody is shooting a low round every day, and you never know where it&apos;s going to come from,&quot; Walker said. &quot;So you&apos;ve got to go out with the expectation you&apos;ve got to shoot a good score tomorrow.&quot;</p> <p>Without the strong wind typical of this tournament, there has been a score of at least 62 every round. That led Kuchar to say that anyone within six shots of the lead is still a threat.</p> <p>If that&apos;s the case, this could very much be up for grabs.</p> <p>Brian Harman (64) and Troy Merritt (67) were three shots behind, while Tim Clark (68) and Justin Thomas (70) were another shot behind.</p> <p>The 21-year-old Thomas, playing in the final group on the weekend for the first time, twice made key putts to turn double bogeys into only bogeys. He was tied for the lead through 12 holes until going well long on the 13th and scratching out a bogey, then dropping another shot on the 16th before closing with a birdie.</p> <p>Max Homa, a former NCAA champion from Cal, had a 63 and was five shots behind.</p> <p>Walker, however, has been steady and good during his two-week stay in paradise. This was his 13th consecutive under-par round in the Aloha State, and he was tied for the 54-hole lead last week at Kapalua in the Tournament of Champions before losing to Patrick Reed in a playoff.</p> <p>Walker said the loss stung, though he was helped by the short turnaround. And playing good golf puts last week even further in the past.</p> <p>Even so, he thought he was losing ground when he was only 1-under par for the day going to the eighth hole. He made his birdie at No. 8 and turned to caddie Andy Sanders and said, &quot;Let&apos;s get going.&quot; And they did.</p> <p>The key putt was a 12-footer at the par-5 ninth to keep his momentum, and a 20-foot birdie putt on the 10th. Just like that, he was back in the game, and Walker poured it on from there. Only after a tap-in birdie at the 15th did it dawn on him that he had been making a lot of putts.</p> <p>&quot;I kind of went back through it and I counted eight (one-putts), and then when I hit it up on the green on 16 I thought, &apos;This is going to be a tough one to keep the streak going,&apos;&quot; Walker said.</p> <p>From 30 feet, the putt was in the center of the cup.</p> <p>Walker stretched his lead to as many as four shots until he caught a plugged lie in the bunker on the 17th, took two to get out, and then made a 5-foot bogey putt. He escaped trouble from a palm tree on the par-5 18th hole, hit his third shot from 210 yards into 10 feet and finished in style.</p> <p>Webb Simpson, who joined Kuchar and Thomas atop the leaderboard through 36 holes, finally struggled to make putts and shot 72 to fall six shots behind.</p> <p>Kuchar three-putted the seventh green for bogey to fall to 1 over on his round, and that was the last shot he dropped. He didn&apos;t make enough birdies to get back into the lead, but he made enough to at least give himself a chance.</p> <p><strong>DIVOTS:</strong> David Hearn made a 10-foot birdie putt on his last hole that knocked five players out of the 54-hole cut. Seventy players made the Saturday cut at 3-under 207, a group that did not include 16-year-old Kyle Suppa, a junior at Punahou School. Suppa shot 71 and missed by two shots. ... Justin Thomas was given relief from the out-of-bounds fence left of the ninth fairway. Because it&apos;s a temporary fence — large net that can blow into a player&apos;s swing — the tour staff allowed for relief this week. ... Thomas is the only player within four shots of the lead who has not broken par in every round.</p> <p><em>Do you think Jimmy Walker will win back-to-back Sony Opens on Sunday? Join the conversation in the comments section below.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:7eb68d5e553c50777e93acd29a8a34af" t="1421454737" feed="200853" position="21"><title>Martin Kaymer Blows Past Rory McIlroy in Abu Dhabi</title><link>http://www.golf.com/kaymer-turning-abu-dhabi-championship-procession</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/17/ap_images/201501170413151991676.jpg?itok=1pzfRLP0" t="image/jpeg" author="AP Photo">Martin Kaymer of Germany tees off on the 3rd hole during the third round of the HSBC Golf Championship in Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates, on Saturday. (AP Photo)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates -- Martin Kaymer turned what promised to be an exciting weekend duel with Rory McIlroy into a procession at the Abu Dhabi Championship.</p> <p>Seeking a fourth title in eight years in Abu Dhabi, Kaymer shot a 7-under 65 in the third round on Saturday to extend his overnight lead from one stroke to six. He moved to 20-under 196 overall -- a record-low total here after 54 holes.</p> <p>The U.S. Open champion&apos;s pace was too hot for McIlroy, whose putting failed to match his tee-to-green play as he shot 71. The top-ranked McIlroy cut a forlorn figure at the end of his round, having dropped eight shots behind Kaymer and going from third place into a share of fifth.</p> <p>( <strong><a href="http://www.golf.com/leaderboard/2015/euro/abu-dhabi-hsbc-golf-championship-0" target="“blank”">Leaderboard: Kaymer Leads Abu Dhabi Championship by Six Shots</a></strong>)</p> <p>&quot;I feel like punching myself,&quot; said McIlroy, who only missed two fairways and one green in regulation all day. &quot;I&apos;m going to try to win the other tournament -- he (Martin) is playing different golf than everyone else.&quot;</p> <p>Belgium&apos;s Thomas Pieters shot 70 to stay in second place but his chances of a first win on the European Tour were virtually dashed by another exhibition from Kaymer on a National Course for which he has a great affinity.</p> <p>The numbers Kaymer is putting up in the United Arab Emirates capital are mind-boggling. He is 107 under here in his last 31 rounds, hasn&apos;t dropped a shot in 43 holes and can break his record score of 24 under -- set in 2011 -- with a 67 or less on Sunday.</p> <p>Kaymer&apos;s three wins in Abu Dhabi -- the opening event of the year for many players -- came in 2008, &apos;10 and &apos;11 and he also has a second and fifth place.</p> <p>The German birdied five of his first eight holes and somehow escaped dropping a shot for the first time since Thursday after hitting his second shot at No. 10 into a bush. He took a drop, chipped from the desert into a greenside bunker, only to find the cup from the sand for the second straight day on that hole.</p> <p>It brought a fist pump from Kaymer, who birdied Nos. 11 and 13 before parring his way home on a third straight day of sunny skies and just a slight breeze. He opened the tournament with rounds of 64 and 67.</p> <p>&quot;I&apos;m surprised the way I have played,&quot; said Kaymer, who took nearly a month off around Christmas and admitted to being rusty in practice in the 10 days before Abu Dhabi. &quot;I had a little bit of a bad conscience coming here because I didn&apos;t practice as much as I did in the past.&quot;</p> <p>&quot;Hopefully I can stay in the 20s, that&apos;s the first goal,&quot; he added, looking ahead to Sunday. &quot;I&apos;m not really thinking of the record. To me, it is important to win the golf tournament.&quot;</p> <p>McIlroy, who started two shots behind Kaymer, had been looking forward to a weekend battle with Kaymer to sharpen his focus at the start of the year in which he will look to complete a career Grand Slam at the Masters in April. But while his driving and iron play remained as strong as Friday&apos;s performance, when he shot a 66, he had a poor day on the greens after giving himself a chance at nearly every hole.</p> <p>&quot;I struggled to read them,&quot; McIlroy said. &quot;Struggled with pace. Struggled with everything.&quot;</p> <p>His only birdies came at Nos. 6 and 12, and he is 12 under alongside France&apos;s Gary Stal (67) and South Africa&apos;s Charl Schwartzel (65). Austria&apos;s Bernd Wiesberger (66) and France&apos;sAlexander Levy (67) are tied for third on 13 under.</p> <p>South Korea&apos;s An Byeong-hun made a hole-in-one on No. 15 for the fourth ace of tournament, which is two off the record set at the Mediterranean Open in 1991.</p> <p>American star Rickie Fowler is 19 shots off contention after a 73, although he eagled the last -- and got a ride on a camel at the back of the 18th.</p> <p><em>Who will have a better year: Martin Kaymer, Rory McIlroy or Rickie Fowler? Join the conversation in the comments section below.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:c8d21064fa864131c836979e57e7a739" t="1421438436" feed="200853" position="22"><title>Tim Clark, Troy Merritt Share Early Lead at Sony Open</title><link>http://www.golf.com/clark-merritt-share-early-lead-sony-open-2</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/16/ap_images/201501161352499239458.jpg?itok=_n7EUURM" t="image/jpeg" author="AP/Hugh Gentry">Tim Clark tees off on the 11th hole during the second round of the Sony Open. (AP/Hugh Gentry)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>HONOLULU (AP) Tim Clark knew he was hitting the ball well. Put him on a golf course more suited to his game, and it showed for two days at the Sony Open.</p> <p>Clark kept the ball in play on the tight fairways of Waialae, took advantage of dry conditions that allow for more roll, and posted his second straight round of 5-under 65 on Friday for a share of the lead with Troy Merritt among the early starters.</p> <p>Merritt had a 64 to join Clark at 10-under 130.</p> <p>Clark finished his round with a 304-yard tee shot that set up a two-putt birdie on the par-5 ninth hole. Hitting 300-yard drives on the PGA Tour is not a big deal these days, but it was for Clark, who considers himself one of the shortest hitters in golf.</p> <p>It was a testament to how he is feeling, tiny change in his swing to set up taller over the ball, and the firm fairways.</p> <p>And he wasn&apos;t complaining.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;It&apos;s obviously very tight off the tee, and I like to drive it here a lot,&apos;&apos; Clark said. &apos;&apos;And when it&apos;s firm like that, I&apos;m getting a lot of run, so I&apos;m hitting it farther than I normally do. Hitting driver and being aggressive gives me shorter clubs in than most of my opponents, where most courses they&apos;re 20 and 30 by me.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Last week at Kapalua was not one of those courses, along with the fact it was soft on the Plantation course, which Clark found a bit of a mystery because it never rained during the week. He liked the way he was swinging the club, even though he finished 12 shots behind.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I hit the ball great last week,&apos;&apos; Clark said. &apos;&apos;I could tell I was hitting it good. I knew coming to a course that I loved would be nice.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Russell Knox, who learned to swing harder when got on the PGA Tour, had five birdies in a tidy round of 65 and was one shot behind.</p> <p>Paul Casey, Webb Simpson and Camilo Villegas were among the late starters on a day of sunshine and some &apos;&apos;vog&apos;&apos; - volcanic ash in the air that occurs without the typical trade winds blowing for several day - though there was no wind and not much resistance at Waialae.</p> <p>Defending champion Jimmy Walker had another 66 - his 15th consecutive round in the 60s in Hawaii - and was in the group two shots behind the early leaders that included 2010 Sony Open winner Ryan Palmer, who had a 63.</p> <p>The cut looked as though it would be 2-under 138 with so few players running into trouble.</p> <p>Merritt has gone back to the swing he used so well at Boise State, when he was releasing the club and hitting more a draw. He had gone to a fade in recent years, and felt like a change was in order. While this is the first full-field event of the year - and his first competition in two months - he is far from rusty. Merritt said he played about 500 holes in Arizona before coming across the Pacific to start his 2015 season.</p> <p>Off the course, he feels at peace. He has had two sons the last few years, along with moving.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;We&apos;ve had a major life change every year I&apos;ve been professional. This year will be the first year - we&apos;re hopeful - we don&apos;t have one,&apos;&apos; Merritt said. &apos;&apos;I&apos;m talking about moving thousands of miles, a couple new kids over the years, moving again, and just a lot of headaches off the course, and finally we&apos;re just where we need to be. I&apos;ve found peace on and off the golf course, which is good.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Knox is another guy who is increasingly comfortable. The Scot has taken a long road to the big leagues, starting with college golf at Jacksonville University, and then have to Monday qualify to get his starts on the Nationwide Tour. Each year brings more belief he can win, and it doesn&apos;t matter the size of the golf course. He lost in a four-man playoff last year at the Honda Classic that featured Rory McIlroy and was won by Russell Henley.</p> <p>Still, any course that requires accuracy off the tee is going to help. It&apos;s just never been a big help at Waialae.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I&apos;ve never made the cut here, so this is a huge achievement for me,&apos;&apos; Knox said. &apos;&apos;I love it here. On paper, it should fit my game nicely, and the last three years it has not. ... I told my wife if we missed the cut, I was probably never coming back. It was great that I made the cut because I love this course.&apos;&apos;</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:13c7861fd882bc9d803da6a37bbca8d2" t="1421358461" feed="200853" position="23"><title>Phil Mickelson Will Sit Out Pebble Beach, Northern Trust at Riviera</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/phil-mickelson-will-sit-out-pebble-pro-am-riviera</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/15/PhilMickelson.jpg?itok=mpc65-B6" t="image/jpeg" author="Lance Iversen-USA TODAY Sports">Phil Mickelson plays the 2014 AT&amp;T National Pro-Am at Pebble Beach. (Lance Iversen-USA TODAY Sports)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2014/11/29/gallery_images/phil75.jpg?itok=RQx7nhkN" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div> </div> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Phil Mickelson will start the 2015 season slowly, electing to sit out two tournaments in February he normally plays: the AT&amp;T Pebble Beach National Pro-Am and the Northern Trust Open at Riviera.</p> <p><a href="http://philmickelson.com/for-good-reasons-phil-looks-ahead-to-2015/" target="_blank">In an announcement on his website,</a> the five-time major champion said he will miss the two consecutive tournaments to spend time with his family.</p> <p>“Those are two of my favorite events, two of my favorites courses,” Mickelson said, “but with the kids in two schools with different spring breaks I’ll take that time off. They’ve accommodated my schedule enough over the years. It’s time for me to accommodate theirs.”</p> <p>Phil said he will begin his season at the Humana Challenge, which starts Jan. 22 in La Quinta, Calif.</p> <p>Mickelson is a four-time champion at Pebble Beach, with his first win in 1998. <a href="http://www.montereyherald.com/sports/20150114/phil-mickelson-wont-be-playing-in-att-pebble-beach-pro-am" target="_blank">That particular event has been dubbed one of the longest tournaments in golf;</a> due to inclement weather and complicated schedule shuffling, the final round was played the Monday after the 1998 PGA Championship in August. Mickelson shot a 67 to win over Tom Pernice Jr.</p> <p>Mickelson has also had success at Riviera, winning the Northern Trust Open in 2008 and successfully defending his title in 2009.</p> <p>After playing what he referred to as the &quot;most difficult [season] for me in 20-plus years on the PGA Tour,” Mickelson is using his struggles in 2014 as motivation for the season ahead. Mickelson was winless in 2014, despite two top-10 finishes, a first for Lefty since 2003. He&apos;s been working out with a personal trainer four days a week.</p> <p>&quot;I’ve had some immediate results,” he said. &quot;I’m getting lighter, developing more core strength and speed and increasing my ball speed. It’s been awhile since I felt so at ease.&quot;</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:4dc25b346b033392af5eea058dc86174" t="1421352960" feed="200853" position="24"><title>Tour Caddie Kenny Harms Wrestled at Foxcatcher Farm</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/tour-caddie-kenny-harms-wrestled-foxcatcher-farm</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/12/Kenny%2520Harms%2520Kevin%2520Na.jpg?itok=Q4cC01ru" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Kenny Harms has been caddying for Kevin Na since 2009. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Kenny Harms, a veteran Tour caddie, will tell you that Tiger Woods is the second-most impressive athlete he has ever met. He ranks only Dave Schultz ahead of him. Not Dave Schultz as played (brilliantly) by Mark Ruffalo in the 2014 film <em>Foxcatcher</em>. The actual Dave Schultz, under whom Harms wrestled, at the actual Foxcatcher Farm, a rural Pennsylvania estate and wrestling camp owned and run by the millionaire and sociopath John du Pont. Steve Carell plays him (brilliantly) in the movie, with a fake nose and heavy thighs.</p> <p>&quot;I never showered at Foxcatcher,&quot; Harms told me. He&apos;s won with Kevin Na, Hale Irwin, Hubert Green, and he has showered in clubhouses all over the world. He used to be married to Emilee Klein, the LPGA player. &quot;I always had a creepy feeling about John du Pont.&quot;</p> <p>In high school and college, Harms was a wrestler, close to elite but never quite there despite his best effort. He was the captain of his high school team, in Paramus, N.J., and one of the best schoolboy wrestlers in the state, 115-pound division. Golf moved in when wrestling moved out. It didn&apos;t take him long to get to scratch.</p> <p>&quot;They&apos;re incredibly similar sports,&quot; Harms said. &quot;Both require intelligence, discipline and selfishness.&quot;</p> <p>His current boss, Kevin Na, credits Harms with speeding him up, getting him stronger and tougher. You don&apos;t hire Harms, a brick of a man with broad shoulders and dark hair and an earnest manner, if you only want somebody to carry your bag. Harms saw how Schultz, as a coach and fellow wrestler, inspired the Olympic hopefuls at Foxcatcher with tough love and encouragement. He did not yell. He did not pound. He taught. Kenny has taken Schultz&apos;s wrestling mat lessons to the golf course. The underlying question is always the same: How deep are you willing to dig? Schultz, like Woods in his prime, was trying to reach China.</p> <p>John du Pont, as a coach and wrestler, was a pretender. &quot;He&apos;d come into the wrestling room with his singlet on,&quot; Harms said. &quot;And he&apos;d be the weakest person in the room. Everybody killed him.&quot;</p> <p>Harms was a junior at nearby West Chester State at the time. He&apos;d drive to Foxcatcher several nights a week, get waved through the gate, wrestle and drive back to his off-campus apartment. He was at Foxcatcher for five months, in the 1988-89 collegiate season, as an all-purpose 140-pound sparring partner for wrestlers trying to make the national team.</p> <p>Schultz and his younger brother, Mark, had both won freestyle gold medals in the 1984 Olympics. Mark Schultz, played (brilliantly) in the film by Channing Tatum, is portrayed as du Pont&apos;s human pet. &quot;We all heard the same rumors,&quot; Harms said, that du Pont was gay, and that he used wrestling as a way to be around physically robust men. &quot;I didn&apos;t care about that. But I didn&apos;t go back for a second year. John du Pont was the reason. He was weird.&quot;</p> <p>Within a year, Harms had his first job in golf, as a sweep-the-shop assistant pro at White Manor Country Club, down the road from Foxcatcher Farm. Wrestling remains his greatest passion, and, at 49, he&apos;s about as fit as anybody on Tour, caddie or player. He used to wear out the other loopers in those caddie races at Colonial and Phoenix.</p> <p>Harms said that he&apos;s watched clips of <em>Foxcatcher</em> and planned to see the movie, but that he would do so with mixed feelings. &quot;From what I&apos;ve seen, they&apos;re showing John du Pont as a strong personality.&quot; At one point, Carell, as du Pont, tells his mother, &quot;I lead men.&quot;</p> <p>&quot;He was a coward,&quot; Harms said. He says he thought that long before the day -- January 26, 1996 -- that du Pont shot and killed Schultz at his farm. Du Pont died in prison in 2010.</p> <p>In the movie, du Pont&apos;s horse-loving mother, played (brilliantly) by Vanessa Redgrave, tells her son, &quot;I don&apos;t like the sport of wrestling, as you know. It&apos;s a low sport.&quot;</p> <p>To Harms, it&apos;s a high sport, the highest. He says Schultz was a great wrestler because he had stamina, resilience and a bottomless capacity for work, mental and physical. Now Harms is trying to help get Na -- as Schultz tried to do with his wrestlers -- to the promised land. Na remains a work in progress. Harms remembers Luke Donald once talking to Na on a practice range when Donald was the No. 1 player in the world. &quot;Luke walks away and Kevin says, &quot;I work just as hard as he does.&quot; I laughed at him.&quot;</p> <p>Harms wishes that Woods and Schultz could have compared notes. &quot;Dave Schultz didn&apos;t think about wrestling just in the wrestling room, and Tiger didn&apos;t think about golf just on the course and range,&quot; the caddie said. &quot;It takes total dedication.&quot; From what Kenny Harms has seen, not in the movies but in real life, total dedication is just the starting point.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Michael Bamberger</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:c672ec1b7a5112b226bbae445db4a115" t="1421352036" feed="200853" position="25"><title>Webb Simpson Rides Short Putter to 62 and Share of Sony Open Lead</title><link>http://www.golf.com/casey-simpson-tied-lead-62-calm-sony-open-2</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/15/ap_images/201501151633596207388.jpg?itok=vCN_2rBu" t="image/jpeg" author="AP Photo/Hugh Gentry">Webb Simpson follows his ball after teeing off on the 11th hole during the first round of the Sony Open. (AP Photo/Hugh Gentry)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>HONOLULU (AP) Webb Simpson made his debut with a conventional putter Thursday at the Sony Open and might have wished he had used one sooner.</p> <p>One year away from the new rule that outlaws anchored strokes, Simpson ditched his belly putter for a regular one for his 2015 debut and ran off eight birdies over his last 10 holes for an 8-under 62 that gave him a share of the lead with Paul Casey.</p> <p>On a day that made the 144 players feel they were in paradise with sunshine and barely a breeze, Simpson and Casey led the low scoring at Waialae.</p> <p>What set them apart is how they got there - Simpson with his conventional putter, Casey with his return to Honolulu for the first time in a decade.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;Today was a big day for me,&apos;&apos; Simpson said. &apos;&apos;I was extremely nervous - first round on the PGA Tour with a short putter. But I just had a couple (Bible) verses in my yardage book today that I kept reading, and I stayed calm. All thanks to God for giving me strength to just get through today.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;Today was a hurdle I felt like I needed to get over, and just real thankful.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Camilo Villegas would have joined them at 62 except for failing to make birdie on the par-5 18th hole. He shot 29 on the front at Waialae before cooling slightly for a 63. Robert Streb also had a 63, the low score from the afternoon.</p> <p>Rory Sabbatini had a 64, while Jason Day, Matt Kuchar were in the group at 65. Defending champion Jimmy Walker played in the afternoon and was in the large group at 66.</p> <p>Casey says he gave up his European Tour membership to concentrate on playing the PGA Tour, spending time with his newborn son and getting his game back into the top 50 in the world. He hasn&apos;t played in a Ryder Cup since 2008. He hasn&apos;t been in the top 50 in nearly three years.</p> <p>And that&apos;s why it has been 10 years since he has been at the Sony Open. He typically is starting his season in the Middle East.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;For as long as I&apos;ve been professional I&apos;ve been a member of the European Tour,&apos;&apos; Casey said. &apos;&apos;For a long, long time now, I&apos;ve been trying to play both the PGA Tour and the European Tour, and some years I&apos;ve done it brilliantly, and other years I&apos;ve failed miserably, and I just didn&apos;t want to keep putting myself in kind of a position where I&apos;m struggling to fly around the world.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Playing both tours is easier from inside the top 50, which effectively guarantees four majors and four World Golf Championships. Casey, who won the Dutch Open last year, is now at No. 78.</p> <p>Simpson said he stopped off in Las Vegas to work with Butch Harmon on his way to Hawaii to make sure he was up so speed with swing changes he made in the fall. But this day was all about his putter. He won the U.S. Open in 2012 with the belly putter, which has been his club since the fall of 2004 when he was at Wake Forest. And he used it last fall in Japan, but there was something about a PGA Tour event that made him nervous.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;It was one of my best putting rounds I&apos;ve ever had, to be honest,&apos;&apos; he said. &apos;&apos;I&apos;ve been putting well with it, but it&apos;s easy to putt well at your home course playing with your biddies. So today there was a lot of pressure. Didn&apos;t sleep that great last night, but had a good morning, talked to my wife, good warmup, and it was big to see a few putts go in early. Real thankful for how the day unfolded.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>He made four birdie putts of at least 15 feet on his front nine, a pace that will be tough to maintain all week.</p> <p>DIVOTS: Geoff Ogilvy made his first hole-in-one on the PGA Tour with a 5-iron from 211 yards on the fourth hole. He said he has made five or six aces on other tours. The ace only helped so much. He opened with a 69. ... Simpson&apos;s 28 tied the front-nine record at Waialae set by Toshinori Muto three years ago. ... Of the five Champions Tour players in the field, Kenny Perry led the way at 67, while Paul Goydos shot 69. Vijay Singh had a 71, and Davis Love III and Fred Funk each had a 72. All but Singh are going over to the Big Island next week to start the Champions Tour season. Singh did not get an exemption.</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:f34ef83a31422c7e995130c031d41d51" t="1421352021" feed="200853" position="26"><title>Watch: Australians Nail the First Ever Underwater Hole-In-One</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/15/watch-australians-nail-first-ever-underwater-hole-one</link><enclosure u="http://www.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2015/01/12/Screen%2520Shot%25202015-01-12%2520at%25202.18.05%2520PM.png?itok=ycyFaBCT" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p> </p> <div class="media_embed" height="315px" width="560px"> <iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="315px" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dvZna3XZJ3w" width="560px"></iframe> </div> <p> </p> <p>In today&apos;s edition of &quot;Cool Golf Trick Shots...&quot;</p> <p>Australian trick shot aficionados &quot;How Ridiculous&quot; have laid claim to sinking - no pun intended - the first ever underwater hole-in-one.</p> <div> </div> <p>A large plastic bucket anchored about eight feet below the water&apos;s surface served as the cup, but with ocean currents considered, it&apos;s pretty impressive.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:ba95fb2da83f5b4802065402421312b8" t="1421343918" feed="200853" position="27"><title>Patrick Reed: The Best Way to Twirl a Club</title><link>http://www.golf.com/instruction/patrick-reed-best-way-twirl-club</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/12/PatrickReed_1.jpg?itok=vNl65mUv" t="image/jpeg" author="Chris Condon/PGA Tour">A killer post-swing club twirl is both reward and validation. (Chris Condon/PGA Tour)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2015/01/12/461456736_0.jpg?itok=-dqwloFA" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>I see nothing wrong with twirling a club after a good shot. It&apos;s both validation and reward–two positive emotions that can fuel good rounds. My twirl is more subdued than some of the other guys&apos;. It&apos;s about acknowledging me, not showing up an opponent. Here are the key steps:</p> <div> </div> <p><strong>1.</strong> Hold your finish for a count, and as you&apos;re watching the ball fly straight at your target, allow both arms to gently fall toward the left side of your torso. If the ball is slicing toward a hazard, stop here.</p> <p><strong>2.</strong> As your arms fall, loosen your hold on the grip and use your right forefinger and thumb to spin the shaft clockwise. Once the club begins spinning, completely let go of the club so it drops straight down.</p> <p><strong>3.</strong> Start walking now, and as soon as you feel the hosel slide through your left hand, grip the club and stop its fall. Get the timing right, and you&apos;ll look as smooth as a Tour winner.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Patrick Reed</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:1a4f86827c219c51b98a16aadcdfccae" t="1421343918" feed="200853" position="28"><title>Rory McIlroy Trails Martin Kaymer by 3 at Abu Dhabi Championship</title><link>http://www.golf.com/mcilroy-magic-puts-no-1-contention-abu-dhabi-0</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/15/ap_images/201501140816298143852.jpg?itok=8MWoZI9q" t="image/jpeg" author="AP Photo/Rick Rycroft">Rory McIlroy is near the lead after the first round of the Abu Dhabi Championship. (AP Photo/Rick Rycroft)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates (AP) -- Martin Kaymer rekindled his fondness for the Abu Dhabi Championship by rolling in 10 birdies to shoot an 8-under 64 in the first round on Thursday, giving the German a one-stroke lead in an event he has won three times.</p> <p>Living up to his tag of the &quot;King of Abu Dhabi,&quot; Kaymer showed the form on the greens that brought him titles in the desert in 2008, &apos;10 and &apos;11, and looked energized after time away from golf over Christmas.</p> <p>&quot;I putted very well,&quot; Kaymer said. &quot;Ten birdies? I&apos;m not sure I have done that in my golf career.&quot;</p> <p>Top-ranked Rory McIlroy and American star Rickie Fowler were also playing their first tournaments of 2015, and fed off each other&apos;s brilliant putting on their back nines to shoot 67s.</p> <p>McIlroy&apos;s round was revived by a superb, improvised wedge shot from the lip of a fairway bunker on his 12th hole, setting up the first of five birdies in his last seven holes.</p> <p>&quot;I was just trying to get it on the green,&quot; McIlroy said about his impudent 95-yard shot from an awkward stance that revived memories of the late Seve Ballesteros. &quot;From looking like going 1 over to finishing 5 under, I&apos;m very happy.&quot;</p> <p>Unheralded Belgian Thomas Pieters shot a 65 to lie alone in second place, with five players - Branden Grace, Gregory Bourdy, first-year tour player Tyrrell Hatton, Alexander Levy and Mikko Ilonen - tied for third on 6 under.</p> <p>Kaymer ripped up his usual festive routine -- which can involve hitting some balls on Christmas Day at his base in Arizona -- and spent time at home in Germany and on the ski slopes of Italy, where he enjoyed learning a new sport.</p> <p>&quot;Life is not all about golf,&quot; Kaymer said. &quot;It was nice to find a hobby that is challenging for me.&quot;</p> <p>He won&apos;t be giving up the day job, though.</p> <p>Kaymer lost form after winning the Players Championship and the U.S. Open midway through last year, but was back to his best on what he calls his &quot;home course&quot; in making four birdies on the front nine and six coming in. Three birdies were from more than 18 feet.</p> <p>With a second place and a sixth place to go with his three titles at the Abu Dhabi Golf Course, Kaymer is the man to beat this week - even with McIlroy around.</p> <p>The only swings McIlroy made over the month either side of Christmas were practice ones in his kitchen at home. The break didn&apos;t do him any harm, either.</p> <p>His first shot of 2015 was a 315-yard drive down the middle of the par-5 10th fairway and he birdied the hole for the perfect start to his attempt to win this tournament for the first time, after three runner-up finishes since 2011.</p> <p>McIlroy&apos;s short game made up for some errant drives for the rest of his front nine but the spectacular shot on No. 3 proved to be a catalyst. With one foot in the face of a bunker and the other out of the hazard, he had to open the face of his wedge and dig out a shot that landed 12 feet away. It brought the biggest cheer of the day from a sparse crowd at Abu Dhabi Golf Club.</p> <p>&quot;It&apos;s not a shot I practice a lot,&quot; said McIlroy, who holed from 15 feet on No. 4, 10 feet on Nos. 5 and 7 and eight feet on No. 8 for birdies that allowed him to chase down Fowler.</p> <p>The American, who lost out to McIlroy in the British Open and U.S. PGA Championship last year, upstaged his rival by making six birdies in 11 holes starting at No. 15 - his sixth hole. However, Fowler sent his approach at the last through the green, misjudged a flop shot on the way back and missed a 10-foot par putt to slip back level with McIlroy.</p> <p>Second-ranked Henrik Stenson had a double-bogey on his first hole and didn&apos;t make any birdies in a 76. Justin Rose shot 73.</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:3c160a30e555cb18040175b86f681a24" t="1421343910" feed="200853" position="29"><title>Rory McIlroy-Rickie Fowler Rivalry Adds New Chapter in Abu Dhabi</title><link>http://www.golf.com/fowler-mcilroy-rivalry-adds-new-chapter-abu-dhabi</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/15/RickieFowlerRoryMcIlroy.jpg?itok=L3cTZ-tX" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Rory McIlroy and Rickie Fowler both shot 67 Thursday in Abu Dhabi. (Getty Images)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2014/12/08/rorylilly.jpg?itok=76M9bMiS" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>ABU DHABI, United Arab Emirates (AP) No matter how hard he tries or how well he plays, Rickie Fowler just can&apos;t seem to get the better of Rory McIlroy.</p> <p>A golfing rivalry that began at the 2007 Walker Cup and is being talked about as potentially the biggest of the new generation was one-sided in 2014, with McIlroy outgunning Fowler in the final rounds of the British Open and U.S. PGA Championship to win both major titles. McIlroy then crushed the American 5 and 4 in a singles match at the Ryder Cup.</p> <div> </div> <p>Would the new year bring new luck for Fowler in his burgeoning competition with the world&apos;s best player? Not quite.</p> <p>The friends - separated in age by six months - were grouped together for the opening two rounds of the Abu Dhabi Championship, but Fowler couldn&apos;t capitalize on a fast start that put him three shots clear of McIlroy after 10 holes on Thursday.</p> <p>The pair, chatting away for much of their first rounds, traded birdie putts in a high-quality back nine but a strong finish from McIlroy - and Fowler&apos;s bogey at the last - saw them post 5-under 67s.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I can&apos;t get rid of him,&apos;&apos; the 10th-ranked Fowler said with a smile as he looked across to McIlroy in a joint interview just off the 18th hole.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;Obviously being able to go back and forth and play against each other, it&apos;s good fun,&apos;&apos; Fowler added. &apos;&apos;We got to see quite a bit of that last year and hopefully there&apos;s a lot more to come this year. It&apos;s going to be a long career, battling each other.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Fowler conceded on the eve of the tournament that McIlroy - the younger of the pair but on tour for two years longer - currently has the edge, chiefly because of his &apos;&apos;better ball striking&apos;&apos; and his length and consistency off the tee. Yet, the 26-year-old American believes his putting is stronger and that was the case on Thursday.</p> <p>During a hot streak from No. 15 to No. 7 (they started at No. 10), Fowler made six birdie putts ranging from 10 feet to 35 feet and was assured with his par putts from closer in, too. McIlroy said he was inspired by Fowler&apos;s brilliance on the greens as he birdied five of his last seven holes.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I just needed to hang on his coattails,&apos;&apos; McIlroy said. &apos;&apos;He was kicking me on today, for sure. I was trying to keep up with him and didn&apos;t want to let him get too far ahead.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Golf is always looking for big rivalries and this McIlroy-Fowler one could endure. They are good friends, too, with Fowler having pledged to play in this year&apos;s Irish Open at Royal County Down that is being hosted by McIlroy&apos;s foundation.</p> <p>Indeed, Europe could be seeing more of Fowler, who is looking to become more of a global player. Fellow American Patrick Reed announced on Twitter last month that he had become a member of the European Tour and Fowler is hinting he could follow suit.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;Definitely moving forward, that could be a possibility with the amount I could play in the future on the European Tour schedule,&apos;&apos; said Fowler, who is planning to play in the Scottish Open - the warmup for the British Open - again this summer.</p> <p>That&apos;s for the future. As for 2015, Fowler is simply looking to make inroads into McIlroy&apos;s dominance - and capture a first major title after top-five placings in the four biggest tournaments in golf last year.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I guess I&apos;m not off to the hottest of starts for my career, with only two worldwide wins, one on the PGA Tour,&apos;&apos; Fowler said. &apos;&apos;I&apos;d like to start adding to that and make myself a little bit more of a prominent player.&apos;&apos;</p> <div> <div class="component-video-player ui-video-player" data-componentid=""> <div class="video-player-content"> <div class="video-ratio"> <div class="video-wrapper" data-id="myExperience3984987011001" data-category="" data-subcategory="" data-title="tour-confidential-tournament-champions-pga-aloha-maui" data-bcid="3984987011001" data-width="300" data-height="100" data-playerid="2538399922001" data-playerkey="AQ~~,AAAAABjSC6U~,4Z3U_tH-Vly48f0a5CdEkba_lR7W0vMj" data-videoid="3984987011001" data-auto-start="false" data-https="" data-forcehtml="false" data-adtags="" data-nid="" data-vdprm="" data-vdins="" data-teach="" data-year="" data-tour="" data-feat="" data-brand="" data-ads_title="" data-zone=""> </div> </div> </div> <div class="inline"> <div class="inline-headline"> Tour Confidential: Should PGA Say &apos;Aloha&apos; to Maui? </div> <div class="inline-description"> This week&apos;s panel debates whether the PGA Tour should consider moving the start of the season outside of Hawaii — and if so, to where. </div> </div> </div> </div> <p> </p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:92857f1d733b509aea92fab57037ab55:92857f1d733b509aea92fab57037ab55" t="1421280000" feed="200853" position="30"><title>Destination Golf: Scottsdale, Arizona</title><link>http://www.golf.com/photos/destination-golf-scottsdale-arizona</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale1Phoenician.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">The Phoenician pampers golfers with complimentary 10-minute pre-round back massages near the first tee, and the resort's Centre for Well-Being provides golf yoga classes for those in need of deep relaxation. Three nine-hole layouts rise from the Sonoran Desert: the Oasis, aptly named for its ponds and lakes; the Canyon, which climbs and dips amid the rocks; and the Desert, wending around the foothills of Camelback Mountain. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale2Longbow_0.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">Only 20 minutes from Old Town Scottsdale, Longbow Golf Club features a Ken Kavanaugh design that tips out at just over 7,000 yards. A 2003 redesign resurrected the course's character and involves a beautiful new club house, more land and a reconstructed practice facility. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale3TPC16.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">Home to the Waste Management Phoenix Open, the best-attended (and rowdiest) stop on the PGA Tour, the TPC Scottsdale Stadium course is nobody's idea of a beauty queen, but what it lacks in looks, it makes up for in thrills. The island-green, par-5 15th and drivable par-4 17th are two water-tinged, risk/reward greats. For trivia fans, note that the latter is the site of the only ace on a par-4 in PGA Tour history (Andrew Magee, 2001), while the loudest hole in golf, the par-3 16th, reached its zenith in 1997 when Tiger Woods carded a memorable hole-in-one. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://www.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale4Camelback.gif" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">A Marriott property located in the shadow of Camelback Mountain, Camelback Golf Club features two 18-hole courses: the Padre and the Ambiente. A recent redesign saw the addition of over 1,400 native Acacia trees, not to mention a removal of non-native habitation and a topography reconstruction. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale5TroonNorth.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">Still the king of the Scottsdale public "must-plays" thanks to a pair of courses that dish out cacti, arroyos, rock outcroppings and stunning vistas of Pinnacle Peak and the surrounding mountains. The Monument course is the more scenic of the two, but Pinnacle is the more cohesive test and is walkable, a rarity among modern real estate-oriented desert courses. A revitalized Dynamite Grille, with a new menu and bar, is now a highly regarded post-round option in the clubhouse. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://www.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale6Grayhawk.gif" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">This facility didn't invent the "country club for a day," theme, but it may have perfected it in the 1990s, when Phil's Grill (named for Phil Mickelson) was a beehive for tour pros. Lefty has moved back to his native San Diego, but the 'Hawk still brims with ambiance, excellent service, above-average dining options and classic rock tunes piped to the practice range via faux-rock speakers. The Tom Fazio-designed Raptor course has hosted most of the big events, including the PGA Tour's Frys.com Open (2007-2009), but the David Graham/Gary Panks-crafted Talon course offers more drama, notably at the par-3 11th, where golfers traverse a swinging bridge to reach the back tee, and at the island-green, par-3 17th that's rimmed with colorful flowers. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale7JWMarriott.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">The JW Marriott Camelback Inn features all the amenities one would come to expect at a luxurious resort surrounded by great golf: spa, swimming, hiking, biking, fine dining, among many others. The resort has six high-quality restaurants including the famed BLT Steak. Whether your party is large or small, private or public, the JW Marriott Camelback Inn can deliver. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale8Kierland.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">Kierland Golf Club offers three championship nine-hole courses, each named after the indigenous life found along the way: Acacia, Ironwood and Mesquite. Course designer Scott Miller, formerly a senior designer for Jack Nicklaus, knows championship golf and had a hand in many of the area's best golf routings. Kierland's 27 holes feature over 300 bunkers, lakes, dry desert washed and strands of desert trees. In addition, signature TifEagle greens offer subtle contours that will keep even the best players guessing. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale9FairmontPrincess.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">The Fairmont Scottsdale Princess resort features amenities for the whole family: Well &amp; Being at Willow Stream Spa, award-winning restaurants and lounges, poolside bar and meal service along with nearby recreational day trips. Also included is over 156,000 square feet of event space (both indoor and outdoor venues) and the Trailblazers Family Adventure Center. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/06/Scottsdale10FP_1.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Scottsdale CVB">The two layouts on tribal land owned by the Fort McDowell Yavapai nation just east of Scottsdale equal any in the area. The Cholla course, a Scott Miller design, has incomparable scenery and holes that zigzag artfully through canyons, over ridges and down mountain slopes. The Saguaro course, a 2006 Bill Coore/Ben Crenshaw design, is wide enough that a spray hitter will still find his tee shot. There are few forced carries, so a golfer who struggles getting it airborne can also enjoy. Strong players will bask in the challenge of strategic bunkers, superb risk/reward decisions and cleverly contoured greens. Add elevation changes, mountain vistas and a forest of cacti to the mix and you've got an unbeatable combination. (Scottsdale CVB)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/ScottsdaleGRAYHAWK.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Grayhawk Golf Club/Lonna Tucker">This facility didn't invent the "country club for a day," theme, but it may have perfected it in the 1990s, when Phil's Grill (named for Phil Mickelson) was a beehive for tour pros. Lefty has moved back to his native San Diego, but the 'Hawk still brims with ambiance, excellent service, above-average dining options and classic rock tunes piped to the practice range via faux-rock speakers. The Tom Fazio-designed Raptor course has hosted most of the big events, including the PGA Tour's Frys.com Open (2007-2009), but the David Graham/Gary Panks-crafted Talon course offers more drama, notably at the par-3 11th, where golfers traverse a swinging bridge to reach the back tee, and at the island-green, par-3 17th that's rimmed with colorful flowers. (Grayhawk Golf Club/Lonna Tucker)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Destination Golf: Scottsdale, Arizona</p>]]></description><author>Scottsdale CVB</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:2e0c3a7725790f55342fc908df184d61:2e0c3a7725790f55342fc908df184d61" t="1421280000" feed="200853" position="31"><title>Destination Golf: Florida</title><link>http://www.golf.com/photos/destination-golf-florida</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/%252317%2520%2520hole%2520Sawgrass.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf">Early in 2006, after the final putt fell at the Players Championship, work crews fanned out across the Stadium Course at TPC Sawgrass, giving Pete Dye's renowned layout its first major renovation since it opened in 1981. Dye's design, never meant to overwhelm with length, has been left largely intact and still requires subtlety and precision. Some holes (like Nos. 1 and 8) have been lengthened modestly, and pot bunkers were added along the seventh fairway (at 270 to 310 yards from the tee, they aren't an issue for most of us). Even the most iconic hole at Sawgrass -- the island-green 17th -- was tweaked: the front slope was flattened a little and the left side widened to accommodate a perilous new pin position. (Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/amelia-island---ritz-carlton-1440x950.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf">Compared to traditional Florida parkland tracks -- you know the type, watery wastelands with fairways wide enough to land a jumbo jet on -- the tree-lined fairways here frame a course with plenty of character. Sure, there's no shortage of water, but at Amelia Island it's used as an element of strategy, not just for landscaping. Take the second hole, a 572-yard par 5 that is almost U-shaped. It's a hole that plays to long hitters but not straight hitters. Shaping the ball is essential here, and the water lurking along the left side comes into play just enough around the green to give even long ballers pause for thought. You won't leave the 18th green thinking this is the best course you've ever played, but you should leave thinking you had a fun, challenging experience without having your wallet gouged. (Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/hammock%2520beach.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Hammock Beach Resort">There's golf, and then there's legendary golf at Hammock Beach Resort. With signature courses designed by Jack Nicklaus and Tom Watson, golfers can choose to take in breathtaking views of the Atlantic Ocean from six different holes (Ocean Course) or take on one of the longest and most challenging courses in the state (Conservatory Course).</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/AIP-Signature-Golf-Ocean-Links-030408-7x5.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf">Ocean Links has 10 holes that feature lagoons and marsh wetlands in addition to concluding with a par three whose green is strategically placed in the waters of Red Maple Lake. The course winds through six miles of the natural sand dunes and seaside terrain that make Amelia Island so special. It can be said that this is as much a nature tour as it is a round of golf. The course yardage of 6,300 yards is somewhat deceiving since small greens, narrow fairways and prevailing winds make the course play much longer. At par 70, this 18-hole combination provides a challenge to golfers of all levels. (Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/07/wgv_overview.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf">Golfers working on their bucket list should be sure to add the World Golf Hall of Fame &amp; Museum and World Golf Village on Florida's northeast coast. The Village features the world's only collaboration between Arnold Palmer and Jack Nicklaus -- the King &amp; Bear is set among pristine lakes, pines and oaks, and uses characteristics from both players to create a one-of-a-kind experience. (Florida&amp;#8217;s First Coast of Golf)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/PonteVedraInnandClub.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Florida&amp;apos;s First Coast of Golf">The Ponte Vedra Inn &amp; Club has been a popular Florida landmark since 1928. Located in the seaside village of Ponte Vedra Beach, near Jacksonville, this AAA Five-Diamond-rated resort has welcomed four generations of guests with elegance and style. Just steps from the Atlantic, the Inn &amp; Club offers two challenging 18-hole course. The 6,573-yard, par-72 Ocean Course (shown) is a masterpiece of strength and strategy, while the shorter Lagoon Course demands accurate drives and thoughtful cpproaches. Other features include the beach, tennis, pools, gym and a spa. Add biking, fishing, sailing and horseback riding, and you have a year-round paradise. Three restaurants offer cuisine ranging from casual to classic, and shoppers can enjoy eight boutiques. (Florida&amp;apos;s First Coast of Golf)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/GrandCypress.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Grand Cypress">The VIllage of Grand Cypress offers plenty of golf options among the North, South, East and New Courses. All four are designed by Jack Nicklaus. The South Course (shown) 1984 and was recently redone in 2007. The result is lengthier holes and characteristics not typical of Orlando golf. The course also features sharply ledged fairways, shaggy mounds and plenty of plateau greens, which you'll find at many Nicklaus-designed courses.</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/NewCourseGrandCypress.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Grand Cypress">The New Course at Grand Cypress, also designed by Jack Nicklaus, opened in 1988 and is the Golden Bear's homage to the famed architecture of the Old Course at St. Andrews in Scotland. This course features double greens, stone bridges and walls, burns and pot bunkers, along with plenty of other areas of both trouble and aesthetic value. The course itself has over 150 pot bunkers.</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/SouthGrandCypress.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Grand Cypress">The North Course at Grand Cypress is built to test accuracy, precision and course management rather than simply distance and strength. Here you'll find platform greens and terraced fairways, often surrounded by contoured mounding and wide bunkers. One of the original nine-hole courses at Grand Cypress, along with the South Course, the North Course presents a challenge for players of all levels.</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/StreamsongRed.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Streamsong">Hewn from a gigantic sand sprawl left over from its incarnation as a phosphate strip mine, the Red course at Streamsong Resort (shown) sports tall, odd-shaped sand piles; significant climbs and drops; firm, fast Bermuda fairways; and lakes and lagoons. The Red was designed in conjunction with Tom Doak’s Blue course and has more drama than its sibling, from the lakes to the propped-up and handsomely framed greens to the demands off the tee. The 474-yard opening hole demands a drive over water and scrub -- check out the massive dune left of the fairway -- and an uphill approach. The 208-yard, par-3 16th features a forced carry over a lake to a Biarritz green bisected by a huge swale. With a caddie, the course is an enjoyable walk, thanks to a friendly back-tee slope of 130.</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/StreamsongBlue.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="Streamsong">Although both tracks share the distinctive sand-based canvas, Tom Doak and Renaissance Golf Design crafted the Blue (shown) with subtle differences from the Red. The land used for the Blue appears perfectly suited for golf holes -- fairways cling to the terrain as though they’ve been there for centuries, and greens seem to melt into their surroundings. Imaginative contouring forces &#x2028;players to think before they hit their approach shot. After the dizzying panorama on the par-4 first, the next stunner is the 203-yard, par-3 seventh, which demands a lake carry to a wildly rippling green. Tempting and treacherous, the drivable par-4 13th might be the best-designed hole on the entire 36-hole property, and the risk/reward par-5 17th sports brilliant cross-bunkering. As with the Red, the Blue is pure fun, with an emphasis on ground-game prowess that’s rare in American golf. (Streamsong)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/2015/01/15/PGANationalChamp.jpg" t="image/jpeg" author="PGA Tour/Stan Badz">Every year at the end of February/beginning of March, the stadium seats at the Championship Course at PGA National are packed to watch the world's best compete for the Honda Classic crown. PGA National gives golfers a chance to replicate their strategy and shots, or to just relax, have fun and enjoy the wonderful scenery. PGA National has five courses, numerous restaurants and bars and plenty of event space to host special occasions, no matter how large. It's a hot spot all throughout the year, but especially during the week of the Honda Classic. (PGA Tour/Stan Badz)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p>Destination Golf: Florida</p>]]></description><author>Florida’s First Coast of Golf</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:568d05871897dd52f67c5dc77b444afb" t="1421265992" feed="200853" position="32"><title>New Callaway XR Drivers, Fairway Woods, Hybrids and Irons</title><link>http://www.golf.com/equipment/new-callaway-xr-drivers-fairway-woods-hybrids-and-irons</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Clubs-Main.jpg?itok=eOA_EOa7" t="image/jpeg" author="Courtesy of Callaway">Callaway XR Driver; Callaway XR Irons; Callaway XR Fairway Woods (Courtesy of Callaway)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Driver.jpg?itok=TpHHYNXV" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Fairway-Woods.jpg?itok=txfhym7v" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Hybrid.jpg?itok=wDUpq7F4" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Irons.jpg?itok=AluB1jgG" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Callaway is set to debut an entire family of XR products, which includes drivers, fairway woods, hybrids and irons. The standard XR models are best suited for average Joes while the XR Pro (and XR Deep) options target better players.</p> <p> </p> <p><strong>Callaway XR Driver <br /> Price: $349</strong></p> <p>Last year, Callaway reestablished itself as a leader in driver technology with its Big Bertha and X2 Hot lines. The company looks to keep the good times rolling with the debut of the XR and XR Pro. Callaway believes the XR can help you swing faster, generate more ball speed and hit longer drives. The club&apos;s thin, lightweight face insert contributes to a low CG, and more efficient transfer of energy across the hitting area while the aerodynamic crown reduces drag during the swing. In addition, the Project X LZ shaft is designed to maximize shaft load during the downswing. The company&apos;s well-known OptiFit hosel enables you to change loft (from 2° stronger to 1° weaker) and lie to optimize launch conditions. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°, 12°, 13.5°. $349. In stores on February 20.</p> <div>  </div> <p>The lower-spinning XR Pro ($399), for better players, features many of the same technologies. It has a more traditional shape plus a forged composite crown, which contributes to lower CG and less spin. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°. In stores on March 20.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Fairway-Woods.jpg?itok=txfhym7v" /> </div> <p><strong>Callaway XR Fairway Woods <br /> Price: $239</strong></p> <p>The company is offering three head styles (XR, XR Pro and XR Deep) for different shots and player types. The XR has the shallowest face height of the three models and a CG that&apos;s 20 percent lower than in X2 Hot woods so it&apos;s easier to hit from fairway lies.The standard XR also has a thinner, lighter forged face cup than in the X2 Hot, which leads to faster ball speeds and a 16 percent larger sweetspot. Lofts: 15°, 17°, 19°, 21°, 23°, 25°. In stores on February 20.</p> <p>The XR Pro ($239) has a deeper face than the standard XR. It&apos;s designed to produce lower-launching shots with less spin and a more neutral ball flight. As a result, it&apos;ll be easier for better players to maneuver shots. Loft: 14.5°, 16°, 18°. In stores on March 20.</p> <p>The deepest face belongs to the complementary XR Deep ($249). It, too, should produce lower-launching shots with less spin and a neutral ball flight. The XR Deep design lends itself to be used more on tee shots than off the fairway. You can expect a strong, boring flight from this one. Loft: 14°. In stores on March 20.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Hybrid.jpg?itok=wDUpq7F4" /> </div> <p><strong>Callaway XR Hybrids <br /> Price: $219</strong></p> <p>A new forged face cup increases ball speed across more of the face so misses perform similar to center strikes. The CG is 46 percent lower than in the X2 Hot, which should boost forgiveness while Callaway&apos;s Standing Wave internal weighting further enhances MOI and face flex. Designed for easy launch and maximum distance. Lofts: 19°, 22°, 25°, 28°. In stores on February 20.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Callaway-XR-Irons.jpg?itok=AluB1jgG" /> </div> <p><strong>Callaway XR Irons <br /> Price: $799, steel; $899, graphite</strong></p> <p>Built to max-out distance, these irons have a &quot;360-degree face cup,&quot; which refers to the way the face wraps over the crown and sole, for improved ball speed across the face. Until recently, the design was limited to woods. The Internal Standing Wave design allows for a lower CG and higher MOI for forgiveness. In stores on February 20.</p> <p><a href="http://www.golfsmith.com/ps/search/callaway-golf-clubs/_/N-69656+1130?tcode=gcom&amp;scode=GOLF14Q1&amp;utm_source=golf-com-shop&amp;utm_medium=partners" target="_blank"><span><strong>BUY your own Callaway gear in our online store</strong></span></a></p> <div> <div class="component-video-player ui-video-player" data-componentid=""> <div class="video-player-content"> <div class="video-ratio"> <div class="video-wrapper" data-id="myExperience3156322488001" data-category="" data-subcategory="" data-title="drivers-2014-golf-magazine-clubtest-2014-driver-roundtable-major-driver-trends" data-bcid="3156322488001" data-width="300" data-height="100" data-playerid="2538399922001" data-playerkey="AQ~~,AAAAABjSC6U~,4Z3U_tH-Vly48f0a5CdEkba_lR7W0vMj" data-videoid="3156322488001" data-auto-start="false" data-https="" data-forcehtml="false" data-adtags="" data-nid="" data-vdprm="" data-vdins="" data-teach="" data-year="" data-tour="" data-feat="" data-brand="" data-ads_title="" data-zone=""> </div> </div> </div> <div class="inline"> <div class="inline-headline"> ClubTest 2014: Driver Roundtable </div> <div class="inline-description"> Learn what regular players like you think about the latest high-loft, low-spin drivers in our ClubTest 2014 roundtable, hosted by Golf Magazine&apos;s Rob Sauerhaft. </div> </div> </div> </div> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Rob Sauerhaft</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:53fbd3324b6dd4cf932a87b799c1383c" t="1421262915" feed="200853" position="33"><title>John Boehner's Former Golf Club Bartender Threatened to Poison Him, Police Say</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/former-golf-club-bartender-indicted-threatening-poison-john-boehner</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/14/116926538.jpg?itok=7Z65fIyQ" t="image/jpeg" author="MANDEL NGAN">House Speaker John Boehner and President Barack Obama enjoy a round in 2011. (MANDEL NGAN)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Michael%2520Hoyt%2520Bartender.jpg?itok=jgwV3uYP" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>A former bartender at House Speaker John Boehner&apos;s Ohio country club has been charged with threatening to kill Boehner, <a href="http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2015/01/13/us/politics/boehner-threat-court-documents.html" target="_blank">according to the United States Capitol Police.</a></p> <p>In court papers filed Tuesday, police said that bartender Michael Hoyt &quot;regretted not having enough time to put something in Boehner’s drink&quot; and that he had also planned to &quot;shoot Boehner and take off.&quot; His reasons, according to police, included his beliefs  <a href="http://www.wcpo.com/news/local-news/hamilton-county/deer-park/michael-hoyt-john-boehner-plot-fbi-says-boehners-bartender-at-country-club-planned-to-poison-him" target="_blank">that Boehner was mean to him at the country club, that Boehner was responsible for the Ebola virus, and that Boehner was the devil</a>.</p> <p>The man known as &quot;Bartender Mike&quot; was fired in October from Wetherington Country Club in West Chester, Ohio and was placed in a psychiatric ward after making the threats toward Boehner, police said. Hoyt has a history of mental illness, according to the documents. He was treated for a psychotic episode two years ago and was prescribed medication, which he voluntarily stopped taking after about six months, according to the FBI.</p> <div>  </div> <p>Hoyt had also emailed Boehner&apos;s wife, Debbie, before calling the police on himself. He blamed his firing on Boehner.</p> <p>In the email, Hoyt says:</p> <blockquote> <p>&quot;If I had any intention of hurting Mr. Boehner, I could have poisoned his wine at Wetherington many, many times.&quot;</p> </blockquote> <p>When Debbie Boehner replies, &quot;What is this about??&quot; Hoyt says:</p> <blockquote> <p>“Mrs. Boehner, I was fired. I could not email Mr. Boehner directly because of the ZIP code block on his email. It doesn’t matter anyway. If he took a real interest in anything, he would ensure his club was better than the country, but they are exactly the same and life goes on. Sincerely, Mike. Mike, your former bartender.”</p> </blockquote> <p><a href="http://www.wcpo.com/news/local-news/hamilton-county/deer-park/michael-hoyt-john-boehner-plot-fbi-says-boehners-bartender-at-country-club-planned-to-poison-him" target="_blank">Police said they later seized a number of weapons, ammunition, prophetic writing entries and list of other country club members at Hoyt&apos;s home.</a></p> <p>Boehner is an avid golfer with a single-digit handicap. President Obama, a fellow golf nut, <a href="http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/210462-obama-boehner-biden-my-favorite-golf-partners" target="_blank">has said that Boehner is one of his favorite golf partners despite the Republican house speaker being on the opposite side of the political aisle</a>. Boehner addressed the charges against Hoyt through a spokesman Tuesday.</p> <p>&quot;Speaker Boehner is aware of this situation, and sincerely thanks the FBI, the Capitol Police and local authorities in Ohio for their efforts,&quot; Michael Steel, Boehner&apos;s spokesman, wrote in a statement released Jan. 13.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:80648d4ea04c4f27365d50362386dd34" t="1421262912" feed="200853" position="34"><title>Cheyenne Woods, Tiger Woods' Niece, Granted Exemption to LPGA Season Opener</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/cheyenne-woods-granted-exemption-lpga-season-opener</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/14/Cheyenne%2520Woods.jpg?itok=ACEPOd1a" t="image/jpeg" author="Matt Roberts/Getty Images">Cheyenne Woods during day four of the 2014 Ladies Masters. (Matt Roberts/Getty Images)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2014/11/29/gallery_images/CheyenneWoods7_600.jpg?itok=WISzmWMW" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Cheyenne Woods will make her LPGA season debut at the Coates Golf Championship after being granted one of two sponsor exemptions for the LPGA season opener, <a href="http://www.lpga.com/golf/news/2015/coates-sponsor-exemption-woods.aspx" target="_blank">the LPGA announced Tuesday.</a></p> <p><a href="http://www.golf.com/2014/12/07/cheyenne-woods-tigers-niece-earns-lpga-tour-card" target="_blank">Tiger Woods&apos; niece earned her tour card last month at the LPGA Q-school</a> after playing the Symetra Tour last season. She won the Australian Ladies Masters last year on the Ladies European Tour.</p> <p>Alexandria Jacobsen (née Buelow), a Stetson graduate who has played 48 Symetra Tour events to date, is the other exemption.</p> <div> </div> <p>You can see Woods in action for the first time on the LPGA Tour January 26-31 at the Golden Ocala Golf &amp; Equestrian Club in Ocala, Fla.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:966f20029ce110f45b50e5256e8be6a8" t="1421259331" feed="200853" position="35"><title>Hunter Mahan: 7 New Ways to Hit Every Green</title><link>http://www.golf.com/instruction/hunter-mahan-7-new-ways-hit-every-green</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-1.jpg?itok=kSr5bbzA" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan2.jpg?itok=YP7ZB31T" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-3_0.jpg?itok=9vyRljpT" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-4_1.jpg?itok=hXVqd7jV" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-5_0.jpg?itok=jTIPoDle" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-6.jpg?itok=1EuTU_pL" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-7_0.jpg?itok=3TzHkZ66" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>I rank among the Tour&apos;s best drivers, but I take even more pride in my iron game. Like you, I&apos;ve suffered through frustrating bouts of &quot;iron deficiency.&quot; These days, though, crisp contact is automatic—my irons almost swing themselves. (In 2014, I finished seventh on Tour in greens hit from 150 to 175 yards, up from 41st in 2013.) When it comes to irons, I&apos;ve cracked the code. The secret? Make the clubface feel like an extension of your body, moving and rotating in unity with your hip and shoulder turns. Hitting square, pure irons has never been easier. I&apos;ve broken down my technique into seven simple moves. Use these keys to elevate your iron game and become a green-hitting machine.</p> <h3><strong>1. ADDRESS</strong></h3> <div>  </div> <p><strong>ALIGN YOUR BODY TO THE CLUBFACE, NOT VICE VERSA</strong></p> <p><strong>Steal the straight-shooter&apos;s secret to on-target alignment</strong></p> <p>I&apos;m always asked what sets weekend players and Tour pros apart. Aside from some technique-related issues, the most glaring difference is in the way better players practice. You work on swinging the club. We work on hitting targets. As a result, amateurs tend to mis-aim like crazy. I&apos;m guilty of aiming problems, too, and if a touring pro can line up too far left or right of the target, just imagine what alignment flaws may hinder your game. And the fix is not as simple as &quot;set up square.&quot; Your eyes can deceive you if you go about lining up the wrong way. The trick? First align the clubface square to the target. Then align your body to the clubface. It&apos;s much easier this way than the other way around. Try this visual: Once you have the clubface set, imagine 2×4s attached to your chest, forearms, knees and feet. Adjust your stance until the boards point parallel left of the target line (photo, above), like four railroad tracks running in the same direction. This square setup gives you a much better chance of hitting your target.</p> <h3><strong>2. TAKEAWAY</strong></h3> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan2.jpg?itok=YP7ZB31T" /> </div> <p><strong>SLOW EQUALS SMOOTH</strong></p> <p><strong>How do you take the club back with ideal tempo? It&apos;s as easy as 3, 2, 1</strong></p> <p>I&apos;m a &quot;backswing-centric&quot; golfer. If the first few feet of your motion are solid, I believe the rest of your swing will fall into place. But what do most weekend players do? They whip the club back or immediately hinge the club up. To relax your pace going back, try this: At address, count down aloud from three (&quot;3, 2, 1&quot;), then slowly, simultaneously move your shoulders, chest, arms, hands and clubhead. Counting down in an easy cadence lets you build smooth backswing momentum, so you won&apos;t sprint out of the blocks. And it helps you feel the clubhead move and turn at your body&apos;s pace. You&apos;ve done it correctly if your arms and the clubhead reach the top at the same time.</p> <h3><strong>3. BACKSWING</strong></h3> <div> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-3_0.jpg?itok=9vyRljpT" /> </div> </div> <p><strong>GET EXTRA STEEP TO GO DEEP</strong></p> <p><strong>Point your left shoulder at the ball for a perfect, power-rich move to the top</strong></p> <p>I&apos;m not a fan of the old tip that says to turn your left shoulder into your chin. Technically it&apos;s correct, but it encourages a flat turn instead of the steep one you need for hitting an iron. And when your shoulder turn is flat, you tend to lift your upper body in your backswing and swing the club below the ideal plane. This results in a sweeping angle of impact (which causes thin shots), rather than an angle that allows the club to drive down and through the ball. My advice? Instead of turning your left shoulder into your chin, turn it under your chin. You&apos;ll create the steepness needed for a descending attack. You&apos;ve done it correctly if, when you reach the top of your backswing, your left shoulder points near the ball—not well behind it. It should also feel as though you&apos;re pushing 100 percent of your body weight into the ground. Now you&apos;re set to make perfect contact and compress the ball, adding yards with every swing.</p> <h3><strong>4. DOWNSWING</strong></h3> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-4_1.jpg?itok=hXVqd7jV" /> </div> <p><strong>MAINTAIN YOUR HEIGHT</strong></p> <p><strong>Here&apos;s an easy visual to ensure blistering strike every time</strong></p> <p>Pros talk of maintaining their &quot;angles&quot; on the downswing. What we&apos;re really saying is we want to maintain our height, because the moment you dip your body or raise it up, your chances for quality contact go out the window. Focus on two areas in the downswing. First, keep the flex in your knees until just before impact—no straightening or bending allowed. Keeping your feet firmly planted on the ground will help with this. Second, make sure your chest is the same height at impact as it was at the top of your backswing. If you tend to lift your chest on your downswing (and catch the ball thin more often than flush), you&apos;re probably standing too close to the ball at setup. On the other hand, if you&apos;re guilty of lowering your chest (leading to fat contact), you&apos;re likely standing too far from the ball. For a quick fix, look down at address and check that your hands are just in front of your toes. That will help you maintain your posture all the way down.</p> <h3><strong>5. DELIVERY</strong></h3> <div> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-5_0.jpg?itok=jTIPoDle" /> </div> </div> <p><strong>“BUMP&quot; YOUR LEFT HIP</strong></p> <p><strong>A simple shift instantly corrects your swing path. Ball, meet the sweet spot!</strong></p> <p>Yes, you have to turn your hips in your downswing, but you don&apos;t need to make it a priority. For starters, your hips turn no matter how much you think about turning them. And overdoing your hip turn makes your swing too flat through impact. Rather than aggressively clearing them, shift your hips toward the target at the start of your downswing, because this gets your energy moving toward the target. More importantly, it moves the bottom of your swing arc slightly ahead of the ball. The bump is what lets good iron players hit the ball first, then take a divot. Don&apos;t be a &quot;turn and sweeper.&quot; Shift left and drive the clubhead down and through the ball. You&apos;ll get much better loft, more distance, and the shot-stopping spin you need to hold fast greens.</p> <h3><strong>6. IMPACT</strong></h3> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-6.jpg?itok=1EuTU_pL" /> </div> <p><strong>HIT ALL THE WAY THROUGH THE ZONE</strong></p> <p><strong>There&apos;s more to impact than just contact. Keep swinging and squaring—or you&apos;ll slice!</strong></p> <p>Weekend players are a little too obsessed with impact. They&apos;re so focused on squaring the clubface at the exact moment they make contact with the ball that they actually stop their swing. &quot;Hitting and halting&quot; makes it virtually impossible to produce the contact needed to hit greens. The act of squaring the face should be a continuous movement, from roughly knee height to knee height. If you stop the natural rotation of your body and the clubface, you&apos;re done for.</p> <p>The dreaded &quot;hit and halt&quot; is also a fast track to thin contact, because when you stop rotating through impact, you tend to leave more weight on your back foot. I suggest you completely ignore the ball and picture impact as a point about a foot past your left big toe. That will encourage you to swing all the way through impact, to continue squaring the face, and to properly shift your weight over your left foot. You should feel as though your arms, body and clubhead are moving in unison and rotating at the same pace. Picture a triangle between your arms and in the middle of your chest, and swing it all the way through impact without altering its shape or position. That will make your contact crisper and more consistent.</p> <h3><strong>7. FINISH</strong></h3> <div> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/07/Hunter-Mahan-7_0.jpg?itok=3TzHkZ66" /> </div> </div> <p><strong>SEEK BALANCE</strong></p> <p><strong>Combine all seven moves in one easy drill!</strong></p> <p>Your finish position is more than just the conclusion of your swing. It&apos;s the result of all the moves you&apos;ve made leading up to the finish, and it reflects the quality of your entire motion. Off-balance finish? Bad swing. Balanced finish? Good swing. It&apos;s that simple.</p> <p>If you&apos;re mis-hitting your irons, start with the finish. Without a ball, make slow swings with the sole goal of finishing in perfect balance. Good balance is when you can hold your finish as long as you like, with the left side of your body—from your feet to your shoulders—forming a straight line.</p> <p>If there&apos;s any bend to your left side, or if your body is fighting to stay upright, you&apos;ve lost some rhythm and tempo along the way. Make your backswing slow and deliberate. This sets the rhythm for your entire motion. It&apos;s okay to feel as though you&apos;re swinging slow. Trust me—if you make the other moves I&apos;ve discussed on these pages, you&apos;ll have plenty of swing speed where it counts: at impact. Plus, this drill lets you better sense the relationship between your body and the clubface, from start to finish. This is the type of full swing feel and control that will help you hit more greens and rip approach shots to tap-in range, leading to a lot more birdies.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Hunter Mahan</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:04204ddd358522969a876061339a08a2" t="1421257523" feed="200853" position="36"><title>PGA Tour Suspends Bhavik Patel One Year for PED Violation</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/pga-tour-suspends-bhavik-patel-one-year-ped-violation</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/14/Bhavik%2520Patel.jpg?itok=xAyxkFaT" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Bhavik Patel tees off in the first round of the Pacific Rubiales Colombia Championship in Bogota, Colombia. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>The PGA Tour has suspended Bhavik Patel, a 24-year-old Web.com Tour pro from Bakersfield, Calif., for one year for violating the PGA Tour’s Anti-Doping Policy on performance-enhancing drugs.</p> <p>According to a statement issued from Commissioner Tim Finchem’s office, Patel’s suspension began on Oct. 7, 2014, so he will be eligible to play again on Oct. 7, 2015.</p> <p>“In an effort to overcome an injury, I made a lapse of judgment,” said Patel in the Tour’s statement. “I regret my decision but have learned from the experience and look forward to returning to competition.”</p> <p>The Tour did not reveal what substance triggered the positive test.</p> <p>Patel is the second player known to have been suspended by the Tour for violating its performance-enhancing drug policy. <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/barron-faces-uncertain-future-after-being-denied-chance-play-q-school" target="_blank">Journeyman Doug Barron tested positive for testosterone and a beta-blocker in 2009</a> and was also suspended for one year, though his suspension was lifted after a lawsuit he filed against the Tour was settled.</p> <p>Vijay Singh faced discipline following his <a href="http://www.si.com/nfl/2013/01/28/strange-lab-lured-numerous-athletes" target="_blank">2013 admission to <em>Sports Illustrated</em></a> that he used deer antler spray, a product containing the growth hormone IGF-1, a banned substance, but the Tour reversed its decision after the World Anti-Doping Agency ruled that the product didn’t contain enough IGF-1 to trigger a positive test. Singh’s lawsuit over allegations of “disparate treatment” <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/vijay-singh-fights-fellow-tour-players-could-expand-his-lawsuit-against-pga-tour-lawyer-says" target="_blank">remains before the New York State Supreme Court</a>, with the next status conference scheduled for Feb. 15.</p> <p><a href="http://www.drugfreesport.com/rec/files/clientforms/2013Anti-DopingManual_1.pdf" target="_blank">According to the PGA Tour’s Anti-Doping Program Manual</a>, in the event of a positive test for performance-enhancing drugs resulting in a suspension or disqualification, it is the Tour’s policy to “publish the name of the player, the fact that the player committed an anti-doping rule violation, and the sanction imposed.”</p> <p>The Tour is not required to announce any disciplinary actions against players who test positive for recreational drugs.</p> <p><em>What do you think of the PGA Tour&apos;s Anti-Doping Program? Join the debate in the comments section below.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Pete Madden</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d1a910b9a939e9d42582af597fc92125" t="1421257509" feed="200853" position="37"><title>Lydia Ko Unveils New Look in LPGA Media Guide</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/14/lydia-ko-unveils-new-look-lpga-media-guide</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Lydia%2520Ko%25202015.jpg?itok=4B73gcM5" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/LydiaKo.jpg?itok=sRXJEJND" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Lydia Ko is debuting a new look to kick off her new season.</p> <p>The 17-year-old phenom shed her glasses and hair-tie in the LPGA&apos;s 2014-2015 online media guide.</p> <p>If Ko is trying to make a statement - &quot;I&apos;m not a kid anymore and I mean business&quot; - it&apos;s working!</p> <p>Ko turned pro in October 2013 following 130 weeks at the top of the ladies amateur list. In 2012, Ko was the youngest amateur to win a professional tour event at 14 (that record is now held by Canadian Brooke Henderson, who was also 14 at the time), and still holds the record for youngest player to win an LPGA tour event - all before turning pro.</p> <p>Here she is on her player&apos;s page at lpga.com:</p> <div>  </div> <p>And here she is during last November&apos;s CME Group Tour Championship:</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/LydiaKo.jpg?itok=sRXJEJND" /> </div> <p>With three tour wins in 2014 including the CME Group Tour Championship, Ko is looking to once again dominate the field in 2015 - signature glasses or not!</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:14c0132c89c4cef0f7b2356d7bda7606" t="1421247625" feed="200853" position="38"><title>Rory McIlroy Opens Defining Year Seeking First Win in Abu Dhabi</title><link>http://www.golf.com/mcilroy-opens-defining-year-seeking-first-win-abu-dhabi</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/RoryMcIlroy1400.jpg?itok=YAGfwBZ-" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Rory McIlroy and Rickie Fowler will play the first two rounds together in Abu Dhabi. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Rory McIlroy isn&apos;t divulging what is on his list of seven goals for 2015 that he jotted down on the back of his boarding pass on a flight to Dubai last week.</p> <p>Completing a career Grand Slam at the Masters in April? Surely that was No. 1. A court case against his former management company, scheduled for February, is also a defining early year date for the world&apos;s top-ranked player.</p> <p>Winning this week&apos;s Abu Dhabi Championship may not have been on the list, but it would end years of frustration for McIlroy at what has become his traditional year-opening tournament.</p> <p>McIlroy has finished second at Abu Dhabi Golf Club in three of the last four years. On two of those occasions, he was hit with rule penalties that ultimately cost him victory.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;One of the goals this week is just to have no penalty shots when I don&apos;t need them,&apos;&apos; he said. &apos;&apos;And see where I end up at the end of the week.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Losing out to Spain&apos;s Pablo Larrazabal in a thrilling end to last year&apos;s tournament was one of the few regrets for McIlroy in a stunning 2014.</p> <p>He won the British Open and the U.S. PGA Championship to double his tally of major titles, returned to the top of the rankings, and was one of the stars of the European team that retained the Ryder Cup at Gleneagles.</p> <p>McIlroy wants more.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I didn&apos;t achieve everything that I wanted to last year,&apos;&apos; he said.</p> <p>It has become something of a ritual for him to write down his objectives for the season on his boarding pass on his flight out for his first tournament of the year. He puts the list in his wallet and memorizes it.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I&apos;ll take that boarding pass out at the end of the year and see how well I&apos;ve done,&apos;&apos; McIlroy said.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I feel 2014 has really set me up for another great year. I&apos;m coming in with a nice little bit of momentum, and (my) game is feeling good.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>With McIlroy having had a month off, his rivals in Abu Dhabi will hope Boy Wonder is rusty.</p> <p>It is another strong field, with No. 2 Henrik Stenson, U.S. Open champion Martin Kaymer, No. 6 Justin Rose and American star Rickie Fowler - making his debut in the desert - among the other entries.</p> <p>McIlroy and Fowler are in the same group for the first two days, marking the first time they have played together since the singles at the Ryder Cup. McIlroy put on an awesome performance that Sunday, winning 5 and 4.</p> <p>Kaymer is a three-time winner (2008, &apos;10 and &apos;11) in Abu Dhabi, and was one stroke off first place in 2009. The German is one of the few players to have a better record on the course than McIlroy, who was third in 2010 and tied for fifth in 2009 before his run of runner-up finishes.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;It&apos;s a golf course I&apos;ve always felt comfortable on, one that has suited me, and I have played well here,&apos;&apos; McIlroy said. &apos;&apos;This is my eighth year in a row starting the season off here, so I&apos;m pretty familiar with the place, and looking forward to another strong start to the season.&apos;&apos;</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:602ee154aef603c25f9f3e8e59ab59cc" t="1421193600" feed="200853" position="39"><title>Golf on TV: Weekly Schedule</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/golf-tv-weekly-schedule</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/14/jimmy-walker.jpg?itok=gmykIQca" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Jimmy Walker celebrates with his family after winning the 2014 Sony Open. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p><strong><span>WEEK OF JANUARY 15-18</span><br /><em>(All times Eastern)</em></strong></p> <p><span style="font-size:18px;"><span><strong><u>PGA TOUR: Sony Open in Hawaii</u></strong></span></span><br /><span style="font-size:16px;"><span>Friday, Round 1: 7:00-10:30 p.m. GOLF <br /> Saturday, Round 2: 7:00-10:30 p.m. GOLF <br /> Sunday, Round 3: 7:00.-10:30 p.m. GOLF <br /> Monday, Final Round: 4:00-6:00 p.m. NBC; 6:00-8:00 p.m. GOLF</span></span></p> <p> </p> <p><span style="font-size: 18px;"><strong><u>EUROPEAN TOUR: Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship</u></strong></span><br /><span style="font-size: 16px;">Thursday, Round 1: 12:30-3:30 a.m. GOLF <br /> Friday, Round 2: 2:30-5:00 a.m. GOLF <br /> Saturday, Round 3: 4:00-8:00 a.m. GOLF <br /> Sunday, Final Round: 3:30-8:00 a.m. GOLF</span></p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:28a6aca2a02e48a6ce57689934de4ca7" t="1421193600" feed="200853" position="40"><title>13 Hot New Drivers to Boost Your Distance and Direction</title><link>http://www.golf.com/equipment/13-hot-drivers-boost-your-distance-and-direction</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/14/New-Driver-Lead-Main.jpg?itok=j7Kyhj2X" t="image/jpeg" author="Michael Chini">Clockwise from top left: Bridgestone J715; Callaway XR; Cobra Fly-Z+; Nike Vapor Flex; Ping G30 LS Tec; TaylorMade R15 (Michael Chini)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Bridgestone-J715.jpg?itok=1fRIE2dE" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Callaway-XR.jpg?itok=-3JSZAMG" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Callaway-Big-Bertha-Alpha-815.jpg?itok=cwzeHaqJ" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Cobra-Fly-Z-%252B.jpg?itok=rUIK-vU0" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Nike-Vapor-Flex.jpg?itok=EfvquAIT" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Ping-G30-LS-Tec.jpg?itok=h7cHVVnY" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/TaylorMade-R15.jpg?itok=dlE45bx3" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Driver technology is evolving rapidly, with brand-new high-tech features appearing every year. There is one main focus pushing innovation in the driver-manufacturing industry, a desire every golfer can understand: increased distance. All golfers want to add length to their tee shots, and the more the better. But fear not, driver engineers and designers at the top club manufacturers are hot on the case.</p> <p>With ClubTest 2015 just around the corner, we&apos;re previewing 13 new drivers that will be hitting store shelves in time for the heart of the golf season. Learn all about the new longsticks, and come back next month for full reviews from ClubTest.</p> <div>  </div> <p><strong>Bridgestone J715 <br /> Price: $399</strong></p> <p>Thin is in. The J715&apos;s crown is only 0.5 millimeters at its thinnest and features springlike ribs on the interior that company officials say can increase ball speeds by 2 mph and launch angle by as much as 2 degrees at Tour-level swing speeds. A process called &quot;power milling&quot; creates a rougher clubface so that the ball doesn&apos;t roll up the face as much as it normally would and thus stays there longer. The combination reduces spin by up to 350 rpm at higher launch angles [12.5°] and by 200 rpm at lower launch angles [10.5°] for a longer, more penetrating flight. Two removable weights in the sole—one behind the center of the face and the other more rearward and heel-biased—are used to alter the club&apos;s center of gravity [CG]. From the factory, the J715 driver comes with a 10-gram weight in back and a 4-gram weight in front, but flipping them will lower launch angle by as much as 0.75° and decrease spin by up to 200 rpm. A weight kit [$80] sold separately includes 2-, 4-, 6-, 8-, 10-and 12- gram plugs for more customization. The club&apos;s hosel offers further adjustability, allowing face-angle changes from 1° open to 1° closed, as well as lie angles from standard to 2° upright.</p> <p>Lofts: 8.5°, 9.5°, 10.5°, 12°. Available February 15.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Callaway-XR.jpg?itok=-3JSZAMG" /> </div> <p><strong>Callaway XR <br /> Price: $349</strong></p> <p>Last year, Callaway reestablished itself as a leader in driver technology with its Big Bertha and X2 Hot lines. The company looks to keep the good times rolling with the debut of the XR.</p> <p>Callaway believes the XR can help you swing faster, generate more ball speed and hit longer drives. The club&apos;s thin, lightweight face insert contributes to a low CG, and more efficient transfer of energy across the hitting area while the aerodynamic crown reduces drag during the swing. In addition, the Project X LZ shaft is designed to maximize shaft load during the downswing. The company&apos;s well-known OptiFit hosel enables you to change loft (from 2° stronger to 1° weaker) and lie to optimize launch conditions. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°, 12°, 13.5°. $349. In stores on February 20.</p> <p>The lower-spinning XR Pro ($399), for better players, features many of the same technologies. It has a more traditional shape plus a forged composite crown, which contributes to lower CG and less spin. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°. In stores on March 20.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Callaway-Big-Bertha-Alpha-815.jpg?itok=cwzeHaqJ" /> </div> <p><strong>Callaway Big Bertha Alpha 815 <br /> Price: $449</strong></p> <p>Callaway&apos;s reborn Big Bertha topped its class in our ClubTest earlier this year. Its replacement, the Big Bertha Alpha 815, takes the signature feature of the equally acclaimed Big Bertha Alpha driver and puts it to work in a model that average Joes can enjoy. The industry-first &quot;gravity core&quot; rod has 10.5 grams of tungsten at one end and 1.5 grams of nylon at the other. You place the rod into the head to move the club&apos;s CG higher or lower to optimize launch, spin and ball speed. The high-CG position [nylon end is closer to the sole] plays like a &quot;mid-spin&quot; driver, while the low-CG position generates 300 rpm less spin. Compared to the current Big Bertha, the Alpha 815 delivers similar mid-spin drives when the rod is in the high-CG position, and 300 rpm less spin in the low-CG position.</p> <p>The Alpha 815 has the same light, forged composite crown as before, along with a thinner, livelier titanium face that&apos;s made possible by stiffened ribs on the crown and sole, inside the body. Also, removable plugs in the heel and toe [7 gram and 1 gram] can be used to create fade or draw bias. Like its predecessor, the Alpha 815&apos;s adjustable OptiFit hosel provides loft options [from 2° stronger to 1° weaker], as well as neutral or draw setting. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°, 12°.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Cobra-Fly-Z-%2B.jpg?itok=rUIK-vU0" /> </div> <p><strong>Cobra Fly–Z+ <br /> Price: $399</strong></p> <p>Cobra&apos;s Fly-Z+ driver, for scratch players to 15-handicappers, utilizes a clever front-back weighting system to optimize CG location. The 15-gram weight [an aluminum shell filled with tungsten nickel] can be moved between the middle of the sole and the rear. According to company testing, the forward CG position [with the gold-colored weight closer to the face] creates a penetrating, low-spin flight, while the back position launches the ball higher with 300 rpm more spin. To enhance ball speeds on mis-hits, the thin, forged titanium clubface includes a &quot;Speed Channel&quot; around the edges. You might think the channel creates more speed because of increased face flex on those shots. Not so. It actually boosts speed because mass that&apos;s removed from the face gets redistributed, which increases the club&apos;s MOI by approximately 10 to 15 percent on mis-hits. The 460 cc head features &quot;MyFly&quot; technology, which allows eight loft adjustments between 8° and 11°, plus the &quot;SmartPad&quot; sole, which is designed to maintain a square clubface angle even as loft adjustments are made. The club comes in five head colors: red, orange, blue, black and white. Available February 1.</p> <p>The Fly-Z [$329] features the same adjustable hosel with eight loft settings [9° to 12°] and color options as the Fly-Z+, but not a &quot;flip weight.&quot; Built with mid-handicappers in mind, the Fly-Z produces 300 rpm more spin and is more stable on mis-hits than the Fly-Z+ in the back-weight position.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Nike-Vapor-Flex.jpg?itok=EfvquAIT" /> </div> <p><strong>Nike Vapor Flex <br /> Price: $499</strong></p> <p>Over the years, various methods have come along to help golfers customize their drivers—adjustable hosels, interchangeable weights, and sliders on the sole, among others. Now comes the Nike Vapor Flex, whose combination of technologies makes it one of the most customizable models yet. Its new adjustable hosel, called FlexLoft 2.0, can set loft [+/- 2°] and face angle to create 15 possible launch and shot-bias combinations. The redesign is also 30 percent lighter than the previous FlexLoft, which allows more mass to be distributed elsewhere in the clubhead.</p> <p>A second tuning technology, called &quot;Flex-Flight,&quot; incorporates an unbalanced polymer resin rod—9 grams on one end, 0.5 grams on the other—that&apos;s placed in a tube in the rear of the head. Orienting the rod with the heavy end in the middle of the head moves the CG 2.4 millimeters closer to the face, which produces a 1° lower launch angle and decreases the spin rate by 300 rpm.</p> <p>Nike has also built upon its go-to cavity-back design for enhanced ball speed and forgiveness. Designers updated the &quot;Covert Cavity&quot; with &quot;FlyBeam&quot; supports that stiffen the crown, sole and back of the clubhead for a greater transfer of energy to the ball. The cavity itself maintains MOI and forgiveness on off-center hits while moving the club&apos;s CG forward to reduce spin. A new channel along the sole close to the leading edge combines with the cavity to produce more face flex on mis-hits, a higher COR and increased ball speeds.</p> <p>The Vapor Flex comes standard with Mitsubishi&apos;s Diamana S+ Blue Board shaft. The Mitsubishi Diamana S+ White Board, Mitsubishi Fubuki ZT50 or Z50 shafts are also available at no additional charge. Available January 30.</p> <p>Both the Vapor Pro [$399] and the Vapor Speed [$299] feature a channel behind the face for greater flex, supportive FlyBeams to stiffen the head, and Nike&apos;s FlexLoft 2.0 hosel for loft-and-lie adjustability. However, neither model offers the Flex-Flight adjustable CG technology. The Vapor Pro is Rory&apos;s new stick, while the Vapor Speed is the most forgiving driver in the family and produces slightly more backspin than the other two models.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/Ping-G30-LS-Tec.jpg?itok=h7cHVVnY" /> </div> <p><strong>Ping G30 LS Tec <br /> Price: $379</strong></p> <p>The newest, stoutest club in Ping&apos;s G30 driver series is the G30 LS Tec. It&apos;s best-suited for fast swing-speed players who&apos;d benefit from a stick that produces lower spin rates than the standard G30 while maintaining reasonable levels of forgiveness. To accomplish this, Ping&apos;s designers moved the club&apos;s CG 8 percent closer to the face than in the G30, which decreases spin on center hits by up to 400 rpm. The CG is as much as 35 percent lower and 30 percent farther back in the head than many &quot;low-forward&quot; CG drivers, for added forgiveness on off-center contact. In addition, the high balance-point TFC 419D shaft allows for a marginally heavier club head and, thus, higher MOI. The redesigned adjustable hosel enables you to tweak loft stronger or weaker by 1° in half-degree increments. And, like the rest of the G30 driver family, &quot;turbulators&quot; on the crown are engineered to reduce aerodynamic drag during the swing so you can generate faster clubhead speeds. Lofts: 9°, 10.5°. Available February 12.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/14/TaylorMade-R15.jpg?itok=dlE45bx3" /> </div> <p><strong>TaylorMade R15 <br /> Price: $429; $499 with TP shafts</strong></p> <p>Tinkerers rejoice. The R15 driver has a pair of 12.5-gram sliding weights in the sole, providing five grams more movable mass than the single 20-gram weight in the current SLDR. Splitting weights between the heel and toe increases the club&apos;s forgiveness; moving both weights in the same direction adds shot-shape bias; and placing them both in the middle produces the fastest ball speed. A new adjustable hosel lets players increase or decrease loft by as much as 2°. [The loft sleeve previously offered +/-1.5°.] What&apos;s more, the 40-gram sole track is more flexible and 12 millimeters closer to the leading edge than in the SLDR. This creates a lower, more forward CG. Company testing reveals that the new track system—it acts like the &quot;speed pocket&quot; in JetSpeed drivers—produces shots that launch 0.7° higher, spin 100 rpm less, and have a marginally higher peak height than shots hit with the SLDR 460. It&apos;s more impressive when you consider that the R15 is nine grams lighter than the SLDR. The R15 comes in white or black and in 460 cc or 430 cc heads. Lofts: 9.5°, 10.5°, 12° or 14°.</p> <p>TaylorMade&apos;s AeroBurner driver ($299; $369 with TP shafts) boasts subtle yet significant aerodynamic upgrades over the JetSpeed. In short, it&apos;s designed to reduce swing drag so you can generate faster head speeds. For starters, airflow is enhanced by a finlike piece along the hosel, while the club&apos;s rounded toe shape and crown curvature also help to lessen drag. In addition, the club&apos;s overall weight is under 300 grams. Testing conducted by TaylorMade shows that players swing the AeroBurner 1 mph faster than the JetSpeed and SLDR drivers. Plus, the updated &quot;speed pocket&quot; now extends the length of the sole, which increases face flexibility on shots struck low or on the heel or toe. The result is a sweet spot that&apos;s 10 percent larger than last year&apos;s JetSpeed driver. It&apos;s worth noting that the 460 cc AeroBurner has a fixed hosel. According to company officials, an adjustable loft sleeve that extends into the sole [like the one used in the R15 driver] would have impaired the speed pocket&apos;s performance.</p> <p>Lofts: 9.5°, 10.5°, 12°, 17° [HL].</p> <p> </p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:1006cc7ef1b113d84380110d19cb252c" t="1421179580" feed="200853" position="41"><title>The Clubs That Won: Patrick Reed's Odyssey Putter and Callaway Driver</title><link>http://www.golf.com/equipment/clubs-won-reeds-odyssey-putter</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/reedhawaii.jpg?itok=g5XmzqwB" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty">Patrick Reed won his fourth PGA Tour event at the Hyundai Tournament of Champions. (Getty)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2015/01/05/BBAlpha815FWHybrid.jpg?itok=5--TUlIF" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/WhiteHotPro3.jpg?itok=V4d4SZp9" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/BBDoubleBlack.jpg?itok=kOivIw4Q" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>An exciting finish to the Hyundai Tournament of Champions in Hawaii Monday night produced Patrick Reed as the first PGA Tour winner of 2015. Though the event did not draw as strong a field as some would have liked, the finish came down to a one-on-one battle between two Ryder Cup teammates who, prior to Reed’s victory, had six wins between them since August of 2013.</p> <p>A number of clutch shots contributed to Reed’s fourth PGA Tour win, the most impressive of which was an 80-yard wedge that Reed holed for eagle on the par-4 16th hole.</p> <div> </div> <p>But the club that ultimately won Reed the tournament was his putter. As we <a href="http://www.golf.com/equipment/hyundai-predictions-and-equipment-round”">noted last week</a>, the last five winners at Kapalua (before Reed) finished in the top 3 in total putts. Reed broke that streak, but finished an impressive fourth, recording only 114 putts through 72 holes.</p> <p>Reed used an Odyssey White Hot Pro #3 putter en route to victory. Among the clutch putts he made was an 18-foot birdie putt on the first playoff to bury Jimmy Walker.</p> <p>Here’s a look at Odyssey’s White Hot Pro #3, followed by a closer look at the Ryder Cup inspired model Reed had in play in Hawaii.</p> <div>  </div> <p> </p> <blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned="" data-instgrm-version="4"> <div> <div> <div>   </div> </div> <p><a href="https://instagram.com/p/xw67_gSa2w/" target="_top">Patrick Reed is T3 heading into the final round of the Hyundai TOC. Here&apos;s his #USA-inspired White Hot Pro #3 gamer on the putting green in #Hawaii. #OdysseyGolf #PGATour</a></p> <p>A photo posted by Odyssey Golf (@odysseygolf) on Jan 12, 2015 at 10:43am PST</p> </div> </blockquote> <p> </p> <p>Reed also ranked fourth in driving distance (282 yards) using Callaway’s Big Bertha Alpha 815 Double Black Diamond driver. He first put the club in the bag at the Hero World Challenge in December, an 8.5° model with a Fujikura Fuel 75-gram extra stiff shaft cut to 44.5 inches. Reed’s driver is configured with a draw bias.</p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/BBDoubleBlack.jpg?itok=kOivIw4Q" /> </div> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Brendan Mohler</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:d133a042487f905028b90f5a92dd4cce" t="1421176743" feed="200853" position="42"><title>Donald Trump, Miss Universe Contestants Open Red Tiger at Doral</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/13/donald-trump-miss-universe-contestants-open-red-tiger-course-doral-style</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/DonaldTrump.jpg?itok=hcxmubbB" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Donald Trump and Miss Universe contestants open the Red Tiger course. (Getty Images)</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Donald Trump unveiled his redesign of the Red Tiger course at Trump National Doral on Monday with a low-key, buttoned-down ceremony befitting the sport&apos;s traditions.</p> <p>Just kidding. Trump is a man who knows how to make a splash. He invited contestants from his Miss Universe pageant to take part in the official opening.</p> <p>We&apos;d rank Miss Ireland Lisa Madden&apos;s swing the best with Miss Israel Doron Matalon close behind. Give Miss Czech Republic Gabriela Frankova credit for her perseverance. It can&apos;t be easy to hit the ball in those shoes while trying to keep your skirt down in the wind.</p> <div class="media_embed" height="300px" width="550px"> <iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="300px" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/6BHjZYvLvF4" width="550px"></iframe> </div> <p>Trump hit his opening drive 285 yards down the middle, according to the <a href="http://www.miamiherald.com/sports/golf/article6166512.html#/tabPane=tabs-c837affa-1" target="_blank">Miami Herald&apos;s report</a>. The Red Tiger redesign follows a reworking of Doral&apos;s famed <a href="http://www.golf.com/scorecard/2014/03/07/trump-national-doral%E2%80%99s-monster-new-blue-has-old-soul#" target="_blank">Blue Monster by architects Gil Hanse and Jim Wagner</a> in 2013. That work put the teeth back into the Monster, which hosts the WGC-Cadillac Championship in March, an event won by Patrick Reed last year after he survived a blustery second round that sent scores soaring.</p> <p>The Red Tiger, Trump said, is a friendlier course.</p> <p>&quot;They can’t all be the Monster,” he said. “The Monster can be brutal.”</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Matt Newman</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:5c477ed6dc826c486348a8e0b633f042" t="1421171263" feed="200853" position="43"><title>Rory McIlroy in Abu Dhabi and More to Watch on the Euro Tour</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/european-tour-4-things-watch-abu-dhabi</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Rory-McIlroy-640-x-360.jpg?itok=wkXkfbvd" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/RickieFowler.jpg?itok=JCVVJstb" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/RobertRock.jpg?itok=4pXrhkCR" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/06/MatthewFitzpatrick.jpg?itok=H0HaxYlD" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/12/AndySullivan.jpg?itok=URygxL5i" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>A host of the world’s top players are in the Middle East this week for the 10th anniversary of the Abu Dhabi HSBC Championship.</p> <p>The tournament marks the start of the Middle East Swing – a three-event series that attracts some of the biggest names on the European Tour.</p> <p>The Abu Dhabi Championship is the traditional start of the golfing season for those who choose to neglect the South African events in December and January.</p> <p>The likes of Rory McIlroy, Justin Rose and Henrik Stenson all start their 2015 campaigns in the desert. Gregarious Spaniard Pablo Larrazabal, who edged out McIlroy and Phil Mickelson last season to claim his third European Tour title, is also making his first start of the year.</p> <p><a href="http://www.golf-monthly.co.uk/tour/us-open/us-open-news/justin-rose-my-putting-secrets-3176?utm_campaign=rose%20putting%20secrets&amp;utm_source=golf.com&amp;utm_medium=web" target="_blank"><strong>Related: Justin Rose putting secrets</strong></a></p> <p>The tournament was staged for the first time in 2006, with Chris DiMarco reigning supreme in the inaugural contest. HSBC came on board as title sponsor in 2011.</p> <p>Once again, Abu Dhabi Golf Club is the host venue. It’s a long, testing 7,600-yard layout with narrow fairways, penal rough and nine water hazards. In other words, it’s a ball-striker’s golf course.</p> <p><strong>1. Strong field</strong></p> <div>  </div> <p>The Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship attracts one of the strongest fields of the European Tour season. In fact, five of the world’s top 11 players are teeing it up. McIlroy, the world number one, has unfinished business with this event, having notched four top-three finishes in the last five years. Rose is another player who will be determined to add this title to his extensive collection. The Englishman’s birdie putt on the 72nd hole in 2013 lipped out, handing Jamie Donaldson a one-shot victory. Elsewhere, Martin Kaymer is bidding for his fourth title following wins in 2008, 2010 and 2011.</p> <p><a href="http://www.golf-monthly.co.uk/tour/tour-videos/rory-mcilroy-new-swing-sequence-54457?utm_campaign=mcilroy%20swing%20sequence&amp;utm_source=golf.com&amp;utm_medium=web" target="_blank"><strong>Related: Rory McIlroy swing sequence and analysis</strong></a></p> <p><strong>2. Rickie Fowler</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/RickieFowler.jpg?itok=JCVVJstb" /> </div> <p>Rickie Fowler accepted a tournament invitation and will be making his debut in the event. He’ll also be playing in the Irish Open in the summer – hosted by the Rory McIlroy foundation - and possibly at the Scottish Open, as per last year. If he plays in those three tournaments, along with the eight Majors and WGCs, he’d only need to compete in two more to be eligible for a European Tour card – something that I’m sure would be welcomed by all parties.</p> <p><strong>3. History</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/RobertRock.jpg?itok=4pXrhkCR" /> </div> <p>This year marks the 10th anniversary of the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship. It’s one of the circuit’s newest events, but undoubtedly one of the most popular. Kaymer and Paul Casey have triumphed here a combined five times, but perhaps the most memorable victory came in 2012, when Robert Rock (above) – a man who not long previously was selling chocolate as an assistant professional – outdueled Tiger Woods to land his second European Tour title.</p> <p><strong>4. The Rookies</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/06/MatthewFitzpatrick.jpg?itok=H0HaxYlD" /> </div> <p>Most of the pre-tournament focus will centre on the established names, but it’s worth devoting some attention to the rookie contingent, particularly Matt Fiztpatrick (above) and Renato Paratore. The former, the 2013 US Amateur Champion, finished in a tie for 5th at last week’s South African Open, while the latter, an 18-year-old superstar in the making, looks poised to make quite an impression in his first year on tour.</p> <p><strong>5. Andy Sullivan</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/12/AndySullivan.jpg?itok=URygxL5i" /> </div> <p>It’s also worth keeping an eye on Andy Sullivan in Abu Dhabi. The boisterous Englishman won his first European Tour title last week in South Africa, which included an early contender for shot of the season. His confidence and mindset will be second to none, and that, coupled with a good record in the Middle East, could spell danger for his peers.</p> <p><a href="http://www.golf-monthly.co.uk/tips/long-game/andy-sullivan-punch-shot-masterclass-56156?utm_campaign=sullivan%20punch%20shot%20masterclass&amp;utm_source=golf.com&amp;utm_medium=web" target="_blank"><strong>Related: Andy Sullivan punch-shot masterclass</strong></a></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Nick Bonfield/GOLF Monthly</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:f546a2f945e4e30a8563f6b0e34f73f7" t="1421161225" feed="200853" position="44"><title>On the PGA Tour, a Hot Stretch Can Mean Big Bucks</title><link>http://www.golf.com/pga-tour-hot-stretch-can-mean-big-bucks-0</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/11/kuchar.jpg?itok=HfAVxy9q" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images">Getty Images</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>HONOLULU (AP) The advice has been passed along for decades on the PGA Tour, and Matt Kuchar believes it has merit. He just doesn&apos;t like it.</p> <p>Call it the 80-20 equation.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I remember coming out and guys telling me you&apos;re going to make 80 percent of your money in 20 percent of your starts,&apos;&apos; Kuchar said. &apos;&apos;The idea was basically you&apos;re going to get hot a couple of times, and that&apos;s what you wait for. And it makes sense. You&apos;re going to get hot and then peter off a little bit.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Scott Stallings would be an extreme example. He won the Farmers Insurance Open at Torrey Pines last year, and that was his only finish in the top 30. One week turned out to be 79 percent of his season earnings.</p> <p>A more typical example: FedEx Cup champion Billy Horschel.</p> <p>Horschel had a hot streak in the spring of 2013 when he was runner-up in Houston, tied for third in San Antonio and won in New Orleans in a span of four starts. He didn&apos;t really heat up again for another 18 months. Horschel had only two top 10s on the PGA Tour and missed seven cuts until he stepped into a phone booth and emerged as guy who couldn&apos;t be beat. He threw away a chance to win in Boston, and then won the next two FedEx Cup playoff events.</p> <p>His tally for the year was $4.8 million to finish at No. 7 on the money list, and that doesn&apos;t include the $10 million bonus for winning the FedEx Cup. A closer look at Horschel&apos;s season last year makes him a candidate for the 80-20 club.</p> <p>He made roughly 80 percent of his season earnings in 19 percent of his starts.</p> <p>So maybe there is some truth to it.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;You get hot, you make your money in five or six tournaments. You make 80 percent in 20 percent of your starts,&apos;&apos; J.B. Holmes said. &apos;&apos;I&apos;ve been hearing that for years.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Holmes won 82 percent of his money in 25 percent of his starts, including a victory in the Wells Fargo Championship.</p> <p>Kuchar used to be one of those guys. He also won roughly 82 percent of his money from 25 percent of his tournaments in 2009. Those days are gone. Kuchar has turned into one of the most consistent players on the PGA Tour. In the last five years, he has missed only eight cuts in 121 tournaments. He has 48 top 10s during that stretch, a rate of 40 percent.</p> <p>Just like anyone else, Kuchar had a hot streak last year. In four straight weeks, he lost a chance to win the Texas Open with a 75 in the final round, he lost in a playoff in Houston when Matt Jones chipped in from 100 feet. He was in the mix at the Masters early on Sunday and tied for fifth. And then he won Hilton Head. After that, he was back to the consistent brand of golf. He never finished out of the top 20 in more than two straight starts.</p> <p>Kuchar won 81 percent of his money in 42 percent of his tournaments. He likes that ratio much better.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;The streaky way is stressful,&apos;&apos; Kuchar said. &apos;&apos;The golf I play ... you could watch me play a round of golf and it&apos;s pretty stress free. I don&apos;t do any crazy things. I don&apos;t make a ton of birdies, but I don&apos;t make a lot of bogeys, either. It&apos;s been a lot nicer the last five or six years.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Would he trade it for a $10 million bonus and one more victory?</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I don&apos;t think I&apos;d trade with Billy Horschel,&apos;&apos; he said.</p> <p>He loved the consistent play of Steve Stricker until his 2014 season was disrupted by injuries and the death of his brother. He loves the way Jim Furyk played last year. Furyk didn&apos;t win, but he gave himself plenty of chances. Winning is hard. Furyk earned 81 percent of his money in 38 percent of his starts.</p> <p>Rory McIlroy, the best benchmark in golf right now, won 81 percent of his tour-leading $8.2 million in 41 percent of his starts.</p> <p>Kuchar is all about opportunities, though he&apos;s willing to make an exception. Bubba Watson went through a 22-month drought without winning from the 2012 Masters until Riviera last year, and then he added another green jacket.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I&apos;d trade with Bubba,&apos;&apos; Kuchar said. &apos;&apos;It would be streaky, but you&apos;d throw a Masters in there.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Geoff Ogilvy is another guy who has heard all about the 80-20 equation, and he believes it to be accurate in most cases.</p> <p>It&apos;s probably true for 80 percent of the players,&apos;&apos; Ogilvy said, adding to the math. &apos;&apos;Guys like Tiger and Jack, and Jim and Kuchar, they make money in all their tournaments. So there&apos;s probably 80 percent of the players who make 80 percent of their money in 20 tournaments.&apos;&apos;</p> <p>Winning is still the ultimate. Ask any of the 34 players at Kapalua to start the year. Even so, most players would take a steady diet of contention and take their chances.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;I would rather contend every week and win a lot, too. Can you have that one?&apos;&apos; Ogilvy asked.</p> <p>Tiger Woods managed that for the better part of 15 years. He&apos;s a different animal.</p> <p>&apos;&apos;The most fun is contention,&apos;&apos; Ogilvy said. &apos;&apos;It&apos;s not fun propping up fields. I don&apos;t do this to finish 40th and have no excitement. The happiest I am on the course is in contention. I&apos;d rather be that guy.&apos;&apos;</p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author>AP News</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:e5e1a9e1f04624c0ff22a8a9aada9f8b" t="1421160348" feed="200853" position="45"><title>Rory McIlroy Writes Down His Goals on a Boarding Pass Each Year</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/rory-mcilroy-writes-down-his-goals-boarding-pass-each-year</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/461471344.jpg?itok=sFZspGiD" t="image/jpeg" author="Andrew Redington/Getty Images">Rory McIlroy during practice before the Abu Dhabi HSBC Golf Championship in the United Arab Emirates. (Andrew Redington/Getty Images)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_photo_tile_image/public/2014/12/10/Rory-Wentworth_0.jpg?itok=KLDIn1Lf" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>We already know one of Rory McIlroy&apos;s goals for 2015 -- the Green Jacket. Now we know where it&apos;s written down.</p> <p>Speaking to reporters before the <a href="http://www.europeantour.com/europeantour/season=2015/tournamentid=2015002/index.html" target="_blank">HSBC Abu Dhabi Championship</a>, McIlroy said each year on his flight from Dublin to Dubai, he jots down what he wants to accomplish on the back of his boarding pass, memorizes the goals and keeps the boarding pass in his wallet for the entire year. At year&apos;s end, he reviews his progress. </p> <p>How did he do in 2014? He wanted to have six worldwide wins and settled for four, but only wanted one major and nabbed two.</p> <p>&quot;I actually didn&apos;t achieve everything that I wanted to,&quot; McIlroy said. &quot;But still, it was a good year.&quot;</p> <p>At the end of 2014, McIlroy <a href="http://www.theguardian.com/sport/2014/oct/10/rory-mcilroy-interview-golf-masters-grandslam-hopes" target="_blank">spoke to the Guardian</a> about his goals and how they aren&apos;t always directly related to the course.</p> <p></p> <p>&quot;One of my goals this year was to be better at replying to people, to be better at getting back to emails,&quot; McIlroy said. &quot;I managed that, I&apos;m much better now. I used to be terrible. I would read something, say to myself I would get back to it later then never do it. I&apos;d have messages the next week asking, &apos;Did you get my email?&apos; That&apos;s an example of how I try to set my goals.&quot;</p> <p>McIlroy&apos;s other on-course goals were to be top 40 in strokes gained putting (he was 41st in 2014, up from 117th) and to improve his scrambling rate (88th from 145th). Those were a success.</p> <p>The world No. 1 didn&apos;t reveal his full list of goals for the upcoming year, but one of his goals for the future will be to travel sans boarding pass, presumably on his own jet.</p> <p>“One day, I won’t need a boarding pass. That’s the ultimate,&quot; he said.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Coleman McDowell</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:10715ee944b25e01ce1281b366a8accb" t="1421160347" feed="200853" position="46"><title>This Week's Heroes? Reed and Woods. Zeros? Occupy Golf</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/heroes-zeros-hyundai-tournament-champions</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Patrick-Reed.jpg?itok=n8wc4NvF" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Kapaula.jpg?itok=b6W5dTTq" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Tiger-Woods.jpg?itok=4IVYSlDy" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Sang-Moon-Bae.jpg?itok=mJ_1qdVV" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Pete-Bevacqua.jpg?itok=AlNblcXY" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Charl-Schwartzel.jpg?itok=ZAiN3GZ5" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Jimmy-Walker.jpg?itok=wwGWziMz" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Jordan-Spieth.jpg?itok=SQaLN6rD" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Chris-Kirk.jpg?itok=DTTbsN6l" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Occupy-Golf.jpg?itok=es_c_BDK" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded">  <p><strong>1. Charl Schwartzel. He once birdied the last four holes to win the Masters. Now, at the South African Open, he <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/andy-sullivan-wins-south-african-open-charl-schwartzel-slumps" target="_blank">coughed up a four-stroke lead with five holes to play</a>. It’s a bummer to see this classy champion’s regression.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Charl-Schwartzel.jpg?itok=ZAiN3GZ5" /> </div> <p><strong>2. Jimmy Walker. A guy who has made winning look easy suddenly has <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/patrick-reed-wins-hyundai-tournament-champions" target="_blank">discovered how tough it can be</a>. All those missed putts on the back nine is graphic evidence of what pressure can do to even the best players in the world.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Jimmy-Walker.jpg?itok=wwGWziMz" /> </div> <p><strong>3. <a href="http://www.pgatour.com/news/2015/01/08/jordan-spieth-justin-thomas-baby-photos.html" target="_blank">The Jordan Spieth-Justin Thomas Twitter “feud.”</a> Swinging their purses at each other would be an uptick in nastiness.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Jordan-Spieth.jpg?itok=SQaLN6rD" /> </div> <p><strong>4. Chris Kirk’s 62. He had to feel like he did something really special in tying the Plantation course record, until Jason Day did the same thing a few hours later, nearly stealing the tournament.</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Chris-Kirk.jpg?itok=DTTbsN6l" /> </div> <p><strong>5. <a href="http://www.golf.com/courses-and-travel/olympic-golf-course-construction-fuels-brazilian-protestors" target="_blank">The ‘Occupy Golf’ protesters in Rio</a>. Really? Is one environmentally sensitive golf course among the biggest problems facing this megatropolis?</strong></p> <div> <img src="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_ap_article/public/2015/01/13/Occupy-Golf.jpg?itok=es_c_BDK" /> </div> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow  <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on  <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to  <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Alan Shipnuck</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:97faee769eeaf3299cd974b961573e94" t="1421160347" feed="200853" position="47"><title>Gil Hanse: Olympic Course in Rio de Janeiro is Ready</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/olympic-course-rio-de-janiero-ready</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/454287906.jpg?itok=c5Wq8zuS" t="image/jpeg" author="Dado Galdieri/Bloomberg Photo">August 2014: An aerial view of Olympic golf course under construction in Rio de Janeiro. (Dado Galdieri/Bloomberg Photo)</enclosure><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_tile_image/public/2014/11/29/2014/03/rio-course.jpg?itok=YNCOyLJo" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Despite delays, Rio is now ready for golf in 2016.</p> <p>The Olympic Golf Course faced a number of setbacks, including lawsuits and delays due to environmental concerns, but course designer Gil Hanse <a href="http://www.golfchannel.com/news/golf-central-blog/hanse-says-olympic-golf-course-complete" target="_blank">told Golf Channel&apos;s &quot;Morning Drive&quot; on Jan. 12</a> that the project is &quot;full steam ahead.&quot;</p> <p>Hanse said that the course is now in full grow-in mode, with the driving range the only remaining section that needs to be grassed.</p> <div> </div> <p>&quot;By all accounts it’s going well,” Hanse told Golf Channel. “We’re still hopeful – the project has obviously had a lot of setbacks here and there along the way, so I can’t expect that it’s going to be completely smooth going forward.</p> <p>&quot;But we’re all enthused; the design is intact. They didn’t ask us to make any changes, so we’re proud of what’s being built.&quot;</p> <p><a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/olympic-official-confident-rio-course-will-be-ready-test-event" target="_blank">A test event will take place later this year</a> or next in preparation for the 2016 games, the first time since 1904 that golf is included in Olympic competition.</p> <div> <em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <a href="https://twitter.com/golf_com">@golf_com</a> on Twitter, like us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a>, and subscribe to <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a>.</em> </div> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Marika Washchyshyn</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:aa6823c6619bb01edd86aacc60daf929" t="1421160346" feed="200853" position="48"><title>Golfers Banned From Throwing Into Stands at Phoenix Open</title><link>http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/golfers-and-caddies-banned-throwing-stands-phoenix-open</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/Mickelsonfootball_APRossFranklin.jpg?itok=Ncj95SWe" t="image/jpeg" author="Getty Images/ Andrew Redington">Getty Images/ Andrew Redington</enclosure><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Sorry, Phil Mickelson, but your days of playing quarterback on the 16th hole at TPC Scottsdale during the Phoenix Open are likely coming to an end. At least the PGA Tour appears to hope so.</p> <blockquote class="twitter-tweet" lang="en"> <p>The PGA Tour becoming like the no fun league. Trying to take the fun out of Phoenix Open. <a href="http://t.co/tuWl7dAwsp">pic.twitter.com/tuWl7dAwsp</a></p> — Alex Miceli (@alexmiceli) <a href="https://twitter.com/alexmiceli/status/555073007056470016">January 13, 2015</a> </blockquote> <p>If the tweeted photo from Miceli, a senior writer at Golfweek, holds true for the January event, then the loudest hole in golf might be a bit tamer this time around.</p> <p>In past years, players enjoyed amplifying the fans with some free gear (Bubba Watson and Rickie Fowler have each tossed free headgear into the stands) as well as the occasional spiraled football from Mickelson. Padraig Harrington even kicked a ball into the stands two years ago.</p> <p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="360" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/cECzlmCQH7c" width="640"></iframe></p> <p>It appears <i>that much</i> fun is too much fun. This of course follows the announcement from a year ago banning the always-fun caddie races from tee to green.</p> <p><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="360" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ubP43qUOVJI" width="640"></iframe></p> <p>With Tiger Woods making his 2015 debut and the Super Bowl being held a few miles away on the final day of the event, there is only so much the PGA Tour can do from the fans at TPC Scottsdale making it the most raucous event of the season.</p> <p><em>For more news that golfers everywhere are talking about, follow <span><a href="https://twitter.com/si_golf">@si_golf</a></span> on Twitter, like us on <span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SI.Golf">Facebook</a></span>, and subscribe to <span><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/GolfMagazine">our YouTube video channel</a></span>.</em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Sean Zak</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:a0c3b34f4b4e5d8f46c90730d3bfe715" t="1421160328" feed="200853" position="49"><title>Michelle Wie Picks Her Fave Photo From 'Most Beautiful Women'</title><link>http://www.golf.com/2015/01/12/michelle-wie-picks-her-favorite-photo-most-beautiful-women-shoot</link><enclosure u="http://cdn-jpg.golf.com/sites/default/files/styles/golf_article_main/public/2015/01/13/michelle_jump_540.jpg?itok=kT1BPfst" t="image/jpeg" author=""/><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="inline-ad inline-ad-right"> <div id="golf-article-inline-flex-small-pos-1" class="ad_slot size_multi_300x250_300x600 max_size_300x250 pos_300x250"></div> </div> <p>Michelle Wie broke through with <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/michelle-wie-wins-us-womens-open-pinehurst-first-major-title" target="_blank">her first-career major victory</a> with a win at the 2014 U.S. Women&apos;s Open. The 25-year-old was runner-up at the year&apos;s first major, the Kraft Nabisco, then was able to hoist a major trophy 12 years after her debut in 2003. </p> <p>Golf.com was fortunate to have Wie participate in the 2015 edition of <a href="http://www.golf.com/tour-and-news/golfcoms-most-beautiful-women-golf-returns" target="_blank">&quot;The Most Beautiful Women in Golf.&quot;</a> She took a look at the final results on Golf.com and selected her favorite photo from the shoot. </p> <p>&quot;I really like the jumping picture,&quot; Wie said of the above photo. &quot;And I love the outfit in that shot!&quot;</p> <p><a href="http://bit.ly/1tRYPVK" target="_blank"><strong>RELATED: The Full Gallery From Wie&apos;s Photoshoot for the &quot;Most Beautiful Women in Golf&quot;</strong></a></p> <p><em>Which photo from Michelle Wie&apos;s shoot do you like the best? Let us know in the comments below. </em></p> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><author> Golf.com Staff</author><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item><item id="urn:onebot:article:6fab7e504e938bd6890575eaa8a8255f" t="1421107200" feed="200853" position="50"><title>Golf Tips, Swing Advice With Top 100 Teacher Brady Riggs</title><link>http://www.golf.com/instruction/golf-tips-swing-advice-top-100-teacher-brady-riggs-6</link><description fullstory="1"><![CDATA[<p><div class="field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden"> <div class="field-items"> <div class="field-item even" property="content:encoded"> <div class="media_embed" height="640px" width="640px"> <div height="640px" width="640px">   </div> <iframe allowtransparency="true" frameborder="0" height="640px" src="//wwwssl.coveritlive.com/embed.html?altcastCode=44ce849797&amp;srcdom=www.coveritlive.com&amp;srcdomsec=wwwssl.coveritlive.com&amp;height=640&amp;entryLoc=top&amp;commentLoc=top&amp;titlePage=on&amp;replayContentOrder=chronological&amp;embedType=stream&amp;titleImage=http%3A%2F%2Fcdnmo.coveritlive.com%2Fmedia%2Favitars%2F201501%2Fphpvwdb44brady-riggs-bunker-shot.jpg" width="640px"></iframe> </div> </div> </div></div></p>]]></description><category>Sports</category><source>Golf</source><channel>Rminutemag1.2311</channel><copyright>Copyright © 2015 TI Golf Holdings, Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright></item></channel>